<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l310-point-shoot-camera/p/itmd7vggudfxzgss?pid=CAMD7VGFFAFGJMJ2&otracker=from-search&srno=t_221&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2erwaJnKn2DUjmfvLxcO%2FRACtJ4P3fDOywM%2BqzpxFh9oaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1a628fb2-5018-4e9f-8924-4ab0d9bd46d1</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">118</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">42</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/j/2/nikon-coolpix-l310-point-shoot-400x400-imad7vgkz6twznck.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">11950</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L310 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I own this camera from since 1-year, and i am feeling great with Coolpix L310. Here are some points you would like to note down this product. 1. 21x optical zoom:-   The main reason i buy this cam was its optical zoom capacity and 21x zoom, its huge.If you move into Hilly Areas then you will realize the presence of Coolpix L310. It reduces 1-mile distance to 10-meter. But you also have to buy a cam stand, because as the zooming increases variations in capturing image also raises due to hands. 2. 14.1 Mp:-   However there are a lot of cams in this price lot and even in lesser one with 14.1 Mp , but that thing is compromise-able. picture quality is really good. 3. Semiprofessional Look :-  As you can see that it have a professional cams look which can attract you , however i have Coolpix in Red color. But after all i love it. 4. Battery Backup:-  i will say that its average. if you are going for a tour i will recommend you to bring a set of non-rechargeable battery cells. cells take 4-6 hours to completely charge and they can live long depending on your usage. One day i bring it to a party and of course i use flash, but after all i was able to take around 250 pics and battery still alive. So i must say that for one day you can use it roughly. 5. video recording:-  well like all other digital cams u can't use flash while recording video. so you need external flash light. But with Coolpix L310 u can record videos with 760pix. and it feels like you are recording a movie(that's depend how you record :p). Its fine for me . 6. Pricing:-  i bought this product last year at the festival of diwali(not from flipkart). I take it from my friend's store which cost me Rs.13200/- plus a diwali gift voucher(hand watch).   So finally i will recommend you that if you are buying this product for tours and travel then it will be good for you. otherwise its all up to you.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I bought this Camera recently 1 month back with 4GB Card + Carry bag + rechargeable kit with 4 battery.The best points that i like in this camera is ... 1. The flash power is very strong as it uses 4 batteries even in total dark. 2. Vibrating or running image can be captured perfectly in sports mode. 3. 14.1 Megapixel with 21x optical zoom is very sharp for any enviornment for a point and shoot camera at this price. 4. Using Auto Mode give a very bright image with more color sharpness and clarity. 5. The CCD image sensor gives a perfect image even in running mode. 6. The battery backup is really amazing as i already took almost 50 snaps day\night and still its active.  If you are planning to buy a reasonable came just go for it.  //  Prodyot Bangalore</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">THIS IS A SERIOUS PIECE OF A STEAL MY FRNDS ... 1.APART FROM ITS BATTERY PROBLEM(i.e..FLASH TAKES AWAY EVERYTHING) ITS TOTAL WORTH TO BUY 2.IT IS A PRO FOR OUTDOOR 3.SETTING IS ON A GO FOR BEGINNERS 4.FEELS LIKE A DSLR 5.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">The L310 from Nikon family is a budget camera for a serious photographer who is tired on carrying SLRs during family outings. It gives the pleasure of using a Bigger Lense Camera with a great 21X optical zoom, while compact in operation even for a novice. The colours are very natural with a perfect and faster focusing. One should not forget to carry a mini tripod to have more control while shooting the distant objects. The lacuna in it is the vibration while using the zoom control as well as occasional out focus during the video recording.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">this camera change your life  hindi  is camere mein bas panorama ko chod ke kuch sikhne ki jarurat nahi hai . aisi gajab ki fotos detA HAI ki bas ...kabhi kabhi aisa lagta hai ki movies banana start kardoon sabko pta hai digi cam mein video mode mein flash nahi chamakta lekin mere kuch gawar dost puch rhe the, isliye plz aisa mat puchna or bas ...main jara fotos kichne bye and go for it not for l810...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Thanks to Flipkart for delivering the product on time. When I brought to the notice about missing SD Card, they immediately couriered it without making any fuss.  Coming to the Camera, It is a wonderful one with amazing clarity and range. Even in the nights where lighting is an issue, it performs well. It has multiple modes, that serves the purpose. Strongly recommending for someone who wants a good camera but on a budget....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">very good camera!! my first cam nd its amazing..looks nd feels lik an SLR..pride among your friends..if u're looking for a amature pro cam..go for it!!!! good zoom..clarity etc..nd flipcart delivered within @ days of order! :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">The service at flipkart is incredible, Nikon coolpix L310 is a superb camera with so many additional features that are not listed on this site, it really worth the price. 13000/- is a steal. Plus the additional goodies really make you feel its a good investment.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">bought this camera for ease of use also read up on it in a photo magazine and they rated it as capable of delivering far better quality than its price tag reflects and I have to say having owned more expensive cameras this is a great allrounder.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">i am facing continuous problem with the camera ,and even i went service center also the problem is not rectifying ,because of this product we loosing trust on Flipkart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5 - 94.5 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 25 - 525 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">21x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">435 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">109.9 (W) x 76.5 (H) x 78.4 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, LR6/L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries (x4), Lens Cap LC-CP22 (with cord), USB Cable UC-E6, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, User's Manual CD, 4 GB SD Card, Pouch, Genuine Nikon battery & charger</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L310</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 6.0 m (W), 1.5 - 3.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.1 - F5.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 0.7 fps up to 19 Images</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto, 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200, 6400 Auto (ISO 80 - 800), Sport Continuous Mode (ISO 400 - 3200)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Sport Continuous, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">25 mm Wde-angle to 525 mm Super-telephoto Coverage</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm ((When Zoom is Set to Middle Position)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Stablizer">Sensor Shuft + Electronic VR Image Stabilization</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">25</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">EXPEED C2 Image Processing System, Scene Auto Selector, Anti-blur, Tripod Socket, Temperature: 0C - 40C, Humidity: 85%, MTP, PTP Data Transfer Protocol, Easy Auto Mode with Scene Auto Selector, Smart Portrait System, Pet Portrait Mode, 3-speed Sport Continuous Mode (H, M, L), DC Input Connector, Vib...View More

EXPEED C2 Image Processing System, Scene Auto Selector, Anti-blur, Tripod Socket, Temperature: 0C - 40C, Humidity: 85%, MTP, PTP Data Transfer Protocol, Easy Auto Mode with Scene Auto Selector, Smart Portrait System, Pet Portrait Mode, 3-speed Sport Continuous Mode (H, M, L), DC Input Connector, Vibration Reduction, 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical Frame Coverage (Playback Mode), 97% Horizontal and 97% Vertical Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4320 x 3240 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Sport Continuous, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Stabilizer">Sensor Shuft + Electronic VR Image Stabilization</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">AAC Monaural</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264, MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">102 MB</specsKey>
