<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s6400-point-shoot-camera/p/itmddaf6z2r4zhzc?pid=CAMDDAYSHY8TW3TX&otracker=from-search&srno=t_316&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3QnjfYa7ZQL%2F8v3KR%2FsHasCZFdwYAfnKIzMHyzyctwh4aLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=77a115fb-88a1-4e50-bcef-820488540c3b</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">22</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/3/t/x/nikon-coolpix-s6400-point-shoot-400x400-imadda25azzwdqrx.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">11350</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S6400 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA), 4608 x 2592 (16:9)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5 - 54 mm (35 mm Equipment to 25 - 300 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">12x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">150 g (Including Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">95.4 (W) x 58.6 (H) x 26.7 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 Years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD Touch Panel with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, Stylus TP-1, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL19 (with battery case), Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, ViewNX 2 CD, Reference Manual CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S6400</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Flash Off, Fill Flash, Slow Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 6.2 m (W), 1.2 - 2.9 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.1 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">25 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256 Segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 10 fps (Continuous H), 19 Images at 2 fps (Continuous L), 5 Images at 18 fps (Pre-shooting Cache)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto, ISO (125 - 1600), ISO 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash, Preset Manual (Custom)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 10 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">31</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Compact Digital Camera, 16.79 Million Total Pixels, 8 Elements in 8 Groups Lens Construction (1 ED Lens Elements), Lens Shift Vibration Reduction, Motion Detection (Still Pictures) Reduction, 12.2 m Macro Mode, Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Auto (9-area Automatic Selection), Center, Manual (F...View More

Compact Digital Camera, 16.79 Million Total Pixels, 8 Elements in 8 Groups Lens Construction (1 ED Lens Elements), Lens Shift Vibration Reduction, Motion Detection (Still Pictures) Reduction, 12.2 m Macro Mode, Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Auto (9-area Automatic Selection), Center, Manual (Focus Area Selected Touch Panel), Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF), Monitor (7.5 cm, Wide Screen, Anti-reflection Coating and 5-level Brightness Adjustment, Approx: 96% Horizontal and Vertical Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode), Approx: 96% Horizontal and Vertical Frame Coverage (Playback Mode), File System (DCF, Exif 2.3, DPOF and MPF Complaint), File Formats (Still Picture: JPEG 3D Images: MPO Sound Files (Voice Memo): WAV Movies: MOV (Video: H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC, Audio: AAC Stereo)), Shooting Modes (Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Draw, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Continuous Shooting (Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (10 fps), Continuous (19 Images Captured Continuously Rate of 2 fps), Pre-shooting Cache (5 Frames Rate of 18 fps), Continuous H: 120 fps (50 Frames Captured Speed of 1 / 120 or Faster), Continuous H: 60 fps (25 Frames Captured Speed of 1 / 60 or Faster), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16, Movie (HD 1080p (Fine) (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 / Approx. 30 fps, HD 1080p: 1920 x 1080 / Approx. 30 fps, HD 720p: 1280 x 720 / Approx. 30 fps, HS 60 fps: 1280 x 720, HS 15 fps: 1920 x 1080, ISO Sensitivity (Standard Output Sensitivity), Exposure: Metering Mode (256-segment Matrix, Center-weighted (Digital Zoom Less than 2x), Spot (Digital Zoom 2x or More), Exposure Control: Programmed Auto Exposure and Exposure Compensation (-2.0 - .0 EV in Steps of 1 / 3 EV), Shutter (Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter), Aperture (Electronically-controlled ND Filter (-2 AV) Selection, Range: 2 Steps (f/3.1 and f6.2 (W)), Self Timer (10 sec and 2 sec), Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Interface: Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP), HDMI Output (Auto, 480p, 720p and 1080i), I/O Terminal: Audio / Video (A / V) Output, Digital I/O (USB), Power Sources (AC Adapter EH-62G), Charging Time (Approx. 3 hrs), Still Pictures (Approx. 160 Shots (EN-EL 19)), Movies (Actual Battery Life for Recording) x 2: HD 1080p (Fine) (1920 x 1080): Approx. 20 mins When Using EN-EL 19 HD 1080p (1920 x 1080): Approx. 20 mins When Using EN-EL 10 HD 720p (1280 x 720): Approx 25 mins When Using EN-EL 10), Tripod Socket: 1 / 4 (ISO 1222), Temperature 0° C - 40° C, 85% Humidity, Digital Zoom Magnification (4x Equivalent Angle) Approx. 1200 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format, 12x Optical Zoom in Slim, Stylish Body, 25 mm Wide-angle to 300 mm Telephoto, Lens-shift VR Image Stabilization, Back-illuminated CMOS Image Sensor, 35 mm Format Equivalent, Intelligent AF, Creative Effects, Full HD 1080p Movie Recording, Optical Zoom and Stereo Sound, Auto Composite Night Shooting, EXPEED C2 Image-processing Engine, Smart Portrait System, Scene Auto Selector, 20 Optimized Scene Modes, Subject Tracking, Eye-Fi Card Support, 3D Photography, LCD with Touch Screen Control, Ultra Compact Camera, Mount Tripod, LCD Viewfinder, Touchscreen, AE Program, Wi-Fi External Connections, Creative Exposure Modes (Back Light, Beach, Black and White Copy, Close Up, Copy, Draw, Dusk / Dawn, Easy Panorama, Fireworks Show, Food, Landscape, Museum, Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Pet Portrait Portrait, Snow, Sports, Sunset, 3D Photography), Mini (Type-C) HDMI Connection, 10 fps Full-resolution Burst Mode (7 Frames), 3.1 Maximum Aperture Range Electronically Controlled ND Filter, Smart Portrait System, Scene Auto Selector, 20 Optimized Scene Modes, Subject Tracking, Eye-Fi Card Support, Auto Composite Night Shooting, Intelligent AF Control System, 10 Continuous-mode Frames / sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, MPO, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, DFC, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-62G (Optional)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">78 MB</specsKey>
