<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d3200-dslr-camera/p/itmdv58hjz4uhmxg?pid=CAMDAA2SJNRTNMZK&otracker=from-search&srno=t_184&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0SejaIRpQvDEMmjw4GlKtPxZFARdT9Pa0wwuee1eVqBYaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=5c320a3f-774a-47ac-acd4-f227d67597ff</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">38</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/z/k/nikon-d3200-400x400-imadaacf5frwy4e7.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">28007</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D3200 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Monaural</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">MH-24 Battery Charger, AN-DC3 Strap, BS-1 Accessory Shoe Cover, DK-20 Rubber Eyecup, EN-EL14 Rechargeable Li-ion Battery (with terminal cover), EG-CP14 Audio/Video Cable, UC-E17 USB Cable, ViewNX 2 CD-ROM, BF-1B Body Cap, Reference CD, DK-5 Eyepiece Cap</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F5.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Image Sensor Cleaning</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix Metering: 3D Color Matrix Metering II (Type G and D Lenses), Color Matrix Metering II (Other CPU Lenses), Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 4 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO in steps of 1 EV (100 - 6400), 1 EV above ISO (12800 Equivalent)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent (7 Types), Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Nikon F Lens Mount (with AF Contact), 1.5x Lens Focal Length (35 mm Format Equivalent, Nikon DX Format), 24.7 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Land...View More

Nikon F Lens Mount (with AF Contact), 1.5x Lens Focal Length (35 mm Format Equivalent, Nikon DX Format), 24.7 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Viewfinder Frame Cavarage: 95% Horizontal and 95% Vertical, Viewfinder Magnification: 0.8 x (50 mm f/1.4 Lens at infinity, -1.0 m-1), 18 mm Eyepoint, -1.7 - 0.5 m-1 Diopter Adjustment, Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark VII Focusing Screen, Quick Return Reflex Mirror, Lens Aperture: Instant Return, Electronically Controlled, Compatible Lenses: Autofocus is Available with AF-S and AF-I Lenses, Autofocus is not Available with Other Type G and D Lenses, AF Lenses (IX NIKKOR and Lenses for the F3AF are not Supported), and AI-P Lenses, Non-CPU Lenses can be Used in Mode M, but the Camera Exposure Meter will not Function. The Electronic Rangefinder can be Wsed with Lenses that have a Maximum Aperture of f/5.6 or Faster, X=1/200 sec Flash Sync Speed, Release Mode: Single Frame, Continuous, Self-timer, Delayed Remote, Quick-response Remote, Quiet Shutter Release, Metering: TTL Exposure Metering using 420-pixel RGB Sensor, Range (ISO 100, f/1.4 Lens, 20C/68F): Matrix or Center-weighted Metering: 0 - 20 EV Spot Metering: 2 - 20 EV, CPU Exposure Meter Coupling, Exposure Mode: Auto Modes (Auto, Auto (Flash Off), Scene Modes (Portrait, Landscape, Child, Sports, Close Up, Night Portrait), Programmed Auto with Flexible Program (P), Shutter-priority Auto (S), Aperture-priority Auto (A), Manual (M), Exposure Compensation: 5 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Exposure Lock: Luminosity Locked at Detected Value with AE-L/AF-L Button, On and Off Active D-Lighting, Focus Detection Range: -1 - EV (ISO 100, 20C/68F), Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S/AF-C Selection (AF-A); Predictive Focus Tracking Activated Automatically According to Subject Status, Anual Focus (MF): Electronic Rangefinder, 11 Focus Point, AF-area Mode: Single-point AF, Dynamic-area AF, Auto-area AF, 3D-tracking (11 Points), Focus Lock, Built-in Flash: Auto, portrait, child, close up, night portrait: Auto Flash with Auto Pop-up, Program, Shutter-priority, Aperture-priority, Manual, Manual Pop-up with Button Release, Guide Number: 12/39, 13/43 with manual flash (m/ft, ISO 100, 20C/68F), Flash Compensation: -3 - EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Flash-ready Indicator, Accessory Shoe: ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync and Data Contacts and Safety Lock, Nikon Creative Lighting System (CLS), AS-15 Sync Terminal Adapter (Sold Separately), Playback: Full-frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar) Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo and/or Movie Slide Shows, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, and Image Comment (up to 36 Characters)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">18 - 55 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 27 - 82.5 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">4512 x 3000 (M), 3008 x 2000 (S), 1920 x 1080, 1280 x 720, 640 x 424</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">6016 x 4000 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, NEF (RAW), NEF (RAW) JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF 2.0, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, MPEG-4 / H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">505 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Cap), 455 g (with Camera Body Only)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">125 (W) x 96 (H) x 76.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Carry in</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC / Compatible with UHS-I</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30p</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
