<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l810-point-shoot-camera/p/itmd72tnzmfjkagz?pid=CAMD72TJQ3VHFDW3&otracker=from-search&srno=t_164&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0Zg%2Fy1cjNS5iImWXtb8dRCX6h%2BYlWUD7eWf5d4ExJyaYaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=7c068d0e-d529-47c0-ba17-8c8fec35b245</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">302</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">76</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/d/w/3/nikon-coolpix-l810-point-shoot-400x400-imad72u5wzmb5tgw.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">9999</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L810 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I own a Nikon Coolpix L310 (14.1mp, ccd, 21x zoom, wide lens), its like the younger sibling of this L810 which is priced at Rs 11.5k. My freind owns a L810, and I got to tell you, if you are thinking about going with this camera, you rather go and get the L310! After using my L310 for a long time, I found certain cons on the L810 which are not there on L310- the camera shows noise on the dark areas... which I think is not there on the L310, and the pictures are likewise noisier (better check for yourselves). Due to the fact the L310 having a better low light sensitivity (with ISO 80-6400) than that of L810 (ISO 80-1600). And mind you, you will need more of that low light sensor than you need the zoom. another thing which I din't liked is that the buttons felt cheaper, than on my L310. Plastic felt indian made.   Rest everything felt good and equal. Battery, flash, clarity, are all just like on the L310.   And if you are still thinking about the L810 because of better specs, let me tell you, practically 14.2mp and 16.1mp make only as much difference as a 3mp and a 3.4mp, you won't even notice it, the difference is so small. Same goes for the zoom, which might be wooing you, while 5x to 10x is like twice the better, but 21x to 26x is negligible. I have used both of them simultaneously, the difference is not noticeable at all.  The only reason for you buying the L810 over L310 is if you want an hdmi port.  The decision is yours. :)  No offence. Yes I am a fan of my camera, but I do not criticize a product just because I don't own it. :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">It is a decked up version of the L120 but miles ahead in performance.The 16.1 Megapixels will never stop to amaze you.I bought it 1 week back,although not from FlipKart and am loving every pixel it clicks. The Autofocus is pretty awesome and photography in low light condition is stunning even without a flash(for moments u don't want to spoil with a flash). The image stabilisers delivers super sharp images even at 14x zoom(unless you are violently shaking).At 26x I was amazed to capture details with clarity(thanks to the EXPEED C2 image processor also).It looks and feels like a DSLR but is much lighter ofcource and comfortable to grip and click. In macro mode I was able to capture the minutest details. Overall its the best value for money at this price range.Perfect for those casual day out's!  Pros: .Look,Feel,Grip .Ultra Zoom .LCD Brightness under sun. .Image stabilizers and processors  Cons: .Don't expect it to fit into your pocket or purse. .Zooming sometimes a bit sluggish(rare moments). .Panorama needs to be stitched manually with the software provided.  This said,its worth a buy.Extremely satisfied.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">What a camera. The clarity of photos during night & the truck loads of modes just make the experience delighful.  For amateurs like me, it would take half an hour to get used to the basic functionalities.  I did not get a chance to click photos during the day, but I am sure it would surpass my expectation.  If you have an old digicam and want to upgrade to psuedo DSLR without taking the hassles of a DSLR. This is it  Flipkart's service was asusual terric (This is my second electronic purchase).</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Wanted to buy a camera but wanted to restrict myself to 15k otherwise sky can be the limit if someone wants to spend money on a camera. Anyways long story short this camera is a pseudo DSLR camera and image quality it is giving me is quite AMAZING!! Video shooting at 720p is awesome as well and can be checked out on youtube for proof. Lastly one of the reviewer had mentioned that having NI-MHx4 batteries is one of this camera's weakpoint is wrong because u may always end up at a place with this beauty where there is no electricity like (some indian and thai villages)and therefore u can buy alkaline batteries to power up this camera for a long time. Lastly NIKON is truly a awesome company to have cramped up so many features in a camera costing only 15k and is EXTREMELY lightweight.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Flip cart is really superb.. I got this camera in just 2 working days as i required.  Excellent Zoom, Good Quality  If u want a camera with good optical zoom this is the right choice!!!!   Packing was great to ensure the safety</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">one of the best VALUE FOR MONEY,, product,,, googling a tons, of cams to start up a beginer level ,,i made a final call after a lot of annalaysation,, this one is simply loaded ,even as a beginer,u feel like pro with L810... amazing clarity, an AWESOME zoooom, macro mode's gr8,,, image stabilizer is decent enough,,, just 2 days of usage & clicked almost 375+ plus snaps, at high resolution,,& also the battery life is cool... for the offerd price its a bankable...  its has made photography experience simply adorable,,trust me u will love it,,as u start understanding ur cam,,,  go get it,,,& explore the world,,a complete different world is waiting to be clicked...! khacchaaaaoooo!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Having better functionality and awesome qualities though got some real negative experience in group photography, just experiencing "Lens Distortion" issue within. found defect in the product. guys, please check your product all the way before you brought.  Second thing when you turn on the camera and try to click images using zoom, the zoom trigger was found fail to work for second's.  Feel that company should rectify this problems from the launched. overall average buying.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I ordered this camera 2 days ago and it was delivered in the promised time. Thank you Flipkart for your amazing service.  Coming to this camera; This is one hell of a camera. Its loaded with stunning features and a powerful lens with splendid zoom capability. Kudos to NIKON.   Coming to the cons; its AA battery powered.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I was looking for a decent bridge camera which was reasonably priced. I went for a Nikon Coolpix L810 just by its brand and its writeup and review here. My mistake. Any camera worth its salt should produce crisp & clear images whatever else features it is loaded with. If it cannot do that then the camera is a worthless piece. The images shot from this camera are worse than the pics shot from any ordinary point and shoot cameras costing half its price. Just google using the search phrase "Nikon Coolpix L810 Image Quality" and you will know the story. I did not do this due diligence before buying, so now I am poorer by 13.5k and stuck with a camera which I am not going to use. That said, I should say Flipkart patiently listened to all my complaints and promptly responded to my mails. But ultimately they are not willing to exchange it for another brand which is higher priced but willing to replace the same camera! Strange! This is my last tryst with online shopping. Thank you very much!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Very good product to purchase in this range... Gives a touch of using a DSLR lots of modes to play .. (Panaroma,Smile,red eye reduction,3D images, HD Video recording etc..) works on 4pic NIMH batteries, wich can be avilable at any places where power shortage like villages, picnics etc, or when there is no source of charging it. Shutter speed is wonderfull. in totality exelent product..</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.0 - 104.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 22.5 - 585 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">26x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">430 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">111.1 (W) x 76.3 (H) x 83.1 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, LR6/L40 (AA-size) alkaline batteries (x4), Lens Cap LC-CP25 (with Cord), USB Cable UC-E16, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Reference Manual CD, 4 GB SD Card, Pouch, Genuine Nikon battery & charger</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L810</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, On, Off, Red-Eye, Slow-sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 5.0 m (W), 1.5 - 2.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.1 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">22.5 mm Wide-angle Landscapes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.2 fps up to 4 Images</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto, 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600 (Auto Gain from ISO 80 - 1600)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm ((When Zoom is Set to Middle Position)</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">HDMI Mini Connector (Type C)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">LPCM Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264, MPEG-4, AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">50 MB</specsKey>
