<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-p530-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdu7qxtvgrzcbr?pid=CAMDU7QXTVGRZCBR&otracker=from-search&srno=t_4&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3x0q1Vj4c64A8APyPUp1%2Fw7ovcZ2TLIq%2BF9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.3</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">58</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">23</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/b/r/nikon-coolpix-p530-point-shoot-400x400-imaeyxfagug5hzuz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">14962</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix P530 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">i purchased this yesterday from a local store for 17.5k.This camera is realy awsome..but donot realy pump your expectation like a dslr camera,but it definitly does the job if you are new in photography..pictures in low light has a promlem to keep in focus and slight shaky hands will find dificulty to take perfect pictures(specialy in macro shot).flash is awsome and helps a lot to take amazing pictures...better use night mode if you are clicking pictures of moon in night..at full zoom you will not get a perfect steady shot,so selection night mode will fix this issue....daylight pictures are awsome over all picture quality,if taken perfectly will bolw your mind...no wifi,view finder is a steal,it has manual control as well as auto,operation is very simple and easy(anyone can operate without problem....go for it for this price value</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I bought this yesterday . Cam is good but drawback is dominating the yellow shade. i am unable to capture original picture colors. I put it on auto mode and took the snaps but the cam is failed to capture true colors pic has captured mixed with yellow shade. this is not fair</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">It's chager started not working after 30 days only. When I called nikon customer care, executive told that they dont cover accessaries in 1 year warranty.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">excellent product with good price. it will nicely capture the photos and videos, it has the very good zoom capacity. Nikon designed a good product</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Excellent camera.its zoom is unbelievable and it covers upto1km distance.Camera quality is very very good with wide lenses.Flash is simply great.Overall best product i feel.So, go for it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Thnks flipkart and ws retail.A very good camera for biggners with less than 16000.The camera has excillent picture quality with a bunch of features.I think it is the great product speacilly with the price.I got also a bag,hdmi cable,8 gb class 10 sd card by sundisk and also thnk you ws retail.In other shop the price is 18000-19500 but in ws retail it is affortable.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">>Super Zoom >Great flash performance >Great battery life >Good indoor shots >snappy >Has a decent EVF  You wouldn't regret! i got it for 14k along with 8GB card n carry case, i think its a real good deal!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">it is an amazing product by nikon.. it's within budget.. i've purchased it for rs 16680...  it's zoom is unbelievable..  it shows a crystal clear effect even in 42x..... the colour sensation is good..  the auto focus is little bit slow.... it is good for auto and programmed mode..... the grip is very well designed.. it can easily fit to hand.. the inbuilt photo editing programmer is great..... the operating programme is very easily and can be operated by any one.... the video recording is full hd.... the battery backup is not too good....  as a conclusion it is very good and helpful for beginner photographers......  it is easy and within your budget.... :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">This is the one of the best cameras i have ever seen. the zoom is superb ...even at 78x it is crystal clear. slow motion photography results are awesome. i purchased it before it came to flipkart . if you want to know what this camera do , you should visit the page- Photography Without a Slr at Facebook . fb/youngpointandclick are their address . I bet after seeing the photos captured on this camera you must will buy this</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Nothing is mentioned about warrant...it just say 2 years of warranty Need to know how to avail the warranty of Nikon p530. Kindly list down the procedure for the same</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Type">Mechanical, CMOS Electronic Shutter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Speed in other Modes">-1 - 1/4000 sec, -15 - 1/4000 (when ISO Sensitivity is 100 in M Mode), when the Aperture Value is Set to f/6.6 - f/8.3 (Wide-angle End)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">16.76</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Movie (1080/30 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080 / 25 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/60i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/50i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/25 f...View More

Movie (1080/30 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080 / 25 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/60i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/50i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (480/30 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (480/25 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (HS 480/4x: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (HS 720/2x: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (HS 1080/0.5x: 1920 x 1080 (16:9))</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.3 - 180 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 24 - 1000 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Construction">14 Elements in 10 Groups (4 ED Lens Element)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Focus Features">Focus Area Selecton: Target Finding AF, Face Priority, Manual (Spot), Manual (Normal), Manual (Wide), Subject Tracking, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Pre-flashes, Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 4000 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus Range">50 cm (1 ft, 8 inch) - Infinity (W), 2.0 m (6 ft, 7 inch) - Infinity (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">42x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">494 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">122.8 (W) x 84.1 (H) x 98.2 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Modes">Programmed AE with Flexible Program, Shutter-priority Auto, Aperture-priority Auto, Manual, Exposure Bracketing Enabled</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Exposure">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Compensation">1/3 EV Steps +/- 2.0 EV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brightness Adjustment">5 Levels Brightness Adjustment</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Connectivity Features">HDMI Output: Can be Selected from Auto, 480p, 720p, and 1080i, I/O Terminal: Audio / Video Output, Digital I/O (USB)</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Tripod Socket">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Charging AC Adapter, USB Cable, Lens Cap, User Manual, Nikon Digital Camera Coolpix P530 1 Set (Including: Strap, Rechargable Battery, AV Cable, Warranty Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">P530</specsKey>
<specsKey="Processor">Expeed C2 Image-processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 7 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 7), Continuous L (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 1 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 200), Pre-shooting Cache (the Frame Rate for Continuou...View More

Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 7 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 7), Continuous L (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 1 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 200), Pre-shooting Cache (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 15 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 20, Including a Maximum of 5 Frames Captured in the Pre-shooting Cache), Continuous H:120 fps (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 120 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 60), Continuous H:60 fps (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 60 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 60), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16, Intvl Timer Shooting</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100 - 1600, ISO 3200 - 6400 (Available when Using P, S, A or M Mode) Hi 1 (ISO 12800 Equivalent)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M...View More

Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M, User Settings</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">ISO Sensitivity (Auto): 0.5 - 8.0 m (W), 1.5 - 4.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">1 cm (0.4 inch) - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey="Temperature">0° C - 40° C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Humidity">85%</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering Modes">Matrix, Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish...View More

Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish, Swedish, Tamil, Telugu, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian, Vietnamese</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Viewfinder: 0.5 cm (0.2 inch), 201,000 dots Equivalent LCD with the Diopter Adjustment Function (+/- 4 m -1), Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift, Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Still Pictures: 240 Shots when Using EN-EL5, Charging Time: 4 hr 10 min (when Using Cha...View More

Viewfinder: 0.5 cm (0.2 inch), 201,000 dots Equivalent LCD with the Diopter Adjustment Function (+/- 4 m -1), Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift, Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Still Pictures: 240 Shots when Using EN-EL5, Charging Time: 4 hr 10 min (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-70P and when No Charge Remains), Movie Recording (Actual Battery Life for Recording), 1 hr when Using EN-EL5, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode and Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Maintain Optimum Contrast with Active D-lighting</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M...View More

Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M, User Settings</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">4608 x 3072 (3:2), 3456 x 3456 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">File System: DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Megapixels">4608 x 3456 (16 M), 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Audio: LPCM Stereo, WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Still Image Size 16:9">4608 x 2592 (12 M), 1920 x 1080 (2 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">JPEG Sound Files (Voice Memo), MOV (Video: H.264 / MPEG-4, AVC)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Aspect Ratio">16:9, 3:2, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-70P AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">56 MB</specsKey>
