<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l820-advanced-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdhwhafdkgs2ec?pid=CAMDGA2HAFXRVQVX&otracker=from-search&srno=t_159&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff11BqojLDa%2FG%2FLOUUJ%2BsIPLFCsg6EputWPbAfZ%2FmKkJvoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=a1b53757-b30a-4964-8785-1ac6f15c41cf</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">451</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">156</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/q/v/x/nikon-coolpix-l820-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadgc386ggbxvxm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">14199</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L820 Advanced Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Blue</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Advanced Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Hi! Pulkit, I am using this Nikon L820 for 3 to 4 months and I have no issue related to this product. I recommend to you please read user manual and control's properly (nikon L820 semi-dslr) and hold your camera very confidently and let make your eyes like a professional snapper for capturing a single frame in micro-seconds. More you active more you get best result of photography. Here you try to understand what happens if I take a still image of fast moving object. Our camera Nikon L820 have a flash range of 7 to 11 meters so I made a test of CEILING FAN with speed regulator (1 to 5 steps). I put the speed of fan from 1 to 5 simultaneously and take 5 sets of still shots of each steps of fan speed. At 1 step speed of fan I put it on sports mode and opens the flash continues, AF mode is On. The 4 of 5 shots are good in image details. In 2 and 3 step speed of fan I put same sports mode, open flash hood and On AF mode now here I get same 7 of 10 shots good image (I am able to count 3 fins as same as switch off fan). Now 4 and 5 step speed of fan I make an off AF mode, in sports mode and open flash, now at 600 to 700 RPM I am able to count the fins of fan and 8 of 10 shots are well detailed (all shots are in without ZOOM, use Nikon's BSS, ISO250- 400 and images are cropped to 100%) with my Nikon L820. You have to read manual thoroughly and do this practical exercise to get crispy shots of moving objects. I am sure you get the perfect picture of photography. ENJOY ITT....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I've purchased this cam today, Although I didn't purchased this through flipkart I would like to share my experience about this Nikon Coolpix l820.  It's simply awesome. I tested in different ways and it satisfied me well.  Here are my pros and cons list.   Pros: -> Zooming is very nice... I am able to identify a person's face far away from me with this zoom. -> I took a video(1080p), I copied it to my laptop and watched it. It's really superb. It's like watching a documentary film :)  -> Clarity of pictures took by l820 are really attractive. We can take 3D images too. -> I tested the slow motion video and it's really good.  Cons: -> I felt that it's some what heavy.Not much, but I hold it with one hand.. after few minutes I feel some discomfort due to it's weight or may be due to it's small size I feel some discomfort to hold it. -> The display is fixed and cannot be adjustable. Taking tricky shots and making movie are somewhat uncomfortable.    It's basic and simple. No extraordinary features and options are present. I don't say it's a con because of it's price range.  Personal Note: I really hate myself as I often forget to remove the lens cap and clicking power on button. :( The lens try to come outside but this cap blocks. this made the cam make small noise and I feel sad assuming there may be some damages in internal structure(hope not). Be careful and remember this point if you are going to buy a cam like this.  If your budget is at this range better to go for it. I'm giving it a ***** rating.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Hi every one I am posting my review of Nikon L820. First of first it have CMOS backlit image sensor for dark night shootings and decent battery performance. Second one is back light HDR feature which enhance clear and crisp images even in low light. I am much impressed its picture performance and ISO3200 (auto) which automatic produces great results. Another interesting thing is Stereo Mic with full HD (30 fps) (1080i) video recording rejoices moments every time. After 10 days I am able to write this review and it takes 469 {superb} shots full charge (only 4.5 hrs for 4 cells) NiMH batteries (Nikon) in which 173 shots use flashes. The still images are detailed and color depth/ saturation is above average. I also develop (6*8) size still photos which are quite good in appearance. I personally recommend this advance point and shoot camera to travelers or semi professionals photographer. points (9.0/10). Cons- Except no external flash (Hot shoe) and no tilt screen.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Not doubt camera is Good. wel.. this is about "flippkkart". they used to deliver the items on next day. Now, to earn Rs.90 more.. they r charging for next day delivery. otherwise u will have to wait for full 3 days. HOW PITY FLIPKRT... keep it up.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">1. Best possible option for not so expert photographers. 2. THE option at this price with the features stuffed inside this 1. 3. 16 Megapixel is sufficient for a normal starter. 4. Delivery time was 48 hours, with a Sunday in between. 5. The FK team was decent enough to call & update us regarding delivery of the product. 6. A good bargain, as I bought a SD Card and got extra 5% discount on the deal.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">this is the latest launch by nikon that have ability to shake entire camera market. this will be the gem of camera .  pros - 1 - CMOS image sensor - available in only high priced cameras 2 - full HD video recording 1080p 3 - support alkaline lithium and NIMH batteries with those you can take up to 500 to 7500 shots with single recharge  4 - iso 3200 auto 5 - crystal clear display with 3 inch and 921,000 dots with anti reflection coating 6 - and last zoooooommmmmmmm.......... 30x optical and 4x digital  just find out no any company is giving such features with this price ...... nikon rocks......</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Excellent Camera for its price with outstanding battery life.. and great service from Flipkart as always.. Just like to mention the pros and cons in simple words..  Pros. 1. Amazing 22.5mm Wide angle lens that captures a lot of details. 2. 30x zoom can be very handy if you're in an auditorium, sitting at the back trying to capture your childs performance..(just one of the many uses of this amazin lens) 3. BSI CMOS with f/3 - f/5.8 Aperture captures really good low light images with much lesser noise(grains) as compared to other digicams under 20k price range. 4. 921k dots, 3inch LCD screen is a beauty..  5. The size of the camera gives you a good grip, and is good even for people with small hands..  6. Navigating through menu is very simple as it primarily has only auto , easy and scene mode(perfect for anyone to just point it and start shooting). 7. The battery life is outstanding!! i have used other point and shoots that use lithium ion batteries in the past, mostly sony with battery capacity of 800 mah or max 1000 mah, giving you a roughly 200 shots with mixed flash usage.. this camera uses 4 AA type cells and the one supplied with the camera is recjhargable 2300 mah each! so 4 cells gives you roughly 9200 mah of power enough for 600 shots with mixed usage and video.. 8. 1080p video recording with stereo audio looks crisp on my HDTV. Also has wind noise reduction.  Cons (I'm really having a hard time thinking of some) 1. No viewfinder - Can be a a deal breaker for some but i think one can live without it with such a good 3 inch lcd (specially if you compare the rest of the features for its price) 2. No manual controls , (PASM) (Not needed for a casual photographer.) 3. the supplied 4 GB card(Class 4) is good enough to get you started but you will have to upgrade it to a bigger capacity Class 10 card for faster shot to shot performance and recording Full HD videos. 4. slightly on the heavy side  Thats about it.. the packaging from flipkart was great and it has everything to get you started. The camera fits nicely in the Camera pouch.. There are 4 non rechargeable batteries to get you started immediately ( 4 rechargeable with charger too !) and lens cap, strap, 4 GB memory card, TV cable (standard AV) and USB cable ..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">This is my first camera from a brand like Nikon. After waiting for nearly a year, I bought it from flipkart in the month of January, 2014 at an affordable price of Rs.12529/-. I used the camera for nearly 2 months & I am very much happy with its performance. I would like to highlight few pros & cons....  Pros: 1. A 16.0 Megapixel Point & Shoot camera which captures very high quality photos  & videos......  2. 30 X Optical zoom is the real advantage the camera has over others. Image  quality is brilliant even at 30 X optical zoom. If your hands are stable you can  click stable images even at 30 X zoom without a tripod......  3. The camera has another big advantage of recording Full HD videos. Video quality  is just mind blowing. But you need to use a tripod while using this camera for   video recording at high zoom for stability of your captured videos......  4. It comes with a HDMI cable, USB cable, AV cable, 4 Ni-MH Rechargeable  batteries, Charger, 4 GB SD Card, 4 Alkaline Non Rechargeable batteries,  & a Camera Pouch from Nikon itself & not from flipkart......  5. Very easy to use even for first time users like me.......  6. Photo quality is just awesome, clear, bright & vivid even under low light &  complete darkness which is a big plus point for this camera.......  7. Ni-MH Rechargeable Batteries lasts really for long hours......  Cons: 1. Camera is a bit heavy to hold for long time use while recording videos.....  2. Need to use a tripod for better image stability (under high zoom)......  3. Photos become blurry sometimes if you don't use appropriate camera settings..  Besides all these I would highly recommend this camera by just closing my eyes. Anyone looking to buy a camera for the first time should have a look at this camera & I am sure that Nikon L820 will not disappoint you. Finally thanks flipkart for their very good packing & timely delivery...........</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">U cant get a better camera in this price range.Period.  Amazing clarity..Awesome picture resolution..Best zoom in its class....  Had seen at least 5-10 cameras,including canon powershot sx500IS before buying this one...None of them cud match this one's quality and precision.  Flipkart does it again (and I really dont kno how !!! ).Ordered the camera at 6 PM on saturday..got it delivered at 2 PM the other day...Best delivery system in the country after Mumbai's Dabbawalas....Well Done Flipkart...U guys never fail to impress me...Keep it up</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">I bought this camera from a retail store and not from Flipkart. Since I read a review before buying anything , thought would share my views on this purchase.  I needed a basic point and shoot which could shoot good quality pics and video with large optical zoom and good image stabilization , decent picture quality , decent battery life, fast enough auto-focus in both modes with min 30 fps video.  The idea was to carry one instrument for the occasional travel or family outing. The idea was NEVER to have a camera with a multitude of "MANUAL" features.Having these implies you need to understand photography in more detail. I have a Canon Powershot IS 570IS which is very good in auto mode and provides a fair bit of manual options. More often than not the manual settings end up in a disaster.   Before buying this I compared Sony HX300\Canon SX50 HS which offer better zoom but are higher priced. I found Sony pics to be too soft while video was excellent. Canon had excellent image quality but found the video a bit jerky(24 fps?) and constantly trying to auto-focus.  Sony Hx50V was a strong contender but its build quality looked cheap(it shouldn't have mattered but alas it did...)   L820 meets all my requirements . This is after almost 3 days of extensive usage.  Pics are sharp , low light images are decent , You have to use the predefined modes to compensate the lack of manual controls in low light , motion blur but this is ok.  Lack of a View Finder doesn't bug me so I don't miss it   Flash is good enough, video is pretty nice with zero lag (have played it on my HDTV), battery life is decent .Eneloop rechargeable s are good enough , it takes lithium AAA which apparently last for > 700 shots (though I have yet to try it).  Buy this if my requirement matches yours and you are happy to be blissfully ignorant instead of trying to improvise on every image (cause it never ends...).  Don't buy this if you are a person who loves fiddling around with manual controls and eventually wants to buy an SLR.  Don't buy this if you are a person who loves fiddling around with manual controls and doesn't realize how to use it but STILL eventually wants to buy an SLR  P.S. The build quality is excellent and my kid loves the Red color...</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Image Size: 4608 x 3456 (16 M), 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 4608 x 2592, Movie: 1080 / 30p: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 1080 / 30p: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 720 / 30p: 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, iFrame 540 / 30p: 960 x 540 / 16:9 /...View More

Image Size: 4608 x 3456 (16 M), 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 4608 x 2592, Movie: 1080 / 30p: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 1080 / 30p: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 720 / 30p: 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, iFrame 540 / 30p: 960 x 540 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 480 / 30p: 640 x 480 / 4:3 / 30 fps, HS 240 / 8x: 320 x 240 / 4:3, HS 480 / 4x: 640 x 480 / 4:3, HS 720 / 2x: 1280 x 720 / 16:9, HS 1080 / 0.5x: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.0 - 120 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 22.5 - 675 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">30x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">470 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">111.0 (W) x 76.3 (H) x 84.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, Lens Cap LC-CP28 (with Cord), LR6/L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries (x4), Reference Manual CD, USB Cable UC-E16, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, ViewNX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L820</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 6.0 m (W), 1.5 - 6 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3 - F5.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 8 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600, ISO 3200 (Auto Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Progr...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Program, Smart, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type D, Micro HDMI Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">32</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">EXPEED C2 Image Processing System, Lens Construction: 12 Elements in 9 Groups (2 ED Lens Elements), Motion Blur Reduction Detection (Still Pictures), Focus-area Selection Center, Face Detection, Frame Coverage Shooting Mode: 97% Horizontal and 97% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverag...View More

EXPEED C2 Image Processing System, Lens Construction: 12 Elements in 9 Groups (2 ED Lens Elements), Motion Blur Reduction Detection (Still Pictures), Focus-area Selection Center, Face Detection, Frame Coverage Shooting Mode: 97% Horizontal and 97% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage Playback Mode: 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Exposure Control Programmed Auto Exposure and Exposure Compensation: -2.0 - .0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Shutter Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, Electronically-controlled ND Filter (-2 AV) Selection Aperture, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, HDMI Output Auto, 480p, 720p and 1080i, 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Temperature: 0° C-40° C, Humidity: 85%, Side Zoom Lever, Back-illuminated 16 MP CMOS Sensor, Compact Body, Smart Portrait System, Retouch Menu, 19 Scene Modes, Easy Sharing, Wireless Transfer</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Progr...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Program, Smart, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, MPO, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">AAC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">35 MB</specsKey>
