<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s1100pj-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdv58djhufgbnx?pid=CAMCVWJFHNJ4FZP6&otracker=from-search&srno=t_452&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff1m2jia%2B3WTucDOAJjXQTCLWdr2rFdXru1BZx3Gt9wX%2B4aLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=99155b2a-8655-453f-886f-08adb91eb056</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.3</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">10</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/p/6/nikon-s1100pj-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqfzptv3nuk.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">12562</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S1100PJ Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR ED Glass Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">5.0-25.0mm / F3.9-5.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">155 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">100.8 (W) x 62.7 (H) x 24.1 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD Touchscreen Monitor</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720p, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">USB Cable UC-E6, Camera, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12, View NX 2 CD, Charging AC Adapter MH-65p, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, Remote Control ML-L5, Stylus TP-1, User Manual, Camera Strap AN-CP17</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">Coolpix S1100PJ</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.3 - 3.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 0.9 fps up to 4 shots</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto gain ISO 80 - 800), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 80 to 200, ISO 80 to 400), Manual selection: ISO 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (Pixel Addition), 6400 (Pixel Addition)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Subject tracking mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Spot metering (meters 3.5-mm circle centered on selected focus point)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">24</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Projector, Monitor Frame Coverage, PictBridge</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4320 x 3240 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene mode, Scene Auto Selelctor, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Subject tracking mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">mono/wav file, MOV movie</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">One Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12 (Supplied), AC Adapter EH-62F (Available Separately), Still pictures: 220 Shots, Movie: 1 Hr 35 min (HD 720p (1280 x 720)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">79 MB</specsKey>
