<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d3100-with-af-s-18-55-mm-vr-kit-dx-nikkor-35-f-1-8g-dslr-camera/p/itmdtak8tjxzvd59?pid=CAMDTAKFFB2PXGWF&otracker=from-search&srno=t_154&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0L%2F2GEbY%2BmrnzDu9qm7kmkRkhjNKDziVHbAfZ%2FmKkJvoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=a1b53757-b30a-4964-8785-1ac6f15c41cf</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating"></specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings"></specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/g/w/f/nikon-d3100-with-af-s-18-55-mm-vr-kit-af-s-dx-nikkor-35-mm-f-1-400x400-imadte39zsdyuqjg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">34500</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D3100 (with AF-S 18 - 55 mm VR Kit + AF-S DX NIKKOR 35 mm f/1.8G DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D3100 (with AF-S 18 - 55 mm VR Kit + AF-S DX NIKKOR 35 mm f/1.8G</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap AN-DC3, USB cable, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, AF-S 18-55mm VR Kit Lens, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL14, Rubber Eyecup DK-20, Camera Body, User Manual, Quick Charger MH-24, Body Cap BF-1B, 2 Ferrite Core, View NX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Red-Eye, Slow, Red-Eye Slow, Rear curtain</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">3D color matrix metering (type G and D lenses, color matrix metering II (other CPU lenses), Center-weighted (weight given to 8-mm circle in center of frame), Spot metering (meters 3.5-mm circle centered on selected focus point)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Continuous shooting mode: Approx. 3fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (12800 with boost)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white-balance with 420-pixel RGB sensor) Incandescent Fluorescent Direct sunlight Flash Cloudy Shade White balance preset</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">20</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Operating Temperature: 0Deg - 40Deg C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection by Nikon Multi-CAM 1000 autofocus module with AF-assist (range Approx. 0.5-3m), 11 focus point; Detection range: -1 to EV (ISO 100 at 20C/68F),</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">18 - 55 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">3456 x 2304, 2304 x 1536</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3072 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (12 bit compressed RAW) JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV movie (H.264/MPEG-4 compression format with monaural sound)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter (Available Separately; Requires Optional EP-5A Power Connector)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">455 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">124 (W) x 96 (H) x 74.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Eye-level penta-Dach mirror type; built-in diopter adjustment (-1.7 to .5m-1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Eye-level penta-Dach mirror type; built-in diopter adjustment (-1.7 to .5m-1)</specsKey>
