<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l26-point-shoot-camera/p/itmd7fnxcsnfzfxz?pid=CAMD7FNWYQNGXF5W&otracker=from-search&srno=t_224&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0tA6qv0a5GHb%2B7Q228TA1l5CBvpaSE6pt5gmP7cxE1hIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=5c7873f1-42c1-4916-ab30-d5583898631f</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">391</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">129</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/f/5/w/nikon-coolpix-l26-point-shoot-400x400-imad7fzrhj3mur76.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">5069</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L26 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I ordered this cam on 5th march n expected delivery was aftr 2-4 days but it was delivered on 6th march(my bro's birthday) itself !!! making the event even auspicious :) B) hats off to flipkart for such a superfast service \\m//  well about d product its just freaking awesome :) complete paisa vasool product. dont waste time searching a decent cam below Rs.7k just go for this(i wasted abt 7-8 days searching a decent one)  PRO's => 1)16 megapixel =>clear n sharp pictures 2)Quality of 5x optical zoom doesnt dissapoint 3)pictures taken @nite r gud(even when zoomed) 4)flash is powerful & range is also gud 5)720p HD recording is too gud 6)internal 20mb memory 7)expandable memory upto 32gb's 8)3" clear screen 9)very easy to use 10)all shooting modes r gr8(compared to products within this price range) 11)economical =>best u can get at this price wit all features 12)trust of nikon B)  CONS => 1)AA battery=>performance far better than other cam's so hardly matters 2)720p video recording cannot b paused :p  suggestion : Do order Sony NH-AA-B2EN Rechargeable Battery OR Fujicell Fujiloop(2900 mAh) Rechargeable Battery for a much better battery performance  its an awesome product just go for it without hesitation 10/10 to flipkart as well as nikon!!!! :)" highly recommended :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I just got the delivery of my new Coolpix L26.  Just 6000+/- [inclusive of the 2800 mAH batteries]... you cant ask for more. Wait a sec - they did give more gifts :) + a camera pouch [Rs. 190/-]  + 4 GB SD card [Rs. 200/-] + Battery charger [Rs. 170/-]  1. Remarkable is the AA battery option. [10/10] I have seen on many occasions my friends camera lasted only about 200 shots... if you think that's a large number, it not! hardly 1 hour of photoshoot, which if you are on tour... is nothing. L26 lasts about 500+ shots with my 2800 maH batteries.  2. Brilliant automode performance in daylight and night mode aint bad either. [9/10] Now for those who are fooling others by boasting about 21 in-built modes... dont bother! most of the ppl dont even try to use those options unless they want a panorama snap. But the auto-mode works fine, so need not to worry.   3. Indoor pics arnt as clear as i wanted them to be. [In short 8/10] Grainy images spoiled my mood little bit but then i fixed some options and its satisfactory now.  4. Dont zoom much, it wont help!  5. The shutter speed is amazing and it hardly takes 1 second to process the image you just clicked so... that's awsm.  All in all... gr8 product for around 6000 K... If you want to complain, i would like to point out.. "WHY NOT BY A DSLR then :P "</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">You get what you pay for.  I bought this camera to use it for outdoor activities where my DSLR would be too big to carry. Like during cycling, trail running to capture those moments.  - The camera has till now performed very well in good daylight, but the low light performance leaves a lot to be desired (expected in this price range). - The size of the overall package is another reason why I bought it. It is small and compact enough to carry around without feeling the weight.  I shot video with it and as long as you do not shoot hand held, the quality is good. Though video is not something I use a lot, I think I will shoot more after seeing the output this small camera can produce.  The camera looks a bit plasticy and I expected a better finish on the body. My older outdoors camera was a DSC W5 from Sony and it was an all metal body.  I liked the fact that this came bundled with a 4GB memory card and rechargeable batteries and its charger. Helped me get going immediately. While on the topic of batteries, the camera is holding its charge really well and I haven't had to recharge it, as yet.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">ny other company ready to give specs like this? 16.1mp 5x zoom hd recording at rs.5500 suerly go for this one as it is the best in the range .The images are clear and sharp. Recording is too good. The flash is good. and it fits nicely in your hand.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Delivery: 5 Stars (record time)  Product: 4 Stars (details below) Ease of use - 4 Stars (Pro: Distinct Video button) Picture Quality - 4 Stars (Display 3 stars, grainy dark pictures, overexposure, Full screen pictures pretty decent 4 stars, Outside shots good colors 4 stars) Zoom - 4 Stars ( Optical zoom pretty neat, digital zoom too sensitive on handheld mode) Internal Memory: 5 Stars Surprise (didnt expect at this price point) Screen 3 inch: 5 Stars (beats competition)  Accessories: 3 Stars Watch !! Good Surprise Battery and case: basic but suffice  Warranty: 4 Stars no Surprises here  Overall: 4 stars Value for money, pretty neat for a basic camera and a steal at 5K price point. Few of the 16 MP 5X camera at this price range. Beats competition (canon and cybershot) at this price point. Fuji is not a competition with Nikon coolpix (confusion about there warranty policy as well!). Complete set with rechargable batteries, memory card and case, so start using on day 1.   Easy interface makes this a first choice, specially since I expect my parents to use this a lot.  Thanks! Abhinav</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Well Flipkart service is exceptional...!  Not really happy with the clarity of the pics taken (L26) at 16 M.P . pics taken at 8 MP through mobile is much better.  Wouldn't recommend this particular L26 model to others.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I shall rate the various features in 1-10 scale:  1.Looks,Finishing and style :Pretty good from the front but plastic panel at the back,which looks a bit cheap. (7/10)  2.Picture Quality: The picture quality is good.Its gives decent images in low light conditions also.(8/10)  3.HD Video Recording : Sorry to say its not as expected. The video appears to be bit grainy and i m not that impressed.(6/10)  4.Flash and Night Mode : The flash is powerful enough.I tried taking snaps in complete darkness and the camera gave good results. (9/10)  5.Battery Capacity : It has a flexible battery facility ie., both Ni-mH and normal alkaline batteries work. So even if the rechargeable Ni-mH is out , you can continue shooting using easily available AA alkaline batteries. (10/10)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I GOT THIS CAM TODAY, ITS LIGHT WEIGHT ANS CUTE. ALSO HAVE MANY GOOD FEATURES LIKE 16MP,HD RECORDING, 5X ZOOM, CCD IMAGE SENSOR ETC. I FOUND ITS COST EFFECTIVE PRODUCT. I RECOMMEND L26 CAM TO ALL WHO WANT 16MP CAM. THANK U FLIPKART FOR YOUR SERVICE.....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">no doubt about the product n flipkart service ..... they are gud but if someone is attracted by the offers, then he/she must think twice before buying.... Actually , 4 batteries r given wid the camera n they are just the "demo" batteries and r not rechargeable at all. After few pics click they will get exhausted. Meaning thereby u hv to buy the separate rechargeable batteries.  I was surprised by this as i didn`t found these things mentioned anywhere before buying.  thts all.  and hope not to get more surprises...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">this is my first camera which i bought from flipkart . i was expecting good performance of the camera but camera is so so type in performance .  pictures in the evening are not good ..  if u want good camera for occasionally , u should buy other camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 23.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 130 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">164 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">96.0 (W) x 59.7 (H) x 28.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, LR6/L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries (x2), USB Cable UC-E16, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Reference Manual CD, 4 GB card, Camera Case, AA battery, Battery Charger</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 3.6 m (W), 0.8 - 1.7 m (T) (ISO Auto)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.2 fps up to 4 Images</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto Gain) ISO 80 to 1600</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">28 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 10 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Recording Time (With Full Batttery): 30 - 40 mints</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">20 MB</specsKey>
