<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l610-point-shoot-camera/p/itmddqfjatdjbhf4?pid=CAMDDQQVK97KZZK9&otracker=from-search&srno=t_404&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3ZMcfWXYLrF8dNAJH%2F0Jsc2ZojQzcZCFdTSZ%2BGEUlyJIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=8380be3e-0a03-45a1-bd25-80add7507bb8</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">62</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">20</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/z/k/9/nikon-coolpix-l610-point-shoot-400x400-imadjz23zentytkz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">6965</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L610 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">pros: best feature is uses 2 aa batteries can be available anywhere grip of camera is too good to take photos without using other hand picture quality is also very good optical zoom is very good to take clear photos from large distance  cons: slow processing in playback mode eat too much battery  but i bought extra batteries to make my camera always ON & i use PC to check captured photos, so overall i liked it very much. if you are buying a travel zoom camera then it is the best option in 10k range</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Things I Like : The optical zoom is very good, better than I imagined. There is a good variety of scene ( Picture mode) selections, which are excellent. Clarity of photos are good. I do not like: The camera takes a longer time to record the image after exposure. The case is same when a frame is deleted. Even though, I would recommend one to buy it.The camera is a good choice between a base model and an SLR.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">The time is over to look after and search the best camera in cool price. This camera is best in its style, performance, photo and video quality. I love its shape. I love its zoom. This cam will give u the exact what u expected as camera should be in such price. It is very easy to handle and very easy in its function. Fully automatic for home users.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">very cute and nice to handle. resolution is excellent. i am very much satisfied with the packing and delivery of the camera. very cheap compared to other brands and more features. great......................./</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">I got the delivery within 24hrs... That's just amazing....!!!!  The camera is good....images are very clear and very nice optical zoom... also two pairs of battery and a free battery charger makes the deal just unavoidable. just grab it...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Guys if you want to have a camera for family / party / small functions & your personal use this is the best buy. Go for it guys. And about the features, all I can say is it the most user friendly camera I have seen. All in all a fantastic camera with all the accessories included :-))</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Hi Guys, this is one of the best cameras you get at 13K. Pros: -Its Camera quality n zoom. -The packaged Li-MH batteries can take 300+ shots per pair. And you are provided with 2 pairs...so its freaking awesum. -Connectivity options are good. USB, AV, HDMI - Preset modes really work well like Panaroma, fireworks, sports, etc Cons: - It very rarely hangs (happened only once)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">The camera features a variety of specs as given which is truly satisfy a beginner. The main bad thing of this camera is only the alkaline batteries which lacks performance as expected. But thats not a big deal. I must recommend it to the beginners.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">good camera for outdoors,  not for ones who need low light shooting without flash good batteries that come with camera i buy on 28 dec 2012 hd videos are awesum batteries on full charge give upto 200-300 shots per pair</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Good one..... only concern is battery.....Other than that rest all features are good.... I like it.....again its my point of view...Please go ahead and do research before you buy any product....Reviews does help but not always... nowadays we are so used to reviews that even we go for movies after reading reviews which is not good at all... search for different products and choose the best....</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1600 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">16 Megapixel (High) (4608 x 3456) (Fine), 16 Megapixel (4608 x 3456), 8 Megapixel (3264 x 2448), 4 Megapixel (2272 x 1704), 2 Megapixel (1600 x 1200), VGA (640 x 480), 16:9 Aspect Ratio (4608 x 2592)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5 - 63.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 25 - 350 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">14x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">2x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">240 g (Including Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">108.0 (W) x 68.4 (H) x 34.1 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:9, 4:3</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, LR6 / L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries x 2, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, View NX 2 CD, Reference Manual CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L610</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 6.0 m (W), 1.5 - 3.2 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.3 - F6.6 (W)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">25 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256 Segment Matrix, Center Weighted (Digital Zoom Less than 2x), Spot (Digital Zoom 2x)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.9 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600, ISO 3200 (Available in Auto Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Back Lighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm (W)</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">USB Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">30</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">16.0 Million Effective Pixels Superior Low-light Performance, Lens Construction: 11 Elements in 10 Groups (2 ED Lens Element), Digital Zoom Magnification Upto 2x (Angle of View Equivalent Approx: 700 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Motion Blur Reduction (Motion Detection), Focus Range (Approx: 50 cm...View More

16.0 Million Effective Pixels Superior Low-light Performance, Lens Construction: 11 Elements in 10 Groups (2 ED Lens Element), Digital Zoom Magnification Upto 2x (Angle of View Equivalent Approx: 700 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Motion Blur Reduction (Motion Detection), Focus Range (Approx: 50 cm (W) to Infinity, Approx: 1.0 m (T) to Infinity, Macro Mode: Approx 10 cm to Infinity, Focus-area Selection (Center, Face Detection, Target Finding AF), Monitor (5 Level Brightness Adjustment), Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): Approx: 96% Horizontal and 96% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): Approx: 96% Horizontal and 96% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Continuous Shooting: Single (Default Setting), Continuous (About 4 Images 1.9 fps (4608 x 3456), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16, Movie (HD 1080p (Fine) Default Setting: 1920 x 1080, 30 fps, HD 1080p: 1920 x 1080, 30 fps, HD 720p: 1280 x 720, 30 fps, VGA: 640 x 480, 30 fps, HS 240 fps: 320 x 240, HS 120 fps: 640 x 48, HS 60 fps: 1280 x 720, HS 15 fps: 1920 x 1080, Wind Noise Reduction, Exposure Control (-2.0 - .0 EV in increment of 1/3 EV), Shutter Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, Speed (4 sec Fireworks Show Scene Mode), Electronically-controlled ND Filter (-2 AV) Selection Aperture, Flash Control (TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes), Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP), HDMI Output (Auto, 480p, 720p, and 1080i), Input / Output Terminal (Digital Input / Output (USB), HDMI Mini Connector (Type C) (HDMI Output)), Battery Life Still Pictures 120 Shots when Using Alkaline Batteries, 470 Shots when Using Lithium Batteries, 330 Shots when Using EN-MH2 Batteries, Tripod Socket (1/4 (ISO 1222)), Temperature 0° C - 40° C, Humidity 85% or Less (Condensation), Smart Portrait System, 19 Optimized Scene Modes, Eye-Fi Card Support, Supported Batteries (Alkaline, Lithium-ion, Ni-MH)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Back Lighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, MPEG-4 AVC, H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-65A</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Operating System">Windows 7 SP1, Windows Vista SP2, Windows XP SP3, MAC OS X 10.6, MAC OS X 10.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">28 MB</specsKey>
