<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-p510-point-shoot-camera/p/itmd72tnhav9ytmf?pid=CAMD7S88MVPEYVYS&otracker=from-search&srno=t_189&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3R0JWE1oikFkwcVk6GbeGcyZeW9UHw%2BFIwwuee1eVqBYaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=5c320a3f-774a-47ac-acd4-f227d67597ff</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">175</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">45</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/y/s/nikon-p510-400x400-imad8yymcgnfmfhd.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">22274</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix P510 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">It's been a week that i got this camera.I wanted a camera which is light weight,have good zoom,decent low light performance.There were only three of them i had to consider, Nikon P500,P510 and Sony HX100V. IMHO Nikkor lens is better than Sony, hence it was either P500 or P510. There are actually only three key differences between P500 and P510. First one is 36x vs 42x optical zoom, Second is better ISO ratings, and third is built-in GPS. I wanted better optical zoom hence i went for P510 and it was totally worth it. It has fantastic zoom. built in GPS means, when you upload photo to various online services it will automatically display the location on map, low light photos are also good. P510 can also shoot higher MP photos but once you cross 10MP there is not much difference in quality unless you want to print it on billboard. I feel it was good decision to go for P510 against P500.Best 3 thousand i spend on gadget :)  Note: in the low light condition and at 40-42x zoom it becomes difficult to click clear photos.If that is what you are looking for, buy a tripod as well.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I bought P510 a month ago(not from FLIP) and am having a very good experience with this one. -42x is a greater closeness to your subject and combined with another of 2x DIGITAL ZOOM, its a BOOM. I clicked few photograps of FULL MOON and I LIVE THEM. -but yeah, this much magnification also magnify the noise and shaking, need to have steady hands or a tripod. -The Electronic VIEWFINDER is not much impressive, you can't use screen and VF simultaneously, need to switch every time. -Manual Shooting gives you full controls over the shots and Automatic Mode acts like an experienced photographer, dual advantage. -They say P510 comes with high ISO rating, great shutter speed, Well I say, thats just OHKEYY NOTE, nothing special about this. -The AUTO FOCUS MODE on video recording is not much impressive, also, while recording, the OPTICAL ZOOM makes NOISE and that is also recorded in the STEREO AUDIO FORMAT. Then what...? I didn't buy this one to shoot videos. HUH. -In SCENES MODE, NIKON has given many shooting modes. Choose your most suitable and ROCK. -Battery life is not bad, and not too good, even. NIKON claims that P510 shoots 250+ on single charge, well, I shoot more than 300(I kept the display off and used the EVF, used sunlight and flash off) but it takes 5 HOURS to fully recharge the battery and bad thing is, when it is on charge, you can't do anything with the camera. . OKEY, ENOUGH, if you want to buy a BRIDGE, this is one of the best Options. Make few more clicks, make your CARD ready, pay and buy this one, I hope you will write a REVIEW of SATISFACTION after few weeks. ROCK.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">The camera is excellent. zoom is great and you can take pictures of very far objects.The picture clarity and quality is great.Its a cheap and better option against a DSLR camera.I started testing it and I am satisfied with its performance.Camera has very good low light performance and video recording is also of good quality.   Service of Flipkart was also good. Got camera with in 4 days after order.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">You May Get Panorama and Other Features in Sony HX100v But the Resolution Matters ..... I Mean DPI.. Sony HX100v Shoots Only at 72 DPI.. Which is of no use Compare to Nikon's More Than 300 DPI, In HX100v when you zoom for a distant image for 30X in Low Day Light.. You May feel doubtful is this a good Camera, Because Even i own the HX100v & Extremely Not Satisfied. But Browsed at the sample Images of Nikon's P510 it shoots at 324 DPI and it's very detailed Image. Thinking to sell this HX100v & Go for it.. If You're Looking For a Panorama Option Go For Sony, If You're Really Interested in True High Res Image Go For Nikon P510</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Its just 2 days since i got this camera and it is too early to jump upon the verdict. So far so good. Though flipkart said my order could be further delayed due to some 'uncontrollable delay' from the sellers side , i got the package in time. As far as camera is considered , it is a VFM . Having said that i notice some startling fact. When i ordered the cam it costs Rs.18180 (on july 3rd 2013) including the freebies (WS Retail) . But the very next day flipkart (or WS ) increased the price to 21300 ( on 4th July 2013) . That was stunning . I don't know why.   Anyhow . You might have heard a lot of positive things about the cam from other reviews . So let me tell what are the grey areas which i found .   --the so called 42 X is useless unless you have a tripod or steady hands. Ofcourse VR is there , but practically not helpful in such high zoom range. But image quality is good even in such ranges. -- View Finder ( Digital) is useless  -- GPS !!! ???   What i like the most  -- full manual adjustments possible . Play around with iso and aperture values. -- manual focus  --- very good macros ( 1 cm) --- massive zoom  --- full HD video recording --- flipout screen --- 3 D photos for your 3D smart TV --- inbuilt HDR   Thats all from me for now . As i said , its only 48 hrs since i got this in hand, so my review doenot reflect all the features and disadvantages of this camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Nikon p510 is just amazing .It is best for amature photographers. Also it is quite easy to use.It is the best deal for whoom who wants quality photos with the fun of photography. i was in dilemma whether to buy Canon 1000d ,1100d or Nikon p510/p500.At last I took the advice of a professional photographer. He suggested p510 for me .I am satisfy with it.  JUST GO FOR IT</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I had bought this camera 6 months ago.....so I think am in a better position to give a review which can help you all who are lil bit confused....  Zoom: It is the best part of this camera.....After I had got it for few days i have just use it for it's zooming....its just in bengali term....."jaa taa"...means unbelievable.... I alwys feel proud to show this quality of zooming to any1....100 upon 100 people just blown away.....Yup...it is...  Picture quality is very similar to SLR quality....not actual but apx to SLR...  Who says its take only 200 snap with its fully charged battery??? i relly don know....But what i can share with you, that today, means 22nd march, 2013 I had taken 287 photographed and its not even lossed a single mark of charge...and every time I have chechd my pics after taken and all photographs have been taken in LCD Display MODE....!!!  GPS is working !!! yes still working....  Now at the conclusion : Most of the people alrdy have said me that they are going to buy this cam after seeing it's performnce.... dont hesitate buddy....Go for it.....I also alwys thought to buy a DSLR cam...but it would not be a good deal..... Just think if you r not a professional photographer yet...U dnt hv to carry extra lenses....What much zoom it ofers that much zooming with SLR lences cost near 80000.00 INR...i m not joking....U dont have to focus manualy...I suggest every1 to buy thiscamera, specially begginner....stat with this cam...learn photography well...then expend mloney on DSLR. I can asssure you it will not dissapoint you....You will give me a spcl thank U.....:)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Went for the P510 mainly for it's 42X zoom and of course the Nikon brand. And the camera does not disappoint either. A little grainy in low light. Max zoom stability is extremely good. Even with the digital zoom, the picture quality is good for an A4 print. Full HD video lives up to it's name with excellent quality and very good stereo sound capture. Video at 120 fps is worth paying for. The lens movement during zooming is a little noisy.  All in all, the P510 is an amazing camera for all the things 85% of the people actually need during photography.  Worth the buy ! ! !</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">A masterpiece from the camera giant! I have bought it yesterday. Experience with my P510 has been impressive so far! It's 16.1 mega pixel CMOS sensor has made the gadget widely appreciable! And the 42X optical zoom is just insane! Night shots are pretty impressive..  Very good bridge camera!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">With this BEAST you only need....time for enjoy this camera, you have EVERYTHING in a compact camera. I recommend this camera, it doesn´t matter if you are a Pro or just enthusiast.period. I have compared like cameras for the last two months trying to determine which product to purchase. Having used cameras of friends, I finally decided on the Nikon P-510. The picture quality and performance is unbelievable. I do not regret my purchase and would do this all over again as I believe I have purchased the finest camera in it's class!</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.3 - 180 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 24 - 1000 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">42x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">2x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">555 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">119.8 (W) x 82.9 (H) x 102.2 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Wide Viewing Angle TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:9, 3:2, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Lens Cap LC-CP24 (with cord), HDMI Cable, USB Cable UC-E6, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Camera Strap, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL5 (with Terminal Cover), Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, Reference Manual CD, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">P510</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, On, Off, Red-eye, Slow-sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 8.0 m (W), 1.5 - 4.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Continuous H (Pictures are continuously shot at about 7 fps), Continuous L (Up to about 30 frames at about 1 fps)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200, Hi 1 (Equivalent to 6400) Auto (Auto Gain ISO 100 to 1600) Fixed Range Auto (ISO 100 to 400, 100 to 800) Hi 2 (Equivalent to 12800) (High ISO Monochrome in Special Effects Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Close-up, Portrait, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party, Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk and Dawn, Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting), Special Effects, Program, Shutter Pr...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Close-up, Portrait, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party, Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk and Dawn, Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting), Special Effects, Program, Shutter Priority, Aperture Priority, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">24 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">HDMI Mini Connector (Type C)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">29</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Close-up, Portrait, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party, Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk and Dawn, Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting), Special Effects, Program, Shutter Pr...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Close-up, Portrait, Food, Sports, Museum, Night Portrait, Fireworks Show, Party, Indoor, Black and White Copy, Beach, Panorama, Snow, Pet Portrait, Sunset, 3D Photography, Dusk and Dawn, Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting), Special Effects, Program, Shutter Priority, Aperture Priority, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG (3D), EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MPEG-4, AVC, H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">90 MB</specsKey>
