<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-p500-point-shoot-camera/p/itmcwapd63tms4hj?pid=CAMCWAPD63TMS4HJ&otracker=from-search&srno=t_249&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff1rPxiBfHXseIR21klIqQu1Dam2HzTI%2BxvQSxUX9kMohYaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=77476514-6655-436f-9c8a-f4423dfc7d42</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">120</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/4/h/j/nikon-coolpix-p500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhqfvnaugarz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">19484</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix P500 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">With a zoom that's both remarkably wide and extremely long, the Nikon P500 exceeds all expectations in a long zoom digital camera with only a few optical compromises. This is the camera you grab when you don't want to heft the SLR and a bag full of lenses. The Nikon P500 takes only 1.5 seconds to power on and take a shot. That's very fast for an ultra-zoom camera. Full autofocus shutter lag is very fast, at 0.158 second at wide angle and 0.119 second at full telephoto; faster than most DSLRs. Prefocused shutter lag is 0.012 second, which is excellent. The camera's AF system was able to focus down to just above the 1/4 foot-candle light level without AF assist, though the camera was able to focus in complete darkness with the AF assist lamp enabled. Connected to a computer or printer with USB 2.0, the Nikon Coolpix P500's download speeds are moderately fast. We measured 4,942 KBytes/sec. SO ENJOY KEEPING THIS WONDERFULL GADGET</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Loved this camera. As usual, flipkart service was great and packaging was very good. Received the product exactly on the date expected (on my birthday). So here is my experience with this camera.  This camera is great if u can use it properly. U need to knows the settings and the environment so as to adjust your camera to get the best picture quality. It even takes awesome pics in low light conditions. I read a lot of reviews and found a number of bad reviews regarding this product. But still I bought it as it was the best in my budget.  Now I am glad I didnt believe those reviews. Time for Pros and cons.  Pros :  1) Great camera, great build, stable. 2) Fast startup, max 2 seconds. Very less time lag between flash charge. 3) Low light pictures are great with proper camera settings. 4) Normal light pictures are quite great. Well u cant expect SLR type picture quality. But still its very crisp and clear. 5) Battery life is good too. Was able to take around 250 pics one day, although I was saving battery by using the viewfinder most of the time and flash only when required. 6) Video recording is ultimate. The quality is too good. Only problem is shaking, but i think that can be solved using a tripod. 7) U'll surely love the super zoom. Just reduce the shaking and u can take extremely nice close ups.  Cons: 1) Still photography in low light is great, but if the subject is moving or in case of disco lights, taking gud pictures becomes a little difficult. 2) In low light, u need to wait a couple of seconds before u can shoot another picture. I don't know why it waits, but it doesn't starts focusing immediately after a pic is taking. 3) High Speed video recording is a mystery to me still. I dont know why I am not able to take good videos in it. When I try to take videos, the videos are very dark. But in the same conditions, the HD video is great. 4) charging of fully exhausted battery takes around 5 hours or more.  It has been only 15 days since I purchased it, and I haven't faced any technical problems yet. I hope I don't face any.  In a nut shell, if u are good with camera settings u can take ultimate pictures with this camera. This is the best point and shoot camera providing SLR features ...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">The decision to buy Nikon P500 was taken after a long research. Wanted to buy a SLR but the simplicity of this camera caught my eye. Its so easy to use and the results are really good.  This was my first major order through Flipkart. Earlier orders were books and DVDs only. So i was a little apprehensive to be honest.  The camera was deliverd to me in three days in pristine condition with everything as listed on the site. Got a 2 GB Go Gear USB player with it for free.  Kudos to Flipkart Team .</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">PROS  Ultra Zoom is great. Full HD Recording. Slow Motion Recording. Ease of use. Excellent burst mode shooting. Macro mode is highly impressive. Variety of shooting modes and scenes. Good for its price.  CONS  Gets grainy in Telephoto zoom. Battery runs out of juice quickly. Camera freezes if turned on with lens hood. Can't click pictures in video mode (compared to other camera). Noisy when zooming during video capture. Picture quality mediocre in low light.  In my opinion, this camera is worth money but you will have to spend a little extra on another battery. Picture quality is quite impressive. Buy it if you do not want to carry a Handycam and a camera together. It is a great tool combines in one.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Simply superb. i bought this camera after months of deliberation and almost  went in for a nikon DSLR,but this stopped me in my tracks.. great wide  angle and even better telephoto (albeit with a bit of chromatic aberration  at 1:1).with this cam i was assured of any pic i ever wanted. video is  great @1080p and the stereo sound recording is exquisite. a bit distortion  when taking closeup pics.(to be expected from this sort of lens).but that counts for nothing.. great macro and in  camera editing options.. but keep at least a 32GB card and a spare battery  handy for trips or events..runs out of juice a bit faster than your typical  cybershot..MUST BUY FOR A SERIOUS NON PRO Photographer</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Well, must I say , it took about 20 days of intensive research, comparison, guidance from some of the good known photographers in the city as well as reviews from youtube and other internet sites including Flipkart, for finalizing this amazing camera called NIKON P 500 !!  what a camera..!, what a performance !!...what a zooooom !!! I am really impressed with its features which even beats , sometimes the close SLRs/DSLRs also ...( i know few of you may have your eyebrow raised on this comment , but trust me... I have taken few snaps with N P 500 as well as a DSLR and found both to be at par)  The red color adds spice. smooth functioning is a plus plus.  Very small two issues ( being an honest reviewer, I must add here) : (1) the display is adjustable... which is ok for photography but it should have that swing/rotation effect in CANON SX40s.. (2) deleting the unwanted snaps is a tedious affair, especially the selection is a bit time consuming and confusing.  But rest, This is a 9.5/10 camera !  Go for it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I was looking for a SLR when this Cam caught my eye. The features offered are pretty high and to-operate its pretty simple. Not to mention the weight...its damn light compared with SONY HX100V(the only match in its category). P500 stands out due to its wide viewing angle (handy in sight-seeing locations).  Thanks to Flipkart for their great service and the prompt delivery! Wish they bring-in more product categories:-P</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I have used this camera....its having superb functionality and features.Its 36x zooming performance is too good, I have just taken this camera from one of my friend for few days.  I just love this camera, Now I also planning to buy one butI cant spent tht much amount at once and i also dont have credit card, i only hve debit card and i wanna pay whole amount in 6 installment or Post dated cheque.  But as per Flipcart.com its not possible, so this is my problem but This camera is Superb once again.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">The Nikon Coolpix p500 is really a nice camera.the main advantage of this camera is the 36x optical zoom which enables us to reach clearly then our eye.i think the price of the camera is much less in comparison to the features of the camera. It has dual image processor,CMOS technology,Red eye reduction etc.i found the camera to satisfactory up to the full extent.it is suitable for those who wants much clear image and full hd videos and who doesnot want to carry a huge DSLR with the extra lenses. I have been discovering a new function daily in the camera.it has lots of features.so those who are planning or in doubt to buy it should buy it with out any tension.in my openion the camera doesnot have any disadvantages.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Camera with cool feature, using it for last 6 months no issues. Only problem is with high zoom when you need a more stable hand though the image stabilizer is available but still it takes time to get a clear image.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">8 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2592 x 1944 (5 M), 2048 x 1536 (3 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 1280 x 960 (1 M), 1024 x 768 (PC), 640 x 480 (VGA), 3284 x 2656 (3:2), 3968 x 2232 (16:9, 9 M), 1920 x 1080 (16:9, 2 M), 2992 x 2992 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR ED Glass Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast-detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4 - 144 mm (35 mm (135 mm) Equivalent to 22.5 - 810 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">36x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">494 g (with Battery and Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">115.5 (W) x 83.7 (H) x 102.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">3:2, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP21, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL5, Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, View NX 2 CD, Lens Cap LC-CP23, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">Coolpix P500</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes, Pop-up</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Flash Off, Fill Flash, Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 8 m (W), 2.2 - 4.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F/3.4 F/5.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">22.5 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256 Segment Matrix Metering, Center Weighted Metering, Spot Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 8 fps (upto 5 Shots, Continuous H), 1.8 fps (upto 24 Shots, Continuous L), Continuous H: 120 fps (1280 x 960, upto 50 Shots), Continuous H: 60 fps (1600 x 1200, upto 25 Shots)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto Gain ISO 160 - 800), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 160 to 200, 160 to 400), High ISO Sensitivity Auto (ISO 160 to 1600), Manual Selection: ISO 160, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Movie Mode, Program, Shutter Priorty, Apertyre Priorty, Manual, Exposure Modes, Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Backlit Scene HDR, Smart Portrait, User Setting Preset</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Preset Manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm (W) - 10 cm (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">HDMI Min Connector</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Scene Modes (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Party/Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk/Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait), Supported Languages (Arabic, Chinese (Simplified and Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnis...View More

Scene Modes (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Party/Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk/Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait), Supported Languages (Arabic, Chinese (Simplified and Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Norwegian, Polish, Portuguese, Romanian, Russian, Spanish, Swedish, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian), Lens Construction: 14 Elelments in 9 Groups, Autofocus (AF) Focus-area Selection (Auto (9-area Automatic Selection): Center, Face Priority, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Focus Lock, LCD Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 97% Horizontal and 97% Vertical, LCD Frame Coverage (Plyaback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical, Voice Memo Function, Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure with Motion Detection, Aperture Priority Auto, Exposure Bracketing, Manual, Motion Detection, Shutter Priority Auto), Exposure Compensation: -/ 2 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Exposure Modes (Aperture Priority Auto (A), Manual (M), Programmed Auto (P), Shutter Priority (S)), Automatic Exposure Scene Modes, Built-in Flash Control (TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes), Interface Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP), Charging Time (4 hrs and 50 mins (When Using Charging AC Adapter EH-69P), 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Image Editing (Black Border, Crop, D-Lighting, Filter Effects, Frame, Quick Retouch, Skin Softening, Small Pic)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4000 x 3000 (12 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Movie Mode, Program, Shutter Priorty, Apertyre Priorty, Manual, Exposure Modes, Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Backlit Scene HDR, Smart Portrait, User Setting Preset</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Mono, WAV File</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV movie</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">102 MB</specsKey>
