<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d3200-dslr-camera/p/itmdv58hcduc33pg?pid=CAMDA6RJFYWRZEZY&otracker=from-search&srno=t_32&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff01qyIsK7bZWBbvWOhJ6Kct1mduP2Q7UZaSrYo7cfIcKIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=70bfa3c3-0ea3-487e-ab2e-3a6bc8e08d03</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">72</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">28</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/z/y/nikon-d3200-kit-with-18-105-mm-vr-lens-slr-400x400-imada6rqeg8czm7e.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">39700</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D3200 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I am a beginner and I wanted a DSLR for a long time. My wish was granted recently when I bought this great camera from Flipkart. I did a lot of research before I decided to go for the D3200. Initially, I wanted to go for the Canon 600D, bit when I compared it with Nikon D3200, I found the Nikon worthy and decided to give it a shot.   The camera is of top notch built quality and is a pleasure to use. It holds firmly and is also easier to use than I thought it was. The user guide mode is of great use especially to beginners, even though I mostly use the manual mode. The lens are awesome. The free carry bag I got with this camera was unexpectedly of great quality. It is compact and has a leather finish. Great stuff! I am now an extremely satisfied customer!   Service from Flipkart is simply great. I have been a customer with them ever since they started of. They never disappoint you in terms of service, packing, or delivery. Great going guys!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Nikon D3200 is pretty nice camera with lots of features, great image quality, lower noise levels even in high iso settings.. Two main rivals of the camera in this price range is Canon 600D & Nikon D5100...I am going to discuss them comparatively.....  1.Megapixels..(megapixels helps you to get high resolution, so that you can crop your primary image and you will still get high quality images)---- 600D- 18MP D5100- 16MP D3200- 24.1MP (so D3200 gives you high quality images, and gets about 30% more detail in images)  2. Autofocus Motor..(body AF motor lets you to auto focus with more lenses)--- 600D- Body AF motor D5100- Lens Af motor D3200- Lens Af motor  3. HDR mode.. (it lets you get high image dynamic range even in backlight situations)--- D5100 has HDR mode, which is nice, but you can also do that with D3200 or 600D, later in any editing software..  4. AF points..(helps to focus perfectly)--- 600D- 9 AF points. D5100- 11 AF points. D3200- 11 AF points.  5. Night shooting-- D3200 is simply better than others in this case, it has very low noise levels even in higher iso settings, trust me, this is amazing.  6. Colour depth and Image quality-- D3200 has much better colour depth, higher image quality, wide dynamic range than others in this case.  7. Sensor size-- D3200 and D5100 both have about 10% larger sensor than 600D  8. Battery life-- D5100-- 660 shots D3200-- 540 shots 600D-- 440 shots  9. Flip out screen..(good for video shooting)-- D5100--Yes 600D-- Yes D3200--No  10. Video quality-- all the cameras have Full HD 1080p video shooting mode, but D3200 has continous autofocus system in video mode, it is a very nice feature...on the other hand 600D has much more manual control on video shooting..  Finally I can recommend you to buy D3200 if you are really interested in still photography and also videography. I am sure this product will satisfy all your needs, but if you want much more control on video shooting you may consider buying 600D. (but keep it on mind that D3200 is much better in image quality, color depth, night photography, dynamic range, image resolution than 600D). I am currently using Nikon D3200, and trust me, you won't regret this buy....  Another thing is that if you are ready to pay about 10k more then you may buy Nikon D5200, which is a really beautiful camera. D5200 has all the good features of these 3 cameras..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">If you are more inclined towards telephoto zoom requirements like wild life photography then go for 18-55 and additional lens of 55-200 or 70-300. consider that 18-55 has too short zoom capabilities resulting in frequent requirement of interchanging of lenses even for routine photography including indoor as well. changing lens is certainly very inconvenient and also compels us to carry additional lens with bag wherever we go.  but if you are more inclined towards in house photography, portraits and other routine photography with limited zoom requirement....then go for 18-105 lens kit. this has decent zoom capacity which is good enough for mentioned uses. it is costlier then 2 lens option if compared in terms of total zoom range availability but believe me its very convenient when you need not to carry any other lens with you for frequent interchanging for most of the time.  From me 4 star for this kit instead of 5 as delivered 1 day late then committed. overall experience with flipkart is great. packing was really appreciable.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I have been researching on an entry level DSLR and had almost zeroed in on the Canon 550D (was getting a good deal on Flipkart with 135mm zoom) when Nikon announced the D3200. It's a great camera and with 105mm is closer to higher end DSLR's than an entry level. Controls are well located, easy to use and user friendly. Scope of experimenting is immense on Manual (why else should one get a DSLR?) and the Guide Mode is a very nifty option to shoot in fast response situations. And I got the delivery within 72 hours from Flipkart (given that 15th August was a holiday) I would have got it within 2 days. A great camera and an equally great experience with Flipkart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Im a wannabe professional photographer, but its a long road getting to the top, so guess I will stay an amateur forever and shoot photographs for my private album mostly. This is my first DSLR after my Vivitar V3800N 35mm SLR that I owned about 6 years ago, so my review here might sound like a bunch of antiquated thoughts from a genie out of a bottle after 6 years. Though Autofocus and the other things amaze me, I still find shooting in manual mode better than letting the electronics in the camera decide the settings for me. Maybe its because I have used only manual film slrs before, I don't know.   I filled up my 16 GB memory card and the battery was only 50% empty. That looks good, I don't have to carry a spare battery when I go on long drives. The proximity sensor on the LCD comes back on when I press the shutter half way to autofocus and release it before pressing full, and thats a little annoying when the light is low.   I used to be able to view the full frame on the view finder on my Vivitar with my glasses on, but on this, the corners are being cut unless I bring my eye really close to the viewfinder. The mirror adjustment tampers with focus and since I shoot in manual, that isn't helping much.   The VR feature works only while you're photographing wild life from a moving jeep or something. Turning VR on doesn't help minor shakes at low shutter speeds. Get a tripod.  The Nikon 3200 is cheaper than the D90, has more resolution, but you can't mount all those flashy high aperture long zoon lenses on it. Well, Im not going to be shooting out drag races anytime soon.   With the 18-105 lens that comes with this camera, and the additional Sigma 70-300 mm macro lens that I have ordered, which I expect to be delivered today, and a circular polarizer, the tripod and the remote that I already have, I guess I have the complete amateur kit, all set to register memories of my trips to enjoy later in life.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">I am happy with the performance of the DSLR and thank Nikon for it. I am a beginner and I am using the Nikon DSLR for the past 3 months under the guidance of my friend cum colleague who introduced me to digital photography. I have compared my DSLR with the equipment used by other photographers and confirm that Nikon is the best. If you are taking photographs in "Auto" mode, this product is not your cup of tea.   Moreover, I can not be more delighted with the delivery. Flipkart is prompt and prudent as ever.....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">This is my first DSLR and i am happy that i have bought it. after using it for a month the advantages i have found are 1. the guide mode. which is user friendly and good for beginners 2. excellant night photography without flash.  3. 24.2 MP helps us to crop pictures after taking and helps to modify the composition. 4. good battery back up. it lasts even more than 500 shots. 5. well placed rubber cushions for better grip. 6. good video with clear audio recording. the disadvantages, if at all, are 1. weight because of the lens. 2. shadow of the lens falling on subjects during flash. 3. no tripod in the offer! thanks to flipcart for the swift delivery and good customer response cos i missed to note the 4 gb sd card which was pasted on the outer cover.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I just ordered Nikon d3200 after I read all the reviews and done some kind of market analysis, I am egarly waiting to take first photo to really test its perfomrance. I will write once I receive my dream camera. before that i was comparing all other cameras with D3200, seems for this price its the best camera. I compared Nikon D3200 with Canon550D, 600D, and found only major technical difference with D3200 specifications are seems Canon has inbuilt AF motor, Nikon doesnot have any in built auto focus motor however the Nikon lense have motor in it, except this rest of the technical functionalities found much better than Canon550D/600D with high resolution 24 MP, low light shooting are very good in Nkon</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I did not buy this from Flipkart. I brought the exact model of the camera with 18-105 lens.  the initial hiccups with the camera: - the pictures appear to be darker than what is shown in the display - pictures also appear with more bluish tinge, if White Balance is set to AUTO - getting the settings right might be tricky  plus points: - amazing picture clarity - 18-105 is a great lens which provides a decent amount of zoom  if i might interest you, consider buying D90.... although that camera is an old model but still a good one</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">The D3200 is equipped with a new Nikon DX-format CMOS image sensor, developed by Nikon with an effective pixel count of 24.2-million pixels, and the EXPEED 3 image-processing engine. Its predecessor, the D3100, offered a pixel count of 14.2-million pixels and standard ISO sensitivities of ISO 100–3200. The D3200 surpasses the D3100 with regard to both with its significant increase in pixel count and support for standard sensitivities of ISO 100–6400 and a Hi 1 setting equivalent to ISO 12800.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Monaural</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">EN-EL14 Rechargeable Li-ion Battery (with terminal cover), MH-24 Battery Charger, AN-DC3 Strap, EG-CP14 Audio/Video Cable, UC-E17 USB Cable, DK-5 Eyepiece Cap, BS-1 Accessory Shoe Cover, DK-20 Rubber Eyecup, BF-1B Body Cap, ViewNX 2 CD-ROM, Reference CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">4512 x 3000 (M), 3008 x 2000 (S)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">18 - 105 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 4 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO in steps of 1 EV (100 - 6400), 1 EV above ISO (12800 Equivalent)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Image Sensor Cleaning</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent (7 Types), Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix Metering, Center Weighted Metering, Spot Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Nikon F Lens Mount (with AF Contact), 1.5x Lens Focal Length (35 mm Format Equivalent, Nikon DX Format), 24.7 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Land...View More

Nikon F Lens Mount (with AF Contact), 1.5x Lens Focal Length (35 mm Format Equivalent, Nikon DX Format), 24.7 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Viewfinder Frame Cavarage: 95% Horizontal and 95% Vertical, Viewfinder Magnification: 0.8 x (50 mm f/1.4 Lens at infinity, -1.0 m-1), 18 mm Eyepoint, -1.7 - 0.5 m-1 Diopter Adjustment, Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark VII Focusing Screen, Quick Return Reflex Mirror, Lens Aperture: Instant Return, Electronically Controlled, Compatible Lenses: Autofocus is Available with AF-S and AF-I Lenses, Autofocus is not Available with Other Type G and D Lenses, AF Lenses (IX NIKKOR and Lenses for the F3AF are not Supported), and AI-P Lenses, Non-CPU Lenses can be Used in Mode M, but the Camera Exposure Meter will not Function. The Electronic Rangefinder can be Wsed with Lenses that have a Maximum Aperture of f/5.6 or Faster, X=1/200 sec Flash Sync Speed, Release Mode: Single Frame, Continuous, Self-timer, Delayed Remote, Quick-response Remote, Quiet Shutter Release, Metering: TTL Exposure Metering using 420-pixel RGB Sensor, Range (ISO 100, f/1.4 Lens, 20C/68F): Matrix or Center-weighted Metering: 0 - 20 EV Spot Metering: 2 - 20 EV, CPU Exposure Meter Coupling, Exposure Mode: Auto Modes (Auto, Auto (Flash Off), Scene Modes (Portrait, Landscape, Child, Sports, Close Up, Night Portrait), Programmed Auto with Flexible Program (P), Shutter-priority Auto (S), Aperture-priority Auto (A), Manual (M), Exposure Compensation: 5 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Exposure Lock: Luminosity Locked at Detected Value with AE-L/AF-L Button, On and Off Active D-Lighting, Focus Detection Range: -1 - EV (ISO 100, 20C/68F), Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S/AF-C Selection (AF-A); Predictive Focus Tracking Activated Automatically According to Subject Status, Anual Focus (MF): Electronic Rangefinder, 11 Focus Point, AF-area Mode: Single-point AF, Dynamic-area AF, Auto-area AF, 3D-tracking (11 Points), Focus Lock, Built-in Flash: Auto, portrait, child, close up, night portrait: Auto Flash with Auto Pop-up, Program, Shutter-priority, Aperture-priority, Manual, Manual Pop-up with Button Release, Guide Number: 12/39, 13/43 with manual flash (m/ft, ISO 100, 20C/68F), Flash Compensation: -3 - EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Flash-ready Indicator, Accessory Shoe: ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync and Data Contacts and Safety Lock, Nikon Creative Lighting System (CLS), AS-15 Sync Terminal Adapter (Sold Separately), Playback: Full-frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar) Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo and Movie Slide Shows, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, Image Comment (up to 36 Characters)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">6016 x 4000 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, NEF (RAW), NEF (RAW) JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF 2.0, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, MPEG-4 / H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">455 g (Camera Body Only, 505 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Cap)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">125 (W) x 96 (H) x 76.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Carry in</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC / Compatible with UHS-I</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30p</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
