<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l30-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdtjgqtc3xrxqf?pid=CAMDTJGZSFRGF9WE&otracker=from-search&srno=t_15&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0z0b4A0RRbr98Wgd1u%2BFiGkjetz9xqRvKF9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">3.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">144</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">36</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/9/w/e/nikon-coolpix-l30-point-shoot-400x400-imaeyxfapfuj7znf.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">4685</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L30 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Please do not buy this product as it taken around 2 minutes to take the next photo.It is not up to the mark of a 20 MP camera.Never expected this from Nikon.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Not workind properly. Iwas not satisfied with this product. Getting poor quality phots and videos. Not getting 20 MP clarity ang quality. Advice:Dont purchase.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Unable to use, memory too low. Clarity too low. Only 7 photos can be saved. We did not receive the 4GB card and battery charger as mentioned on the box.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Never go for this cam.  Literally you got to wait at-least 30-40 secs for every consecutive shot.  Its taking more time to process and store pics into the memory. That will make you crazy. Finally this is the worst product I ever got from flipkart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Delivery took 3 days and I was fine with that. The Camera came with all essentials - batteries, charger, a pouch, memory card and Timex watch.  But photo capture time is very slow, after taking pics to normal it take about 7-8secs to process. so have to wait 7-8 secs to take another pic. Photo clarity is good. videos is 720p which is good and qulity is 'Fine' .</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">I got this camera1 day before the date given, execellent service flipkart,, nikon l30 is the best cam for the begginers...  it take about 10secs after taking pics to normal,, so have to wait 10 secs to take another pic.. photo clarity is good,, it is 1 of the best small easy handable cam for all at best price..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">At this budget this is close to the best you can get. It takes good photos. Video is good.. Shutter could have been a little better. Quality suffers in low light but that is understandable.. But the problem I had is with delivery and a dreadful customer service.. THESE GUYS JUST ANSWER THE PHONE AND DO NOTHING.. I think only BSNL is worse than them.. So my review is only for the product rest is ridiculous.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Average performance at this price. Picture quality is good, Zoom is okay. I am not too impressed with the shutter speed though. it works fine in a well lit atmosphere however in low light it didnt impress me</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Superb camera, delivered right on time. Thanks flipkart, you guys are awesome...!! :) Thanks for the same day delivery.!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">cells is not rechargeable ..., in case over the batteries we insert new cells thats the main problem</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L30</specsKey>
<specsKey="Processor">Expeed C2 Image-processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Strap, Two LR6/L40 (AA-size) alkaline batteries, UC-E16 USB Cable</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600 (Auto)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">10 cm - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">One Touch HD 720p Movie Recording, Battery Life of Still Shooting: 320 Shots with Alkaline, 950 Shots with Lithium / 570 Shots with EN-MH2 Batteries, Easy Auto Mode, Glamour Retouch, 5x Zoom with 26 mm Capability, Smart Portrait System, Easy-to-hold Handgrip Design, Motion Blur Reduction: Motion Det...View More

One Touch HD 720p Movie Recording, Battery Life of Still Shooting: 320 Shots with Alkaline, 950 Shots with Lithium / 570 Shots with EN-MH2 Batteries, Easy Auto Mode, Glamour Retouch, 5x Zoom with 26 mm Capability, Smart Portrait System, Easy-to-hold Handgrip Design, Motion Blur Reduction: Motion Detection (Still Pictures)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 23.0 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 26 - 130 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Focus Features">Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 520 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus Range">50 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">20.48</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">20.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Megapixels">5152 x 3864 (20 M (High)), 5152 x 3864 (20 M), 3648 x 2736 (10 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Still Image Size 16:9">5120 x 2880</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">164 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">95.4 (W) x 60.3 (H) x 29 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
