<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l24-point-shoot-camera/p/itmcw23rsbh24rhv?pid=CAMCW23RSBH24RHV&otracker=from-search&srno=t_429&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3aEfUEKleppZAf51rp5Jw%2FQPAdwieYl5CpVfQi63%2BVLoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=253ed7b5-5da9-4a5a-a8fa-ce78ba4f83c5</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.1</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">30</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/r/h/v/nikon-l24-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq8yxgdgzgj.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">5069</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L24 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Glass Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Contrast Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">6.7 - 24.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 37 - 134 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">3.6x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">182 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">96.7 (W) x 60.5 (H) x 28.3 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">640 x 480</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap AN-CP19, User Manual, Camera, LR6/L40 (AA-size), Alkaline Batteries, USB Cable UC-E6, View NX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">Coolpix L24</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Flash Off, Fill Flash, Slow Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 7.0 m (W), 0.5 - 3.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F/3.1 F/6.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 0.7 fps (upto 3 Shots)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto (Auto Gain ISO 80 - 1600)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Preset Manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Easy Auto Mode, Smart Portrait Mode, Movie Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm (W)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256 Segment Matrix Metering, Center Weighted Metering, Spot Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Shutter Speed: 4 sec (when Scene Mode is Set to Fireworks Show), Lens Construction: 6 Elements in 5 Groups, Autofocus (AF) Focus-area Selection (Center and Face Detection), Min Focus Range: 30 cm (W) - 70 cm (T), Focus Lock, Monitor Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): (98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical), ...View More

Shutter Speed: 4 sec (when Scene Mode is Set to Fireworks Show), Lens Construction: 6 Elements in 5 Groups, Autofocus (AF) Focus-area Selection (Center and Face Detection), Min Focus Range: 30 cm (W) - 70 cm (T), Focus Lock, Monitor Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): (98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical), Monitor Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal, Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure with Motion Detection), Exposure Compensation ( 2.0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV), Exposure Modes (Programmed Auto), Scene Modes (Back Light, Beach / Snow, Close Up, Copy, Dusk / Dawn, Fireworks Show, Food, Landscape, Museum, Night Portrait, Panorama Assist, Party / Indoor, Portrait, Sports, Sunset), In-Camera Image Editing (Crop, D-lighting, Small Picture), Shutter (Mechanical and Charge-coupled Electronic Shutter), Built-in Flash Control (TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes), Interface Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4320 x 3240 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto Mode, Scene Modes, Easy Auto Mode, Smart Portrait Mode, Movie Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">AVI Movie JPEG Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Operating System">Windows 7</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">17 MB</specsKey>
