<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d7100-dslr-camera/p/itmdv58fsyz8mnmu?pid=CAMDJ4X8RZQEGHDA&otracker=from-search&srno=t_47&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff1IJteNOBI%2Bicjm%2BTJAX365KP3DzYsqZbXT11Rvyw0qHoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=3b543042-881b-4704-8be0-941f818f1611</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">44</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">11</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/h/d/a/nikon-d7100-slr-400x400-imadj4xujehnwuep.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">92100</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D7100 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Purchasing your first camera can be a headache. I was bewildered to see huge collections online and on flipkart. After extensive research I decided I would go with either Canon or Nikon, and zeroed down upon Canon EOS 60D vs. Nikon D7000 vs. Nikon D7100 vs. Canon EOS 7D, yeah I agree all of these models are expensive ones, but I intend to pursue photography beyond a hobby and I don't see myself buying another camera until few years (budget constraints)  Actually, comparing Canon vs.Nikon reputation or which is better?, is not justified at all, both are highly specialized players in this field , Canon has a dominant presence in the market and is respected by professionals while Nikon enjoys mass popularity and has carved it's own niche.  Lens of both corporations are of superior standards and well built.  I finally chose the "Nikon D7100" , earlier it was D7000 but changed my mind when heard about the latest upgrade (D7100 launched in mid feb 2013), I didn't mind spending a few extra bucks.  so why I didn't go for the Canon EOS series ?   Well to start with , the D7100 beats 60D in nearly all aspects (just like D7000), the only things that pulls up 60D is the flipout screen useful for tricky shots.  In fact D7100 competes with the EOS 7D, and gives it a stiff competition overall. If 7D has "some" advantages over D7100 (like 8fps vs. 6fps) then D7100 has a "lot" advantage over the 7D with better image quality, two memory card slots and lots more (compare the features online) and this excludes the High Pixel debate, honestly 24 MP, will be useful only when higher grade lens are used. Canons 18 MP is at par (but yes it does give a slight advantage to Nikon).  So choosing D7100 was an obvious choice.  finally, my experience with my first DSLR camera,  Well, to be honest I have struggled with the controls, but I am now getting used to it. READ THE MANUAL CAREFULLY before operating the camera. The autofocus ability is great but sometimes manual focus is needed when there are multiple objects near and far.  If money is a constraint , you can go for D7000 too but keep in mind it's an aging model(launched sept. 2010) , but hey it's the reason why D7100 exists.  finally I would recommend anyone buying their first camera to research extensively "online","offline" and then choose, if money is a concern then choose more wisely.Get a feel of your cameras by visiting stores so you can get a better idea.  I am happy with my D7100 and hope to learn with experience and enjoy and know more of its features soon.  P.S- It's the person behind the camera who makes the real difference not the camera, it only bridges classic shots with your ability.  anywho, I wish everyone all the best in choosing their cameras. =)  (Sony ,Olympus and Pentax are great choice too)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">The D7100 replaces my trusted D90. A day of use and I found it to be an excellent camera (way ahead of the D90 not only in sensor megapixels but picture quality too). Captures great pictures even in low light, loads of functions, no complaints at all. Priced most competitively on this website, and I'm very happy with this purchase. Now for the 2-star rating.. the freebees include a cheap low speed 4GB card (good for the trash can) and an even worse camera bag.. really bad. None of them are fit to be used with this camera in terms of quality or reliability. Trust me you will want to throw them away at first sight. And to my unpleasant surprise these freebees seem to come straight from Nikon India. I just ordered a Lowepro Adventura 170 for the camera.   Please don't stop reading yet.. The delivery was late by a day which wasn't really an issue. I usually trust Flipkart courier for good service. However this time they sent the camera through a courier service named E-Com Express (cost cutting?). This courier company's website is forever down and hence your shipment cannot be tracked. Many phone calls to their customer care number went unanswered. Finally the delivery came unannounced yesterday evening. The delivery and the condition of the package was straight out of Ace Ventura Pet Detective, where Jim Carry delivers the package in the beginning of the movie (watch the scene on youtube). The box was literally crushed and battered (I took pictures). My heart sank and I asked the delivery guy -- do you know there is an expensive and fragile camera inside this box? And he said to me - that's ok, there is lot of padding inside. Wow!! There was little protective packing inside the main box, which did little to build my confidence (just a few air packets and shrink wrap).  Many thanks to Nikon's excellent camera packing, and the fact that the cheap free bag was taped on the outside of the camera box, the camera and lens turned out intact. But I have no idea how many bumps and jolts they have taken and how long they will work without developing issues. E-Com Express is just bad!!! (If you need pictures, just ask). As for the camera, if you have the dough, go for it!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">This camera sports 51 points auto-focus system which is pretty fast. Its low light performance is very good, even the inbuilt flash works pretty good, no need for dedicated flash for close range photography such as parties and indoor events. Its battery stamina is excellent, you can capture as much as 800 shots in single charge with Live View and Flash turned off.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Love this camera, this fits the budget and looks like a long time companion in terms of built. However, why does WS retail not include a version with 18-140mm lens, which is much better in comparison to 18-105. I would be interested to pick it up from Flipkart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">The Nikon D7100 is a semi-professional with the build and performance of a professional. The price may seem a bit high than the canon D600 and so, but D7100 gives you a much better experience of shooting in many ways. Coming to the sharpness, picture clarity and colors you may feel a bit less but when you zoom in the image it gets better the true components of the image are seen so whenever you take a shot once zoom it in and if you want you can use the command dial and browse through the images. This is because of the high amount of pixel density. So I recommend this beautiful beast to those who want to enjoy their photography.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">i brought it on april 4th..  when i compare d7100 with d90 ,d7100 is fast.. for auto focus and capture.. and its 3.2inch rgbw screen is enough evaluate sharpness of image. its 1.3 crop is very usefull one..for telephoto HD video recording is improved.. better autofocus too.. servo auto focus is awesome..i love its video recording button arranged on top.. it have HDR capability , simply d7100 is rich with new features.  as my knowlege ,its price is much high compare to d7000 and its feature.. and i`m not satisfied with its image quality when compared to d90.. that may be due to its higher megapixel, battery backup is also low compared to d90. its dual layer mode dial is need much effort to use..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">One week before nikon D7100 price was around 86,000. They have increased it price to 92,000. Well done with your Price game flipkart... Almost everyday i was watching your price list of this product....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">This Camra Is Review Picture Too Late And Without Flesh High regulation Picture"s Allmost Out Of Foucs</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Love to have this camera with 16-85mm Kit. Hope flipkart adds that in their range. Their pricing is really competative</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">After so many review, I bought Nikon D7100. Superb Camera. Price wise its cheap when we compare with other online store.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/8000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">DK-5 Eyepiece Cap, AN-DC1 Strap, User Manual, EN-EL15 Rechargeable Li-ion Battery (with Terminal Cover), UC-E6 USB Cable, MH-25 Battery Charger, ViewNX 2 CD, BS-1 Accessory Shoe Cover, DK-23 Rubber Eyecup, BF-1B Body Cap</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D7100</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off: Auto FP High-Speed Sync Supported</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Image Size: DX (24 x 16) Image Area 4494 x 3000 (M), 2992 x 2000 (S), 1.3x (18 x 12) Image Area 4800 x 3200 (L), 3600 x 2400 (M), 2400 x 1600 (S), Photographs with Image Area DX (24 x 16) 6000 x 3368 (L), 4494 x 2528 (M), 2992 x 1860 (S) Photographs with Image Area of 1.3x (18 x 12) Taken in Movie L...View More

Image Size: DX (24 x 16) Image Area 4494 x 3000 (M), 2992 x 2000 (S), 1.3x (18 x 12) Image Area 4800 x 3200 (L), 3600 x 2400 (M), 2400 x 1600 (S), Photographs with Image Area DX (24 x 16) 6000 x 3368 (L), 4494 x 2528 (M), 2992 x 1860 (S) Photographs with Image Area of 1.3x (18 x 12) Taken in Movie Live View 4800 x 2696 (L), 3600 x 2024 (M), 2400 x 1344 (S)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Color Filter">Primary (RGB) Color Filter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F Mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Auto Focus</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100 - 6400</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (2 Types), Incandescent, Fluorescent (7 Types), Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual (upto 6 Values can be Stored, Spot Measurement Available During Live View), Choose Color Temperature (2500 K - 10000 K), Fine-tuning</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Programmed Auto with Flexible Program (P), Shutter-priority (S), Aperture-priority (A), Manual (M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">30</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">TTL Exposure Metering using 2016-pixel RGB Sensor</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Single Lens Reflex Digital Camera, Lens Mount: Nikon F Mount (with AF Coupling and AF Contacts), Effective Angle of View: Nikon DX Format; Focal Length in 35 mm (135) Format Equivalent to 1.5x of Lenses with FX Format Angle of View, Dust Reduction System: Image Sensor Cleaning, Image Dust-off Refere...View More

Single Lens Reflex Digital Camera, Lens Mount: Nikon F Mount (with AF Coupling and AF Contacts), Effective Angle of View: Nikon DX Format; Focal Length in 35 mm (135) Format Equivalent to 1.5x of Lenses with FX Format Angle of View, Dust Reduction System: Image Sensor Cleaning, Image Dust-off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Selected Picture Control Modified, Storage for Custom Picture Controls, Frame Coverage: 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical Magnification, 0.94x (50 mm F/1.4 Lens at Infinity, -1.0 - m-1), Eyepoint: 19.5 mm (-1.0 - m-1; Center Surface of Viewfinder Eyepiece Lens), Diopter Adjustment: -2 - m-1, Focusing Screen: Type B Briteview Clear Matte Mark II Screen with AF Area Brackets (Framing Grid Displayed), Reflex Mirror Quick Return, Depth-of-field Preview: Pressing Depth-of-field Preview Button Stops Lens Aperture Down to Value Selected By User (A and M Modes) or Camera (Other Modes), Instant Return Lens Aperture, Electronically Controlled Vertical Travel Focal Plane Shutter Speed: 1/3 or 1/2 EV, Bulb, Time, X250, Flash Sync Speed: X=1/250 sec, Synchronizes with Shutter at 1/320 sec or Slower (Flash Range Drops at Speeds between 1/250 and 1/320 sec), Release Mode (Single Frame (S), Continuous Low Speed (CL), Continuous High Speed (CH), Quiet Shutter-release (Q), Self-timer, Mirror-up, Interval Timer Photography Supported), Remote Control Modes (Ml-L3): Delayed Remote, Quick-response Remote, Remote Mirror-up, Metering Method Matrix: 3D Color Matrix Metering, Color Matrix Metering II, Color Matrix Metering Available with Lenses, Center-weighted, Flash Range (ISO 100, F/1.4 Lens, 20° C / 68° F), Matrix or Center-weighted Metering: 0 - 20 EV, Spot Metering: 2 - 20 EV, Exposure Meter Coupling, Scene Modes: Landscape, Child, Sports, Close-up, Night Portrait, Night Landscape, Party / Indoor, Beach / Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Pet Portrait, Candlelight, Blossom, Autumn Colors, Food, Special Effects Modes: Night Vision, Color Sketch, Miniature Effect, Selective Color, Silhouette, High Key, Low Key, Exposure Compensation: -5 - EV in increments of 1/3 or 1/2 EV, Exposure Bracketing: 2 - 5 EV in increments of 1/3, 1/2, 2/3, 1, 2, or 3 EV, Flash Bracketing: 2 - 5 in increments of 1/3, 1/2, 2/3, 1, 2, or 3 EV, White Balance Bracketing: 2 - 5 EV in increments of 1, 2, or 3, Exposure Lock: Luminosity Locked at Detected Value with AE-L / AF-L Button, Active Lighting Auto, Extra High, High, Normal, Low, Off, Focus Autofocus: Nikon Advanced Multi-cam 3500DX Autofocus Sensor Module, Fine-tuning, 51 Focus Points (Including 9 Cross-type Sensors, Center 1 Focus Point is Available at Apertures Slower F/5.6 and Faster than F/8), Detection Range: -2 - EV (ISO 100, 20° C / 68° F), Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF): Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S / AF-C Selection (AF-A), Predictive Focus Tracking Activated Automatically According to Subject Status Manual Focus (M), Electronic Rangefinder, Focus Point: Selected from 51 or 11, AF Area Mode, Focus Lock: Focus Locked by Pressing Shutter-release Button Halfway (Single-servo AF) or by Pressing AE-L / AF-L Button, Flash Compensation: -3 - EV in increments of 1/3 or 1/2 EV, Flash-Ready Indicator: Built-in Flash or Optional Flash Unit is Fully Charged, Flashes after Flash is Fired at Full Output, Accessory Shoe: ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync and Data Contacts and Safety Lock, Live View Modes, Live View Photography (Still Images), Movie Live View (Movies), Lens Servo, Autofocus (AF): Single-servo AF (AF-S), Full-time-servo AF (AF-F), Manual Focus (M), AF-area Mode, Face-priority AF, Wide-area AF, Normal-area AF, Subject-tracking AF, Autofocus: Contrast-detect AF, Matrix Metering Method, Audio Recording Device: Built-in or External Stereo Microphone, Playback: Full-frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar) Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo and Movie Slide Shows, Histogram Display, Highlights, Photo Information, Data Display, Auto Image Rotation, Audio Input: Stereo Mini-pin Jack (3.5 mm Diameter; Plug-in Power Supported), Audio Output: Stereo Mini-pin Jack (3.5 mm Diameter), 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Temperature: 0° C - 40° C, Humidity: 85%</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">6000 x 4000 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Programmed Auto with Flexible Program (P), Shutter-priority (S), Aperture-priority (A), Manual (M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, DCF 2.0, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MPEG-4, AVC / H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">765 g (with Battery and Meomry Card), 675 g (Body Only)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">135.5 (W) x 106.5 (H) x 76 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 Years</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC / Compatible with UHS-I</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT Monitor with 170° Viewing Angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3.2 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">1,228,800 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentaprism Single-lens Reflex Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentaprism Single-lens Reflex Viewfinder</specsKey>
