<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d90-dslr-camera/p/itmdv58hfgkzgfnd?pid=CAMCVYDJPFSCN5PA&otracker=from-search&srno=t_456&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff24%2BgfOVcYk44f4a3VwzrW4rfLarTMyXmQaBbju%2Fza6O4aLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=99155b2a-8655-453f-886f-08adb91eb056</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">76</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">16</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/5/p/a/nikon-d90-dslr-400x400-imaeyxyn4ck5wmmn.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">57180</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D90 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Nikon D90 is a great prosumer DSLR in this price range. As someone else pointed out - anything lower than a D90 is not worth being called a DSLR.  Customizability: You can shoot in multiple resolutions, multiple sizes and in JPEG/NEF formats. It has the standard nikon variety of white balances and picture tones, but setting anything is extremely simple once you get a hold of your camera.   Ergonomics: It fits your hand nicely, unlike the D5100 and D3100. Really rock solid, and you immediately get the feel that you're ready for the shoot. The two dials (one for aperture and another for shutter) is much MUCH better than having just one dial as D5100, or any Canon in this range.  Low light performance: Pretty decent. I usually go up to ISO 1600 when I'm in low light, and the pics that come out are usually good enough, with very less graininess.   Battery: Extremely reliable and long lasting. Doesn't take a long time to recharge, and takes about 1000 shots (if you don't use flash).   Autofocus: YES! Which is another big differentiator in the low end cameras like D5100 and D90. The camera itself has an autofocus motor, and it's compatible with all lenses. On a D90. you don't need to buy expensive lenses with AF motor, just because your camera body sucks.  Included Software: Horrible :) Just use Adobe lightroom or Aperture, and you'll be good.  Included Kit lens: 18-105 is a very versatile lens and extremely reliable too. It covers most of the range that you're likely to encounter. Also, the autofocus on this is very silent.  Video: Pretty basic. No autofocus makes it useless for me, really. Even the most basic camcorder is better than a D90 when it comes to video.  Overall - 4/5, mostly because of useless video functionality and due to the fact that D7000 tops D90 in all departments.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Nikon D90 a great camera, with all the features that needed for excellent photography. If we can understand the manual and try all the modes... you become an expert of photography... real good camera... I'd say this is the best when compared with D5100 and D7000 with in the budget</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">I watched many people using entry level DSLRs, but the fact is, the photo quality of those DSLRs are never the same, which is the main criteria for buying a DSLR. Pictures look blotchy and not sharp, specially at night photography on those cameras. I bought D90 even though some newer models were available at that point of time. The reason behind that was its great handling. If you want to take photography seriously and upgrade your camera later on, D90 provides you the same features that other pro cameras offer, including buttons and others features which are essentially same. 12 megapixels are good enough for me, and in daylight the camera is a marvel (I compared my prints with my friends who owns a 5DMII and daylight pics are at par). But the camera pic suffers at night, due to low ISO tolerance. Obviously adding a big aperture lens improves the quality drastically (I use one f-1.4 50 mm prime for night), and adding an external flash can really help you out. Focus speed is not the fastest, but does not matter as long as you do not shoot sports. Weight and ergonomics of the camera is just awesome (an essential for a DSLR, as users know it, a bad ergonomically designed camera weighing more than 1 kg can really hurt your hands for sure). ISO range till 1000 is ok, after that noise is very obvious. Camera features some basic post-processing features, but nobody uses it. 12 bit compressed RAW is a impressive feature and every serious photographers should learn how to use RAW photographs. In built flash is just not good, you need to buy an external flash. VR lenses work fine with this camera (some camera in Nikon lineup has this problem). Best photos can be taken (according to me) in landscape photography and in abstract photography.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">The reason is simple.....it has a more professional body....and gives a feel of actual higher end pro bodies.....lots of switches on the body for tweaking all imp settings u need to change to get that perfect shot....once accustomed.....u hardly have to delve into menus.....just like riding a bike....controlling everything without looking at your gear.....  Whereas in lower end (till d5100) models....u would actually delve into that "nice" menu to change aperture, iso, WB etc......instead of capturing those split second moments u bought your dslr for !!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">D90 was launched somewhere in 2008 but still its ruling the minds of camera lovers. Excellent camera, full of features which you can expect from a high end SLR but almost half the price. I found 18-105mm lens to be bit softer but still its a great lens. I use it for mostly outdoor shootings and this camera is very reliable in all respects. A good buy for many years to come I guess.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">design refresh with slightly sharper lines, the D90 is externally very similar to its predecessor (dimensions are identical, though it is heavier). Looking at the differences it's obviously a solid incremental upgrade rather than a total reinvention of the popular D80, with several key improvements (most importantly the sensor and screen) and a welcome smattering of must-have 2008 features (live view, dust removal). Oh yes, and of course there's that one little new feature sitting at the back of the classroom with its hand waving in the air, shouting 'Sir! Sir!'; the 'world's first' DSLR movie mode.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Not saying anything about D90. People of this domain knows, what D90 means for.  About packing, its awesome. Flicpkart is too good at packing and delivering the product on time.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Ofcourse Nikon D90 marked a turnigg point in the DSLR series. Although 5 years old still D90 holds a dignified position in DSLR market. As usual got the product in express delivery time. (Bangalore) Product was in excellent condition, neatly and thoroughly packed.  About the product, this is an excellent option to go for if you are starting with DSLR. Although for a begineer if budget is less dont go for this. you can always start with a lower one like 3100 5200 etc. All exposure controls are through body knobs making it faster to use. Two controller knobs are there in front and back, one for aperture and one for shutter speed. An ISO button in the front, a high resolution screen. White balance control Auto/manual button. Altogether excellent product for the price</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Honestly i believe the Nikon D90 is the best DSLR available in the market on which you can actually learn photography. it is a truly amazing camera to start off and honestly i still love using this camera. everything about this camera is great. if you are planning of going professional then this would be the best choice as your first camera. once you truly master the skill of taking pictures in this camera shifting to a high end pro DSLR will just make you know your settings much easier and the high ISO will seem to come in easy use. one advice while using this initially its okay to use the kit lens but the rest of your kit try saving up and target the good fast lenses (24-70 f/2.8, 50 f/1.4 etc). if you are planning of getting a DSLR get the D90. you will not regret your decision.   One thing i should mention is that this camera has two main functions that i find to be really useful. this camera has a bigger body compared to the D3200 and the D5200 so if you have huge hands like me then its much more easier to hold and if it still isnt comfortable enough you can buy a battery grip. its really useful and the camera just feels really solid. second, this camera supports autofocus on the body. this allows you to use old lenses which do not have an built in autofocus motor. third. the camera has two separate dials that allow you to use one for aperture and the other one for shutter speed. i found this to be much more useful and comfortable than having to press a button and then scrolling to change the settings as found on the other cameras. few points you want to keep in mind before purchasing one</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Nikon D5300 has many advantages compared to D90 at a similar price tag.  Advantages of the Nikon D5300 over Nikon D90  Higher resolution movies - 1080p @ 60fps vs 720p @ 24fps Significantly lower noise at high ISO - 1,338 ISO vs 977 ISO Significantly better image quality Much higher true resolution 24 MP vs 12.2 MP Video autofocus Significantly larger screen - 3.2" vs 3.0" Has in-camera HDR Has an external mic jack Has a flip-out screen Better color depth - 24 bits vs 22.7 bits Distinguishes 1.3 more bits of color Significantly more focus points - 39 vs 11 More dynamic range - 13.9 EV vs 12.5 EV 1.4 f-stops more dynamic range Has a GPS - Automatically geotags your photos when traveling Higher resolution screen - 1,037k dots vs 930k dots Better boost ISO - 25,600 ISO vs 6,400 ISO  Size - Smaller 124x99x76 mm vs 132x103x77 mm More than 10% smaller Better maximum light sensitivity - 12,800 ISO vs 3,200 ISO Shoots faster - 5 fps vs 4.5 fps Weight - Significantly lighter 480 g vs 703 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D90</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Body, AF-S 18-105mm VR Kit Lens, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL3e, Quick Charger MH-18a, USB Cable UC-E4, Video Cable EG-D2, Camera Strap AN-DC1, Body Cap BF-1A, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, LCD Monitor Cover BM-10, Software Suite CD-ROM, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Fill-in flash, Red-eye reduction, Red-eye reduction with Slow sync, Slow sync, Rear-curtain sync, Off</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">3D-Color Matrix Metering II (type G and D lenses); Color Matrix Metering II (other CPU lenses) performed by 420-segment RGB senso2), Center-weighted: Weight of 75% given to 6, 8 or 10mm circle in center of frame, Spot: Meters 3.5mm circle (Approx. 2%)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Continous low shooting mode: 1-4fps,Continous high shooting mode: 4.5fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 200 to 3,200 in steps of 1/3 EV, plus HI-0.3, HI-0.5, HI-0.7, HI-1 (ISO 6400); sensitivity decreases approx. LO-0.3, LO-0.5, LO-0.7 and LO-1 (ISO 100)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continous low shooting mode: 1-4fps, Continous high shooting mode: 4.5fps, Self-timer mode, Delay remote mode, Quick-response remote mode, D-Movie</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white-balance with 420-pixel RGB sensor), 12 manual modes with fine-tuning; color temperature setting; preset white balance; white balance bracketing</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">17</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection by Nikon Multi-CAM 1000 autofocus module with AF-assist</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.3 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4288 X 2848</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continous low shooting mode: 1-4fps, Continous high shooting mode: 4.5fps, Self-timer mode, Delay remote mode, Quick-response remote mode, D-Movie</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (12 bit compressed RAW),JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">AVI (Motion JPEG compression format with monaural sound</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-5a (Optional)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">620 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">132 (W) x 103 (H) x 77 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">920,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-2 to m-1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-2 to m-1)</specsKey>
