<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d7000-dslr-camera/p/itmduzhmcucnhnga?pid=CAMCVYDJZKYFZVUG&otracker=from-search&srno=t_31&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff21%2BgjdeWCyWGzUqwi0x1wi6PAslvbT8gKSrYo7cfIcKIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=70bfa3c3-0ea3-487e-ab2e-3a6bc8e08d03</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">191</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">46</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/u/g/nikon-d7000-dslr-400x400-imaeyxfajacx9rm2.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">59990</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D7000 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I was really confused while buying this and did a lot of research on several other cameras from nikon and canon - (d90 60d d5200).I even considered spending some more for nikon d7100 or canon 7d and decided instead.This is perhaps the best camera from nikon in APS c range and vastly popular.It provides you all the tools to become a better photographer.I would recommend people not to go for d5200 which lacks autofocus motor - this would prove expensive in the long run since u have to get a motored lens every time.It beats D90 and canon 60d hands down in almost every department (except canon 60d in video).This is the sort of camera that you can own and built a kit around and buy may b a pro body in some years time.You can then use this one as a second camera.People who would like to go for nikon d7100 and 7d i would say get this one and invest in better glasses ..there isnt a lot between d7000 and d7100 (get out of the mega pixel syndrome). For people new to photography or someone who would buy this as an upgrade from basic slrs - i would say get the kit lens , if you already have a 18-55 get the body only...get a 50mm 1.8 d with this one which is quite cheap ... you would then have both wide angle and potrait covered...if you want amazing night results ..make sure u get a tripod and a remote trigger with this one (the 50 mm +tripod +remote = Rs 7500 roughly) .That is a better way to spend money and learn the craft.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I ve purchased it in the month of Sep 2011 from Flipkart. The best deal @ this price range specially compared with Cannon. Cannon cannot stand at this price range with all this features. About performance - it's just awesome. It's AF motor, AF points, low light shooting (excellent), wide range of "scene mode" function for the beginners, heavy weight gives extra stable shooting, magnesium alloy body (for dust protection), for professionals manual mode with LCD preview is greatly helpful for getting a perfect shot. I am still doing new things daily with my cam and it's endless qualities giving new surprises and satisfaction with every shots.  I ve just one word to say...  If U are planning for a cam to experience some great shots, and if you are hesitating by it's high price - I would say GO 4 it if U ve craze on photography.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">I ordered this camera from flipkart and got it delivered in 2 days , all well packed brand new. This is possibly the best semi prof slr body. The kit lens is also reasonably good. The night photos are class leading , real gem of a camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Nikon D7000 SLR is at the pinnacle of semi-pro cameras! It delivers like a pro and at the cost you get it here, it is unbeatable! If you are going for D90, stretch a bit, use the EMI option...and make your dreams come true!   PS: Not to mention the delivery service went flawless...Thanks!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Thanks to flipkart for fast service. I was worry to buy this camera from flipkart because i saw in nikon website that flipkart was not their distributor. Flipkart is the way where people buy their product from their distributor like WS retail and others. I got confuse and called to NIKON, they said you can buy the product any where but the product number has to match with their data base. if not then it is not a right product then i bought the camera from fliptkart and got crosscheck with customer care of NIKON and the product number is matching with NIKON database. So people should not fear to buy Nikon from Flipkart. Eventhough they are buying from Distributor need to cross check with NIKON...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">I have been doing amateur photography for last couple of years. I was using Olympus 4/3 system (E620) for last four years. But lack of service centers and quality in India made me move out of the brand Olympus. And as usual I was confused to choose between Canon and Nikon. Recent price hike of Canon lenses made the lens price comparable between the two giants. And feasibility of using old SLR lenses directly in the body made me lean towards Nikon. Still the contender was Canon 60D and Nikon D5200 (with a wish to get D7000). I am not a fan of taking video using camera (don't like handycams too) so the performance of video was out of my preference points.   For 60D it was the articulated display, price vs performance (being a semi-pro of a time) and for D5200 it was the latest AF system and Nikon's ISO performance.   However opted for D7000 with little more than that of 60D's regular price. D7100 was out in the market then, but the price difference does not justifies the need.   Moving from a 4/3 system, I was overwhelmed with AF lock performance, ISO, DOF factor, and number of lenses that I can opt for (used and new). I am not expert enough to present differences with digits and numbers, but its fun to use this camera. I miss the super menu UI of Olympus, but with direct access buttons and top LCD viewer made the task of changing settings easy. Though the camera is towards heavier side compared to a 4/3 system or other entry level dSLRs, it strikes a perfect balance with 18-105 Nikkor lens and I can carry it around my neck without much trouble, but a sling strap will help a lot to distribute the weight around your shoulder than on your neck.   The 18-105 lens is excellent and it has a good balance between size and reach for a kit lens. And it is sharp enough for an amateur to choose not to opt for more advanced general zoom lens.  There are a lot of advanced settings that I have not tried, and most probably wont use also, but some basic settings I have done and love them, like auto ISO, WB settings, picture control for saturation-contrast and use of U1 and U2 mode. Backed with 2 slot for memory card, I don't have to switch between cards when one is full. A large view finder (compared to my old one) helps me to compose the frame better.   Image Quality is superb with high ISO performance. Now I can go up to ISO3200 with usable quality photos. In 6400 noise it too much unless the frame is filled with less mid-tone and more of full blacks and bright highlights. Color reproduction is natural for most of the WB settings that is set by camera automatically.   Overall I am very happy with this camera - excellent.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">One of the best cameras out there today. Takes photography to a new level of precision and beauty. A must have for any photographer amateur or pro ! I ordered it 2 days back and flipkart definitely lived up to its reputation.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Writing anything about this camera would be like showing wicks to the sun and also people buying this camera, know exactly what they are buying. So unlike other post I wont talk about the camera but Flipkart. I got this camera brand new, awesomely packed with Nikon bag and memory card free. But the best part was the price as I got it at almost a discount of more than 15% with EMI. I compared the price with the local wholesale dealers and it was way less than their price. So thank you Flipkart. :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I've started using the camera from day one. I was quite astonished by the quality of image from the camera. This camera is very user friendly and flexible to use. I highly recommend this DSLR for an enthusiast.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">After using both the Canon 60d and Nikon D7000 for about 2 weeks each, I must admit, it is increasingly difficult to distinguish between the two. Similarly priced with a difference of about 4k with the Canon 60D and 18-135 IS lens, and a similar specs sheet. Ergonomically feels the same as well. But, it is worth noting, that the D7000 does have a few flaws, compared to the Canon 60D.  1. The 60D has an articulated screen. Simply, it can tilt and swivel, much like a handycam. Also, I felt that the 60D had a slightly brighter screen as well, and the screen has a higher resolution - 1,040k dots vs 920k in the D7000. So, if you're into a lot of experimental and creative photography, the 60D clearly beats the D7000 is that aspect. The tilt-y screen does come is handy.  2. The Nikon d7000 oddly drained its battery a lot faster than the 60D! Even though, the specs sheet given by Nikon says it can pump about 1000 shots in a single charge, it doesn't give more than 800, in ideal conditions - with VR switched off in the lens, no use of flash, and minimal change in settings. The canon never fails to deliver anything below 1100 shots. More on this - the canon does switch on after getting off, so, you can manage about 20 clicks after that! but, Nikon, sadly, doesn't.   3. Video Quality. We know it. You know it. Canon will forever beat Nikon in this segment. The continuous Autofocus somehow seems a little inefficient. Though i didn't really get much time to test the video mode much, but, take my word, search up Youtube - Canon 60D delivers a way more warmer and richer Video, than the D7000. Period.  4. For those who suck on megapixels, the 60D has 18 MP, while the D7000 is 16.1 MP. I wouldn't say it necessarily makes a difference, but, when it comes to using wide angle lens, or when you don't have a good telephoto lens, those extra MPs do help in delivering more detail. Nikon fans argue that the higher MP count in canon is the reason for lower image quality, specially a lot noise at higher ISO. Well, I'd suggest you try either the 550D or the 60D at a 12 or 14 MP resolution, lowering it in the camera, trust me, in my old 550D, i got results which rival the Nikon d90 and even the d7000.  5. Even though the Nikon D7000 delivers excellent image quality, beyond all doubts, it still think, its not the same..err..type as the 60D. As in, the Canon delivers images which have a different warmth factor in them. And, to be honest, it somehow matches with most street/abstract/landscape scenes in India. The warmth and the colour tones delivered by the Canon, with identical settings, just seem to compliment the Indian eye better. Ask a friend to click two photos with the same scene, with both the cameras and look at them without knowing which belongs to which. 7/10 times, you'll prefer canon. It might just be my personal experience/feeling, but, somehow canon seems more suited to Indian photography, where most photographs have a sort of dry and warm feel. Nikon never really has tried to improve on this, and hence keeps competing with themselves.  Both the 60D and D7000 are excellent cameras. If you a want to be serious about what you buy, i'd suggest renting them for a day/getting it from a friend and choosing for your preference. Mind you, the d7000 is a tad costlier, but offers you a slightly(5.3 vs 6fps) higher burst rate and a stop more if ISO (upto 25600). Think and buy. happy clicking. Cheers.</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Video Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/8000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D7000</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Body, AF-S 18-105mm VR Kit Lens, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL15, Quick Charger MH-25, Rubber Eyecup DK-21, Camera Strap AN-DC1, Body Cap BF-1B, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, USB Cable UC-E4, Video Cable EG-D2, View NX 2 CD, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes, Pop-up</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Front-curtain Sync, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">12 m (ISO 100)</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes, (Hot-shoe, Wireless)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">3D Color Matrix Metering II, Color Matrix Metering II, Center-weighted, Spot Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">1/250 secs</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6 fps (Top and Sull Speed)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100 to 6400 in Steps of 1/3, 1/2, or 1 EV, plus HI-0.3, HI-0.5, HI-0.7, HI-1, HI-2 (ISO 25600)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (TTL White-balance with Main Image Sensor and 2016-pixel RGB Sensor), Incandescent, Fluorescent, Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manua, Choose Color Temperature</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single Frame Shooting Mode, Continuous Low Shooting Mode (1 - 5 fps), Continuous High Shooting Mode (6 fps), Quiet Shutter-release, Self-timer Mode, Remote Control, Mirror-up Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C Mini-pin HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">22</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">LCD Monitor (170째 Viewing Angle, 100% Frame Coverage, and Brightness Adjustment), Playback Function (Full-frame, Movie Playback, Thumbnail (4, 9, 72, Calendar) Playback, Playback Zoom, Faces Detected During Zoom, Slide Show, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, Image Comment), Del...View More

LCD Monitor (170째 Viewing Angle, 100% Frame Coverage, and Brightness Adjustment), Playback Function (Full-frame, Movie Playback, Thumbnail (4, 9, 72, Calendar) Playback, Playback Zoom, Faces Detected During Zoom, Slide Show, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, Image Comment), Delete Function (Single Image, Selected Images, Images Taken on Selected Date, All Images (Except Protected Images), 1.5x Lens Focal Length (Picture Angle (35 mm (135) Format Equivalent), Viewfinder (Built-in Diopter Adjustment (-3 to .0 m-), Focusing Screen (Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark II Screen with AF Area Brackets), 100% Viewfinder Frame Coverage, 0.94x Magnification (with 50 mm Lens at Infinity; -1.0 m-1), Autofocus (39 Focus Points (9 Cross-Sensors) by Nikon Multi-CAM 4800DX Autofocus Module, Detection Range: -1 to EV (ISO 100 at 20째 C /68째 F), Focus Modes (Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous Servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S / AF-C Selection (AF-A), Predictive Focus, Manual Focus (MF): Electronic Rangefinder), Exposure Control (Digital Vari-Program (Auto, Auto (Flash Off), Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Child, Sports, Close Up, Night Portrait, Night Landscape, Party/Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk/Dawn, Pet Portrait, Candlelight, Blossom, Autumn Colors, Food, Silhouette, High Key, Low Key), Programmed Auto (P), Shutter Priority Auto (S), Aperture Priority Auto (A), Manual (M), U1 (User Settings 1), U2 (User Settings 2), Auto Exposure Bracketing, Shutter (Electronically Controlled Vertical-travel Focal Plane Shutter), Sync Contact (X-contact Only), Flash Contorl (TTL, Auto Aperture, Non-TTL Auto, Distance-priority Manual), Depth of Field Preview Button, Remote Control (Via Wireless Remote Control ML-L3 (Optional)), GPS (GP-1 GPS Unit (Optional)), 1050 Shots Battery Life, 1/4 inch (ISO 1222) Tripod Socket, Expeed 2 Image Processing Engine, D-Movie (Full HD Recording, External Stereo Microphone Input, In-camera Movie Editing), Full-time Servo AF (AF-F) Movie Recording, Dual Card Slots for SD Memory Cards</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F Bayonet Mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">18 - 105 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">3696 x 2448 (M), 2464 x 1632 (S), D-movie (1920 x 1080 at 24p, 1280 x 720 at 30 fps, 1280 x 720 at 25 fps, 1280 x 720 at 24 fps, 640 x 424 at 24 fps)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4928 x 3264 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single Frame Shooting Mode, Continuous Low Shooting Mode (1 - 5 fps), Continuous High Shooting Mode (6 fps), Quiet Shutter-release, Self-timer Mode, Remote Control, Mirror-up Mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (12 bit Compressed RAW), JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Linear PCM Sound, Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV Movie (H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">690 g (without Battery, Memory Card or Body Cap)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">132 (W) x 103 (H) x 77 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Operating System">Windows XP SP3, Windows 7, Windows Vista, MAC OS X 10.4.11, MAC OS X 10.6.4, MAC OS X 10.5.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 24p</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Fixed Eye-level Pentaprism</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">03:02</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Fixed Eye-level Pentaprism</specsKey>
