<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d5100-dslr-camera/p/itmduzhmeyjh2zec?pid=CAMCXH4FFUDGAMHS&otracker=from-search&srno=t_19&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2lhsgsTyCq6R8%2FQo0qYoY%2FUD8TAgS6ZMWF9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">1</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">277</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/m/h/s/nikon-d5100-dslr-400x400-imaeyxfaqgyzvqeb.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">28450</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D5100 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I've used both products, and also own D5100, so I guess the review will be useful for many!  Why you should go for Canon 550D? 1. Well well, street price is lower, you can actually buy some low end camera with that difference.. 2. Built-in focus motor.. This is most important reason why you should go for 550D than D5100. It will save your hell lot of money on your further lens purchases.. You will not need to go for lenses with built-in auto-focus motor, which are much more costly. 3. More megapixels.. About 2 megapixels more.. (Does not bother me much, but bothers few people for sure!) 4. Smaller, thinner and lighter, though not very much! 2.4 inches compared to 3.1 inches.. and 530gm against 560gm! lol... 5. Now on some sites I read that it has lesser start up delay and less shutter lag, but the lag is in few milliseconds, you won't even recognize unless you use both cams for couple of years, separately.. 6. Allegedly, better video quality! 7. Better resolution of live-view-screen, c'mon, nothing related to camera quality though!  Now, did you notice that except built-in motor and more megapixels, everything else are physical attributes, nothing really connected to photo quality,  now lets see why you should go for Nikon D5100? 1. Canon delivers better video quality, but does not auto-focus once the shooting starts.. Will annoy you if the subject moves towards you! 2. The screen has lesser resolution, but flips out and rotates, amazing feature, trust me! 3. Larger sensor, well, APS C of Nikon (DX) is same as standard APS C, but Canon APS C is a little smaller than that! (23.6mmX15.6mm vs 22.3mmX14.9mm, believe me, each nanometer counts!) 4. Better colour depth as each manual shouts, 23.5 bits vs 22.1 bits, well, that means better image quality. 5. More focus points, 11 vs 9, yup that counts! 6. shoots at 4 fps vs 3.7 fps of canon 7. longer battery life, well, something that I have experienced. The capacity says the other way round though, 1120 mAH vs 1030mAH. I guess Nikon engine is more efficient! Also, I find Canon batteries a little costlier than Nikon. 8. Larger ISO 9. Has in camera HDR, awesome, captures two photos at different exposure and combines them to give exact picture as seen by naked eye! That's really cool, something which you cannot do with Photoshop that effectively once the image has been captured! 10. In-camera effects, that's awesome, especially to show-off in front of photography-illiterate people, or photo-editing-illiterate I would say.. :') 11. Allegedly, better image quality at higher ISO owing to more dynamic EV range.  So, I guess the winner is Nikon D5100!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Like you, even i was confused... Nikon D5100 or Canon 600D? I had spend months trying to decide the same. And whenever i was about to decide on one, the thoughts of other came and haunted me :/ On top of those, the reviews and 'expert' advises of friends... My situation was hopeless :) But on 24th July 2013, i declared an end to the war!  Yes, i had a bias towards Nikon. But that was not the only reason for selecting Nikon... Since i had gone through the pain and torture of this selection process, i thought i would pen down, here, what worked for me... Who knows, may be this would help some of you!   First some facts :   1. There is no 'the best' or 'the better' here. Both are absolutely worth the money you spend.  2. If its the photography that you are interested in, then N 5100 is the one for you. But if it is video too, then C 600D 2. I felt Canon to be more user friendly. Also, while holding Canon, you feel full. Hope you got what i meant! Where as Nikon gives you a kinda light weight stuff feeling. But after using Nikon for a while, i am very comfortable with it.  3. Also, Never make the mistake of comparing pictures taken in both by looking at the LCD screen in camera. Canon has a sharper LCD screen. So, if you want to compare the pictures, copy it in a laptop/tab and see it. Much better option would be taking print and analyzing it. 4. Now the much hyped 'built in motor'. Its quite natural if it confuses you. Just chuck it! But if you just cant, open 2 pages and compare Nikon and Canon Lenses side by side. You would discover that both are costlier no matter what. So... no point in worrying about it... Besides, once you buy a particular brand, i dont think you would think "oh my god, the other brand lenses are cheap!" Instead you would only be looking at the same brand lenses and compatible lenses.   Now how would you select:   1. Walk into reliance digital or QRS or something of that sort and ask for a demo of these 2 devices and take couple of pics too. As you go home, you would have decided on the user friendliness factor. 2. Ask yourself which brand you are more inclined to. Start watching youtube videos on that rather than watching both Nikon and Canon videos. It helps :p  3. Now, once these 2 are over, you keep a watch on the prices in Flipkart, eBay etc... There will an offer one day or another. I had to wait it a bit long, but it proved to be worth. I bought it for 28104 (24th July 2013). When converted to EMI (6 months) the total cost became 28500. It was a pretty good deal that time (normal price was 31k). With 4gb card and carry case :)  My Exp with Nikon D5100:   Absolutely worth the money i spend for... Learning phase is great.. Besides, the wow factor that appears on others face. I recently (August 2014) added Nikkor 35mm f1.8G (affordable bokeh lenses - 7.6k).  I am pretty happy with the pics i take. One thing is for sure, when you start experimenting with it, you will automatically graduate to the next level of photography.. So dont worry about your present expertise level. All you need is a creative mind. Also, never worry about the lenses you have to add. Start with the basic lens. As you progress you will realize what is your specialty (zoom, bokeh, landscape, portrait etc). Once you finds that out, purchase lenses accordingly rather than just adding with out any purpose.   So happy shopping and enjoy your camera. Gook luck :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Nikon D5100 is a superior DSLR Camera, priced at entry level. Its is mainly compared with Canon 550D.  Nikon D5100 scores for : Superior Image quality due to Nikon's Advanced Exceed processor. Sturdy Build. Higher ISO Rating , by that Higher low light efficiency. 3.0' Vari-Angle swivel LCD.  Canon 550D:  Higher Image Capacity : 18MP Include inbuilt AF Motor, and availability of variety of lenses. Smaller Build. Sharper LCD screen. Various speed video recording efficiency.  Bottom Line: Both Cameras are equally good , leap frogging others marginally in different zones which makes someone who have to chose his first camera totally confused. You cant go wrong with each one of them.  If your area of interest is "Real Photography" , I would suggest Nikon D5100. But if you are a "Photography Video Enthusiast" , canon 550D might suit you better.  For me I picked Nikon D5100, because would like to horn my Photography skills.  As far as Value of Money and Delivery is concerned, Its very hard for another E-commerce site to beat FlipKart....  Happy shopping guys !!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I ordered the Nikon D5100 DSLR from Flipkart on the 1st of Nov'12 and received it within 48 hrs of placing the order, on the 3rd Nov'12 at my door step. Thanks Flipkart.com for the super fast delivery of the product in good condition.  Nikon D5100 DSLR, is placed between Entry level and Pro level DSLR cameras from Nikon. Precisely between D3100 and D7000. Before zeroing on the D5100 I did my own research about Nikon and Canon. Since Nikon and Canon are the leading brands in Camera Optics, it was easier to ignore the others in the trade. I specifically compared Nikon D5100 Vs. Canon EOS 600D. The Specs looked quite similar, except that the Nikon D5100 has a slight edge over the Canon EOS 600D in terms of Image capturing, quality of images, color and details of images. The Canon scored the brownie points in terms of Video shooting.   Being Nikon fan, it was easier for me to opt/choose for NIKON DSLR as my next. Before Graduating to NIKON DSLR, I have used Nikon Point-n-Shoot(Nikon Coolpix L20) and a Bridge camera (Super zoom Nikon Coolpix P80).   Product Details:  NIKON are very good at Optics in terms of IMAGING. Their EXSPEED Processors built into their cameras are exceptionally built and are of high quality image processing unit. The D5100 has Exspeed II Processor which is very good are processing the image captured and then saving it ont he Data storage (Internal storage or External storage). The sensor is of 16.2 mega pixel DX format CMOS sensor.  Advantage of Nikon D5100 over Canon EOS 600D or for that matter even other brands (Sony alpha DSLRs) are as below: a) 11 Point Auto focus system over Canon's 9 Point. b) Lighter in weight than that of Canon EOS 600D c) Slightly Cheaper in price compared to Canon. d) Greater Color depth 23.5 bits as compared to Canon EOS 600D e) Wide Dynamic range 13.0 EV f) Images are sharper and less/low noise at high ISO Sensitivity while capturing snaps. g) The NIKON D5100 has in camera HDR (High Dynamic Range) where as the Canon EOS 600D does not have HDR in built. h) Nikon D5100 has larger Sensor @ 23.6mm x 15.6 mm Vs. 22.3mm x 14.9mm of that of Canon.(Hence more light enters into the sensor and better image capturing experience) i) The Shutter lag is less than that of Canon EOS 600D. (273 mili seconds Vs. 283 mili seconds) j) The Nikon D5100 shoots at a faster rate of 4fps (frames per second) that than of Canon at 3.7 fps. k) Has additional Special Effects option on the Mode dial with around 5 -7 special effects for better and innovative image capture. l) One specific observation I have noticed is that at low ISO settings, the D5100 is equal with the best of the competition Canon EOS 600d, Nikon D3100 , but at the higher ISO settings, it produces some of the best image quality that on would have ever seen from an APS-C sensor camera. m) The it lens provided with this product (Nikon D5100) is good for getting you started with DSLR. A good all purpose lens at a cheaper price but is worth using for your start-up into DSLR photography.  n) The lens is of focal length 18mm - 55 mm G type lens. it is quite good at capturing your subject's image at a wider range. o) Both Nikon and Canon have a good repository of lenses to choose from.  p) The kit lens of Nikon is quite good, but I would only suggest to go for additional lens once you have got a good hang of DSLRs . One all purpose zoom lens (Tamron or Sigma), one Prime lens of 50 MM f1.8 aperture fixed focal length for outdoors is a must have in your lens collection. q) I observed that the Battery life of Nikon D5100 is pretty good at capturing even the high resolution images. So at a Medium size image capture the number of images would increase and save battery life. r) The LCD Menu is easy to understand and with the help button in hand on the rear body of the camera it serves as a good tutorial as well. s) The Live view on the Tilting LCD screen is great to have. But the only problem here is that it takes quite a split of a second to focus on the subject. t) Image quality is definitely the D5100's trump card. It offers effectively the same image quality as the higher-end D7000, at a lower cost, and it's hard to argue that this is not a good thing.  The final word from my side is : The Nikon D5100 is without doubt one of the most compelling and competitive products in its class compared to Canon and Sony, and offers an excellent mixture of straightforward handling, a well-targeted feature set, and excellent video and still image quality. As we'd expect from a camera with such a solid lineage, the D5100 is responsive and reliable in operation, and produces excellent images with a minimum of fuss.   Overall, I am very satisfied with the product bought and would definitely recommend the Nikon D5100 DSLR to someone for his/her first choice as a beginner DSLR camera.   - Cheers!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Big thanks to Flipkart and WS Retail for quick delivery! 48 hours from order to receipt! Packaging was good, as always.  I am very satisfied with my Nikon D5100 + 35mm f/1.8, would recommend both wholeheartedly to anybody considering a DSLR.  My review is to help others buying their first DSLR make a decision. Firstly, all DSLRs take excellent photos and videos too. I believe that no one brand is MUCH better than the others  1. Budget: Whatever your budget, buy at least one good lens to suit your needs. Don't spend your full budget on a DSLR + kit lens *UNLESS* the kit lens is really enough. Good lenses help take good photos. If your budget is around 35k, consider a camera for under 30k with kit + at least one more lens to suit your needs.  2. Lenses: What type of photography do you plan on doing? Indoors/outdoors, portraits/landscapes, kids/pets etc.? Your satisfaction with any DSLR depends heavily on your choice of lenses to match your needs. Research a little and find what focal length/aperture/zoom and PRICE suits your needs.  3. Camera control: Understand your needs. If you are new to photography in general or don’t want to fidget with settings but still want to take good photos, too many buttons may not be needed, or just get in the way and overwhelm you. A camera that takes good pictures in "Auto" may better suit you. Nikon is usually the best at doing everything well automatically. As you learn more, you can fine tune all of your Nikon DSLR's 'Auto' settings too!  4. Features: All cameras offer broadly the same features, but here is why in the entry to upper-entry segment, I believe Nikon DSLRs are the best -- feature wise:  -- Intelligent Auto ISO: Set MIN ISO, MAX ISO *AND* MIN Shutter speed. Other DSLRs have a button to adjust ISO, but with this Nikon feature, you will rarely ever need to adjust ISO again! It's not found on the 600D, no idea about the 1200D. -- Customizable White Balance presets: All Nikon DSLRS allow you to customize every WB preset to your tastes including Auto. Plus one custom setting too! As far as I know, you will not find this on entry level DSLRs. -- Nine Custom picture styles in camera + 99 on SD card. You can also transfer these to a different Nikon DSLR, so your custom picture styles will be with you as long as you use Nikon DSLRs. -- Menu history tab. Nikon menus are simple anyway. But they also have a history tab. Your most recently changed setting are saved. Even if you changed one item in playback menu, one from shooting menu, one from touch up menu, the history tab stores them. You may never have to keep navigating the entire menu again after just a short while of using your Nikon DSLR. Neat! -- Easy live view/Movie mode: Nikon beats Canons here. Push one lever to lock the mirror up, Live view starts, press the movie record button. Movie recording begins. No need to turn the mode dial. -- Live view/Movie autofocus. The Nikon D3x00/D5x00 and above will do this. Not all other brands of entry/upper entry DSLRs offer movie autofocus. It's not super-fast, but it's better than manual focus! -- In-camera RAW to JPEG. Some competing entry level DSLRs lack this feature. All Nikon DSLRs have it. All DSLRs should have this. Non-pro buyers at this price point are unlikely to want to process their RAW files on their PC/Laptop, especially if they only occasionally need to adjustment white balance/color tone. -- Reliable exposure metering: Nikons are generally believed to have reliable exposure metering, with/without flash. Other entry/upper entry DSLRs are generally a small step down, my research suggests. You may still have to apply exposure compensation but you won't find yourself needing to change it often or have your subject under/over exposed when you least expected it on a Nikon.  Overall, Nikons entry/upper entry DSLRs are better suited to users who want to take great photos, with minimum fuss, and don't want to spend a lot of time changing settings or post processing images. Nikons are generally perceived to be more reliable and rugged, and built to last. Also, Nikon make great lenses at many price points and you get lots of accessories for them, so it's not a brand you will ever have to worry about starting out with.  One last point. D3xx/D5xx, it can get confusing. Here is my advice: - 24 vs 16 MP: You will benefit from 24 MP if (a) you have good lenses that can resolve 24 MP OR you shoot with apertures 5.6 or smaller for max sharpness, (b) you shoot at low ISOs, never over ISO 800, and (c) you need to take small crops or make big enlargements often. Otherwise, the only difference between 24 vs 16 MP are larger file sizes. - Swiveling screen. The D5xxx range has it, D3xxx doesn’t. It’s a great feature and worth having. - Overall price/performance/VFM/image quality: In my opinion, the D5100 is the clear winner here, compared to other Nikon DSLRs and other brands too, in the 30k segment.  Happy shooting :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Hi, this is an ongoing war between two market leaders in DSLR segment. but if you are looking for serious (as mentioned by Harikrshna) then I would strongly recommend go with Nikon while considering following points.  Nikon D5100 Highlights: > Low noise at high ISO  > Great color depth > Great image quality > Wide dynamic range  Canon 550D > Built-in focus motor > Thin(2.4")   This will give you an idea that Nikon D5100 has best entry level fully loaded camera for serious aspiring photographers.   People this is never ending debate between Nikon users and Canon users but I personally find Nikon as a better camera over its counterpart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I was looking for a DSLR for our first foreign family holiday. Selected D5100 after reading good reviews on Flipkart. But today having made the advance payment, I regret my decision. Today I feel that COD would have been the better option. Since they have received the payment, Flipkart is not at all interested in getting the product delivered to me. The Ekart Logistics tracking site states that the Camera has reached my locality on 30th Nov. But today is 7th Dec & even after repeated reminders, it is yet to be delivered to me. It seems that Ekart Logistics is a Big Liar & Bluffers. They are updating their sites with false data (dates) and definitely it is done with the full knowledge of Flipkart. Eagerly waiting for this camera to arrive before I leave for the holiday. But now it seems I will have to go on my holiday without this camera. I would advise everyone to think twice before making advance payment. COD would be better.  Update on 10th Dec Even after repeated reminders & requests to the Callous Flipkart Customer care & Customer Support the Camera has not yet been delivered to me. Nobody in Flipkart has any clue what-so-ever about its current status. Everyone is giving vague replies & empty assurances after conveniently pocketing my hard earned Rs 28920. I have to leave now for the holiday without the camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Nikon's D5100 exceeds expectations, performance by the brilliant CMOS sensor found on the larger and more expensive D7000, the Nikon D5100 is the ideal DSLR for those who are serious about quality pictures and plan on using the camera long term at an affordable budget. The Nikon D5100 takes low light photography to a level that competing DSLR'S desperately try to reach. Full HD 1080p recording and full time auto focus, with the option of an external mic input, the D5100 might very well replace your stand alone handycam! And really this simply sweetens the deal. Flipcart offers an amazing discount with a DSLR camera bag and an ipod shuffle, simply perfect for those occasions when you're waiting for the perfect time! Best of all a 30 day guarantee! No other online destination offers such awesome deals! Get it now! =D</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I'm not a professional Camera person, just a click-mate. Purchasing your first DSLR camera can be a hectic exercise to your fingers and eyes & Yes ! more amount of internet data usage. Reviewing lots of videos on You tube, lots of links for different comparisons between Nikon and Canon needs to be done.   Nikon and Canon are more like the opposite faces of a sword, Similarly Sharp & Shiny. Go for whatever you want. Don't take a brand for granted, nothing is perfect though.   I chose D5100 because during my searching process I found It a high-end beginners camera at a starting Price. So just have this in your hands and wait for the magic.  Comparison leads to confusion without any conclusions at some places but still if you compare it with its successors and predecessors (D5200, D5000, D3100 and D3200) it is a good machine to Grow your third eye in budget.  One more thing, don't look for the Megapixels. This is just a technical term unless there is a difference like 8 Megapixels and 24 Megapixels. Don't forget, you still like that digital picture taken by a mobile VGA camera in resolution of 128X160 pixels.  As I can see in some reviews, problems about registering the product. I registered it easily.  & for flipkart, Change your name to Quickkart.:)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Hi , I upgraded my camera from Fuji Fine Pix 2000 HD to DSLR after doing lot of research, I was about to take the Nikon D3100 as I can not afford the D7000 but this camera is you can say having most quality that D7000 is offering. I am happy to buy this & Having no complained till date. But for new user I would say take this machine only when you have the passion of the camera as it requires lot of care.  For complete utilization of this camera, you will have to take one 70 mm to 300 mm lense as 17-55 mm lense is not sufficient enough.</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D5100</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Body, AF-S 18-55mm VR Kit Lens, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL14, Battery Charger MH-24, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, USB Cable UC-E6, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Rubber Eyecup DK-20, Strap AN-DC3, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, Body Cap BF-1B, ViewNX 2 CD, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Fill-flash, slow sync, auto slow sync, red-eye reduction, auto with red-eye reduction, slow sync with red-eye reduction, auto, slow sync with red-eye reduction, rear-curtain sync, rear-curtain with slow sync.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">3D color matrix metering II</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Continuous shooting mode: Approx. 4fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100 to 6400 in steps</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame, Continuous: 4fps, Self-timer, Delayed remote, Quick-response remote, Silent shuttle release, D-Movie.</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white-balance with main image sensor and 420-pixel RGB sensor), Incandescent, Fluorescent ( 7 types ), Direct, Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, preset manual.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">HDMI output (Type C mini-pin connector)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">22</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection,11 focus points</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4928 x 3264 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame, Continuous: 4fps, Self-timer, Delayed remote, Quick-response remote, Silent shuttle release, D-Movie.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (12 or 14-bit lossless compressed or compressed RAW), JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV movie (H.264, MPEG-4 AVC compression format with Linear PCM sound; Stereo sound with external microphone)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">509 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">128 (W) x 96.9 (H) x 78.7 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Eye-level pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Eye-level pentamirror</specsKey>
