<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l27-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdg4kf4grzgf6z?pid=CAMDGAFF99ANZAYX&otracker=from-search&srno=t_152&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0apxW%2Fc5KLRwQ1suVtXufhJCyLEgJB8dDbAfZ%2FmKkJvoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=a1b53757-b30a-4964-8785-1ac6f15c41cf</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">3.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">192</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">50</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/a/y/x/nikon-coolpix-l27-point-shoot-400x400-imadgx992zgbjnbp.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">4641</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L27 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">White</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Flipkart maintained standards and delivered L27 within 3 days. L27 is my first digital camera. Habituated of the simplicity of a phone camera (I own samsung galaxy note) and the touch screen, the first day with this new toy was frustrating. But after going through the camera manual, I am now convinced with my purchase. Specification wise it is same as L26 though with a smaller screen, but is almost 400 Rs. cheaper. Initial photos were a bit shaky, but as the day passed I was able to take some decent pics. Pouch is nice but without a strap. Over all I am quite satisfied, and will recommend to those who want a decent camera at cheap price. nice one to learn basics of photography</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I bought NIKON Digital L27 camera on 21st of Oct 2013 from flipkart. Everything was going fine with it till last week of July 2014 when I found some lining marks on LCD screen of the camera. I thought it was because of the low battery and ignore it. But after two weeks (Aug 2014) if found a large black spot on LCD screen.  I went to the Nikon service Centre PUNE (Surana services) on 30th of Aug 2014 and told them the problem. Instead of providing me the free service (because the camera is still under warranty) they ask me to pay 2250 as a replacement charge for LCD because the defect doesnât come under warranty. I donât know why it doesnât come under warranty. The representative name is PRAKASH.  When I contacted the customer care number of NIKON, a lady named MANISHA was there for my help. I told her my problem and the response from her was âSir, we donât encourage our customers to buy our product ONLINE. As you buy this product from flipkart, we are not sure about the quality of the productâ.  And when I question her that why you guys sell your product online(flipkart) if you are not sure about the quality that flipkart is providing, the answer was âwe canât do anything sir. You have to pay the amount whatever the service Centre guy is askingâ  My question is to the Nikon personals that if you don't trust online sites then why are you allowing them to sell your product and defame your name?</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Do not expect much, you will be happy... Its better than mobile camera or the best in class if you have budget of 4.0k - 4.5k around...Its good that it comes with all required accessories, so just open the pack and capture the moments.. - Aniruddha</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">1st of all its from Nikon. So, picture quality is better quality. It costs only 4.7K (under 5K). It comes with HD video recording. & About the Video quality it is very very good quality.. Its also with 5X Opt Zoom which is also good at this budget. Apart from this, you will get the complete package which means- Nikon L27 Digi Cam, Cable, Battery, Battery Charger, Hand Strap, 4GB SDHC Memory Chip, Camera Pouch.  It has the features of 35 Pre Set Camera Photo Capturing Mode. Lastly, Grab it ASAP.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Three months of nominal usage and the flash is down. Sometimes it flashes erratically without any command and with a command refuses to fire! Thoroughly disappointed with the product. A slap on the face of Nikon's brand value. Hope they are listening.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">this camera is best for capturing your precious moments at your home, party, hangouts with friends and outdoor activities.this is a light wight camera. you can keep it in your pocket.   this is not a professional photography camera. so if you want to use it for advanced photography plz select another cam.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">PROS: [+] Amazing picture quality in daylight. [+] Very portable due to its small size and lightweight,the strap provides good hand grip [+] Strong flash : really useful in cloudy or evening time. [+] Software : makes easy to port images from camera to computer(Windows: XP,7,8 tested, Linux: Unbuntu tested, Mac not tested ) [+] Best budget digital camera.  CONS: [-] To recharge, the battery case need to be opened every time [-] Image quality is poor if taken in night [-] Image quality is poor if taken in excessive/direct light exposure e.g. sun  Note: Buy a pair of rechargeable AA battery (I received as I bought it during offer period) along with a charger to make photographic experience smoother :D .</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">First of all thanks flip kart for delivering this in a day..ordered it on a sat and got it on Monday!! Awesome service..and the packing and stuffs were all good!!  This is a good camera at below 5k and let me tell you the pic quality is awesome..u can modify the pics with the inbuilt apps as well!! I loved this camera and was a good buy for me. It has HD 1080 recording ..the clarity is superb..!!  U will fall in love with photography once u start clicking on this camera!!  Go for it !!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I have recently purchased it and its a good deal at a cheaper price.I have had used Sony cybershot and a Cannon point & shoot cam. and this one comes with loads of features at a decent price.It has hd video recording and quality is much better.It can be easily carried anywhere you go.A very handy product.My Blackberry(curve) does not have a very good image quality so, i had to purchase it and I think every penny i've spend on it, got its worth.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">quality is good. flash is good free: 4gb memory card,2 rechargable batteries worth rs.600,good camera pouch and a rope,and extra 2 unrechargable batteries  cons: have 2 remove the battery and recharge it again and again.it irritates me.  yaah.i bought it from another dealer for rs.4450.the camera will b delivered after 7-8 days from this dealer but i got it within 6 days.thanks flipkart.  thats it. it's an awesome camera. go for it!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Image Size: 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 4608 x 2592, Movie: HD 720p (Default Setting): 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, VGA: 640 x 480 / 4:3 / 30 fps, QVGA: 320 x 240 / 4:3 / 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 23.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 130 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">161 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">96.4 (W) x 59.2 (H) x 28.9 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,400 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">USB Cable, View NX 2, Battery, Camera, User Manual Guide, Strap</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L27</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 3.6 m (W), 0.8 - 1.7 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.2 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">26 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 10 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">EXPEED C2 Image Processing System, Easy-to-hold Handgrip Design, Stylish Body with High-grade Metallic Exterior, 18 Scene Modes, Smart Portrait System Blink Proof Alerts, Red-eye Fix Corrects False Eye Color Due to the Flash, Motion Blur Reduction, Crisp HD (720p) Video Recording, Lens Construction:...View More

EXPEED C2 Image Processing System, Easy-to-hold Handgrip Design, Stylish Body with High-grade Metallic Exterior, 18 Scene Modes, Smart Portrait System Blink Proof Alerts, Red-eye Fix Corrects False Eye Color Due to the Flash, Motion Blur Reduction, Crisp HD (720p) Video Recording, Lens Construction: 6 Elements in 5 Groups, Center Focus-area Selection, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Exposure Control: -2.0 - .0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Shutter: Mechanical and Charge-coupled Electronic Shutter, Aperture: Electronically-controlled ND Filter (-2.7 AV) Selection, Aperture Range: 2 Steps (f/3.2 and f/8 (W)), Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Temperature: 0° C - 40° C, Humidity: 85%</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Easy Auto, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG Compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-65A AC Adapter (Optional), MH-72 / MH-73 Battery Charger (Optional)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">20 MB</specsKey>
