<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-p600-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdv8ucnbdww4kk?pid=CAMDV8QK4JFEBXXQ&otracker=from-search&srno=t_17&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff1KywcyJqRAcJw7t425PIUlbcA9e8o36pWF9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.3</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">123</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">38</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/x/q/nikon-coolpix-p600-point-shoot-400x400-imadvfg92tpurhz6.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">21299</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix P600 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">extremely good product. 60 x zoom is what attracted me to the product. and also the pricing which is quite affordable considering you want such good zoom. I dnt think any other brand offers it in this price range and Nikon can't be compared to others. Only thing I found a little disheartening was that the autofocus on the subject while zooming is a tad slow compared to other cameras and even compared to Nikon L830 which has 30x zoom. Otherwise its cool. The multivariangle display is cool if you are looking out for a zoom monster and dont want a dslr this is the product to choose</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Few days back we visited Singapore and felt that our many of the memorable shots are not coming correctly just because of camera. We did lot of research and found 2 options for myself 1) D SLR 2) Point & Shoot Camera  After a detailed research we found Nikon Cool Pix 600 and found value for money and best device in the segment. The level of zoom it has and other capabilities will make you mesmerised. Amazingly superb device for novice users.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">After all the confusion of buying an SLR, I would clearly state this is a good point and shoot camera :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">If you are not a professional photographer then this camera is for you. Excellent performance and great delivery by flipkart. If someone has seen moon videos of this camera on youtube..then they dont lie. I managed same quality video from this.  Best utility is camera remote control through ipad or android device.. works great</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Pros- Lithium-ion battery wi-fi enabled makes easy sharing 60x zoom is very quick and sharp view finder enables to give slr touch Adjustable screen is too good   Cons- Sorry</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Worth buying camera with super zoom of 60X and cool features for 20K price range.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">a very nice camera for the price. it has awesome zoom and very good functions. I wanted a camera only for zoom purpose as I already have a DSLR, so i found this to suit my needs and budget.  Only flop side was Flipkart having promised an offer of 8GB card plus camera pouch with the product, and the pouch i received was of some other digital P&S camera, more so of the small sleek types. the pouch hardly measures 4inch by 3inch size, obviously not for p600. Flipkart should note what products they are shipping and what offers they are giving before shipping</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Looks to be a good camera.. i received it few days back yet to explore it. Took some pics from it.. appears to be ok with good clarity and zoom. I was dilemna to buy either to go for cannon or nikon finally i bought nikon and hope it stands up to my expectations.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">THIS IS NOT A PROFESSIONAL CAMERA... IF YOU ARE LOOKING FOR ONE, THEN GO AND BUY AN SLR...   FOR LESSER MORTALS... 1. Looks awesome 2. Can be controlled manually. 3. Feels nice. (light) 4. Image quality: suits your basic need 5. Zoom: Monstrous 6. Aperture, Shutter speed: negotiable</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">My first experience of shopping on flipkart. The order reached fast. The camera is awesome.good discount. Worth buying.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 Sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Type">Mechanical, CMOS Electronic Shutter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Speed in other Modes">-1 - 1/4000 sec, -15 - 1/4000 sec (when ISO Sensitivity is 100 in M Mode), when the Aperture Value is Set to f/7.6 (Wide-angle End)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">16.76</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Movie (1080/30 fps (Default Setting)): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080 / 25 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/60i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/50i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/25 ...View More

Movie (1080/30 fps (Default Setting)): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080 / 25 fps (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/60i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (1080/50i: 1920 x 1080 (16:9)), (720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (iFrame 720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (480/30 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (480/25 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (HS 480/4x: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (HS 720/2x: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (HS 1080/0.5x: 1920 x 1080 (16:9))</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.3 - 258 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 24 - 1440 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Focus Features">Focus Area Selecton: Target Finding AF, Face Priority, Manual (Spot), Manual (Normal), Manual (Wide), Subject Tracking, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Pre-flashes, Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 5760 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Construction">16 Elements in 11 Groups (4 ED Lens Element and 1 Super ED Lens Element)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus Range">50 cm (1 ft, 8 inch) - Infinity (W), 2.0 m (6 ft, 7 inch) - Infinity (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">60x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">565 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">125 (W) x 85 (H) x 106.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Modes">Programmed AE with Flexible Program, Shutter-priority Auto, Aperture-priority Auto, Manual, Exposure Bracketing Enabled</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Display Viewing Angle">6 Levels Brightness Adjustment</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Exposure">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Compensation">1/3 EV Steps +/- 2.0 EV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Wi-Fi Standard">IEEE 802.11b/g/n</specsKey>
<specsKey="Wi-Fi Connectivity">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Wireless Connectivity">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Tripod Socket">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">P600</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Compensation">Flash Exposure Compensation: 1/3 EV Steps, +/- 2 EV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.3 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 7 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 7), Continuous L (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 1 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 200), Pre-shooting Cache (the Frame Rate for Continuou...View More

Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 7 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 7), Continuous L (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 1 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 200), Pre-shooting Cache (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 15 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 20, Including a Maximum of 5 Frames Captured in the Pre-shooting Cache), Continuous H:120 fps (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 120 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 60), Continuous H:60 fps (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 60 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 60), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16, Intvl Timer Shooting</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100 - 1600, ISO 3200 - 6400 (Available when Using P, S, A or M Mode) Hi 1 (ISO 12800 Equivalent)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M...View More

Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M, User Settings</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">ISO Sensitivity (Auto): 0.5 - 7.5 m (W), 1.5 - 4.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">1 cm (0.4 inch) - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Temperature">0° C - 40° C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Humidity">85%</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering Modes">Matrix, Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type D Micro HDMI Out</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish...View More

Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish, Swedish, Tamil, Telugu, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian, Vietnamese</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Viewfinder: 0.5 cm (0.2 inch), 201,000 dots Equivalent LCD with the Diopter Adjustment Function (+/- 4 m -1), Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift, Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Still Pictures: 330 Shots when Using EN-EL23, Charging Time: 3 hrs (when Using Charging...View More

Viewfinder: 0.5 cm (0.2 inch), 201,000 dots Equivalent LCD with the Diopter Adjustment Function (+/- 4 m -1), Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift, Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Still Pictures: 330 Shots when Using EN-EL23, Charging Time: 3 hrs (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-71P and when No Charge Remains), Movie Recording (Actual Battery Life for Recording), 1 hr 20 min when Using EN-EL23, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode and Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Vari-angle TFT LCD (RGBW), Communications Protocols: IEEE 802.11b: DBPSK/DQPSK/CCK IEEE 802.11g: OFDM, Range (Line of Sight): 10 m (11 yd), Operating Frequency: 2412 - 2462 MHz (1 - 11 Channels), Security: Open/WPA2, Access Protocols: CSMA/CA, 120x Dynamic Fine Zoom, Aperure: Electronically-controlled 6-blade Iris Diaphragm, Range: 8 Steps 1/3 EV (W), (A, M Mode), Lithium Battery (EN-EL23)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M...View More

Auto, Scene (Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Landscape, Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, Moon, Bird-watching), Special Effects, P, S, A, M, User Settings</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">4608 x 3072 (3:2), 3456 x 3456 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Megapixels">4608 x 3456 (16 M), 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">File System: DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Audio: LPCM Stereo, WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Still Image Size 16:9">4608 x 2592 (12 M), 1920 x 1080 (2 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">JPEG Sound Files (Voice Memo), MOV (Video: H.264 / MPEG-4, AVC)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Aspect Ratio">16:9, 3:2, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-71P AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">56 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Wi-Fi">Yes</specsKey>
