<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s6700-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdu5x4nczgrn5h?pid=CAMDU5X4NCZGRN5H&otracker=from-search&srno=t_39&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff00BVC%2BGP3RyL53Nq957mt0%2B9TcY5QngVaSrYo7cfIcKIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=70bfa3c3-0ea3-487e-ab2e-3a6bc8e08d03</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">3.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">61</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">14</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/n/5/h/nikon-coolpix-s6700-point-shoot-400x400-imadu6uc6uhqqehz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">6300</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S6700 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">At the very beginning, I would like to thank Flipkart.com for such a prompt delivery within 2 days, and that too in such a beautiful and tamper proof packaging!! I was in need of a camera, which should be more user-friendly and easy to use, and also light weight. I did various R&D works over the internet, not less than 1 fortnight, and finally 2 models stood in my list, which were:  i) Nikon S6700. ii) SONY-W830.  I go confused about which one to opt for, and then I luckily got a link, showing the video quality of Nikon-S6700 in Youtube, after which I made my decision to simply go for this 20.1 MP and 10x Optical zoom camera.  And, while I received the camera and after checking some snaps and videos, I realized that by choosing this camera, I took the RIGHT decision. A really awesome camera, with easy-to-use features and so light-weight and it easily fits in one's hand. I will recommend this to those who are searching for a Family Camera, especially or the beginners. And at last but not the least, thanks to WS-Retail, for providing this camera at a reasonable price, as compared to other sellers.  Note : Battery takes upto 2.30 Hours to get charged completely (As it took in my case). And there is no separate Charging unit supplied, hence for charging the battery, you will need to connect one end of the wire to the wall socket, and the other end to your camera (In switch off mode), and obviously with the Battery inserted in it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I have purchased this from flipkart , the picture clarity of this product is very low..for every snap i was like blur.10X zoom is no use since all the pics are not having the clarity. I really not happy with this model.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">First thanks to flipkart for delivering product within specified date.Let me come to the camera ,I'm writing review after using it for a week.Its a nice camera,perfect for family use. Pros *it has decent 10X zoom and it also has further 10X dynamic zoom,total 20X Zoom,with 20.1 mp clarity@rs 8k *Photos are amazing in day time. *It has vast customizing options while shooting.like skin softening Cons *Photos are not so good at night time(as it contains CCD image sensor,CCD is goot at day time,CMOS is good for low light shooting and night time). Totally a nice camera @ this price.Best in its class.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Nikon coolpix is good. But some time it takes more than a minute to get ready for a take. Quality camera display is very bad, but the photos are good when you see in a system.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">PROS: Light weight, handy, has many features to play around with snaps. Clarity is the best feature. Added benefits of free camera case and 4 GB SD card saved the trouble of hunting for them separately. CONS: Slow in processing pics after they are taken, needs around 3-4 seconds to finish recording the snap. Has auto-flash enabled by default on startup, need to disable it manually every time, as per need. Also, flash has only 2 options - auto and off. There is no on mode.  Overall, good product, small discrepancies that can be ignored.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Nikon's product always good .Also this budget this camera is best . And flipkart delivery is so good.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">User Friendly device. Excelent service by Flipkart. The Camera box was sealed at the time of delivery, which shows that the device is original. all the belongs in the box were sealed and not opened with a warranty card in it. GREAT</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Deadly slow processing while capturing photos. Display quality s not up to the mark. After taking one pic, it will tk again a mnit to process and to get ready for the next.  So moments will not wait till the camera get ready to capture it..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I am using it from delivery date, its just super. But the camera pouch not standard quality, very cheap & short in size.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">awesome product by nikon.looks great, lightweight, awesome clarity. nice battery backup. over all good thumbs up (y)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Type">Mechanical, CMOS Electronic Shutter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Speed in other Modes">4 sec (when Scene Mode is Set to Fireworks Show)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Connectivity Features">Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, I/O Terminal: Audio / Video (A/V) Output, Digital I/O (USB)</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">NTSC, PAL</specsKey>
<specsKey="Tripod Socket">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S6700</specsKey>
<specsKey="Processor">Expeed C2 Image-processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">20.48</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">20.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Movie (720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (480/30 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (480/25 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (240/30 fps: 320 x 240 (4:3)), (240/25 fps: 320 x 240 (4:3))</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5 - 45.0 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 25 - 200 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Focus Features">Focus Area Selecton: Face Priority, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Center, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF, Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 1200 mm, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Pre-flashes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Construction">10 Elements in 9 Groups</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus Range">50 cm (1 ft, 8 inch) - Infinity (W), 1.5 m (5 ft) - Infinity (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Single (Default Setting), Continuous (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 1.1 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 6, BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600 (Auto), ISO 3200 (Manual)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Scene Auto Selector, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">ISO Sensitivity (Auto): 0.5 - 3.5 m (W), 1.5 - 2.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">5 cm (2 inch) - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Temperature">0° C - 40° C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Humidity">85%</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering Modes">Matrix, Center-weighted (Digital Zoom less than 2x), Spot (Digital Zoom 2x or more)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish...View More

Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish, Swedish, Tamil, Telugu, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian, Vietnamese</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift (Still Pictures), Lens Shift and Electronic VR (Movies), Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Charging Time: 2 hr 40 min (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-70P and when No Charge Remains), Still Pictures: 230 Shots when Using EN-EL19, ...View More

Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift (Still Pictures), Lens Shift and Electronic VR (Movies), Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Charging Time: 2 hr 40 min (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-70P and when No Charge Remains), Still Pictures: 230 Shots when Using EN-EL19, Electronically Controlled ND Filter (-3.3 AV), Range: F3.5 - F11.1 Aperture 2 Steps, Movie Recording (Actual Battery Life for Recording): 50 min when Using EN-EL19, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode and Playback Mode): 98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Smile Timer Continuous Function</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">10x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Scene Auto Selector, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">3864 x 3864 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Megapixels">5152 x 3864 (20 M) (High), 5152 x 3864 (20 M) (Fine), 3648 x 2736 (10 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">File System: DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Still Image Size 16:9">5120 x 2880 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">JPEG Sound Files (Voice Memo), AVI (Motion JPEG Compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Aspect Ratio">16:9, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-70P AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">137 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">95.3 (W) x 58.2 (H) x 21.4 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">25 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Modes">Programmed AE</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Compensation">1/3 EV Steps +/- 2.0 EV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brightness Adjustment">5 Levels Brightness Adjustment</specsKey>
