<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l120-point-shoot-camera/p/itmcw25fqgyexkma?pid=CAMCW25FQGYEXKMA&otracker=from-search&srno=t_444&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2R%2BTe4mMa2VUZg5XQ4wgoq1jt2aRJ4Go5BZx3Gt9wX%2B4aLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=99155b2a-8655-453f-886f-08adb91eb056</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">265</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">83</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/k/m/a/nikon-coolpix-l120-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq8hyvtfgfm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">12974</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L120 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">If you are a beginer and are looking for a good camera with excellent zoom and great picture quality then this the camera. Its fully automated and extremely quick on reflex.  I spent a lot of time trying various models and makes of camera before settling for the L120. With such large zoom facilty it is essential the focus returns ASAP as soon as you stop zooming and doesnt just keep screeching back and forth to come to focus. Even at the max zoom it focuses within split seconds and does not make unnecessary noise or vibration. At 14 mega pixel the daytime pics are just too good. The clarity is mind blowing when zoom to full size.  The best part is the battery life. Simply put it is fantastic and since you use AAA battery very easy to get them every where. Unlike many other or my previous camera which has NiCd one and it is difficult to get since it is camera specific and the cost, less said teh better, the battery cost is 50% of the camera cost.  All said and done, for this price you wont get a better deal in my opinion. JUST GO FOR IT.You will love it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I got this camera 2 days back, undoubtedly after an extensive survey, and am surely loving it...!!! First and foremost... the tag line of 21x zoom really works well... specially amazing is the quick autofocus response even at maximum zoom. The clarity is very impressive... with the LCD screen showing you extremely vivid images. I even tried the ISO 1600 setting and strangely it gave good results despite some reviews against it.(although you need to place the camera on a surface or use a tripod to see what i am talking about.) I even tried the neat trick it has with the macro setting mentioned in some online professional reviews... and is impressive.  All in all... with the price tag it is undoubtedly the best point and shoot super zoom available. (after P500 if price is not a factor). Having used DSLRs of friends, I wanted something to capture the existing moments in all there refineness rather than creating a one!!  PS: Flipkart did an amazing job. They not only offered the best deal I could find but also shipped the product in a very neat packing. Plus, the customer support people are really co-operative. They delivered it in 1 1/2 days and even agreed to deliver it during a requested time slot.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">If you are planning to buy a camera which not only captures HD quality video but captures hardly audible sounds then Nikon Coolpix L120 is the best option. Its stereo sound is amazing which makes video more realistic with great audio quality.  External Flash : You can not differ a picture which is taken in complete darkness with flash turned on from a picture taken in day light. It has got an awesome external flash so that you do not have fear of darkness while clicking the moments !!!! I would suggest to buy this long lens camera with super zoom.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I know you all are aware of Flipkart's amazing service.. they delivered this camera at exactly 26th hour of placing the order, so lets just focus on the camera..  Point & Shoot cannot get any better than this one, auto focus is good, flash works nice, sturdy design, thumb rest & a grapple section helps taking blur free shots. Zoom is too much which you cannot easily find in any other camera in this section (you wont be able to handle it by hand, so might consider buying a tripod as well, I ordered slik compact II from flipkart). This is my second camera after Canon DSLR & I am honestly surprised by its performance. The battery system helped me a lot, I was gone on a mountaineering trip and couldnt find electricity but a shop offered AA size batteries which was a life saver. Moving on to technical specs, 14mp max to 640*480 vga min. you can take plenty of shots (559) in a 4 gb mem card provided free with it. Nikon battery charger also comes free & take around 4-5 hours to charge 4 AA batteries fully. but dont worry once full charged the batteries will work for ample time. Remember that this is not a handycam so video is not good compared to handycam but looking at the built & make, this one egts the job done quite nicely.. HD movies (720p) are nice if the lighting is good (flash, obviously cant be used while shooting a video). Various modes make it easy to take shots according to the need, one thing weird is that Panorama mode requires a computer to stitch.. but it doesnt matter that much. Also, its boot time is a bit long (4 seconds). Since i am a landscape & object photographer, the camera's macro mode & landscape modes perform their job good.  This camera is no doubt a keeper, I own 3 cameras & planning to buy a new one as well but I will always keep this one close to me.  In summary, final review:  Photo- 9.5 Video-7 Look-10 Durability-8 Ease of Access-9 Connectivity-10  Contact me on email if you want some sample shots</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Okay, so the thing is I wanted to buy a Camera for my parents' use. So obvisiouly it had to be a point and Shoot camera.  While researching at various sites and from various authors, this model of nikon came up everywhere, but I wasnt sure seeing the price of it. I mean, come on, they used to compare it with Nikon P5 which is 20k. So I was in doubt for it.  While buying a camera, my range was for Rs. 25k, so price wasnt a big matter, but after being recommended by everyone I went for this and I was surely shocked.  Its simply AMAZING. Fully automatic. Now this automatic feature can be disadvantageous for someone who is pro in photography, but for general users, like my parents, this is the best possible thing you can have. It has got various presets of settings like Portrait, Dawn, Fireworks, Musuem, Landscape, Night and plenty of this, so that you can just select them according to the situation and the camera puts everything accordingly. And the best of them is "Easy mode", you dont need to do anything, the camera looks at the subject and does everything.  Now some pros: 1. Flash is superb, no complain in that.  2. Red-eye removal amazing, i have clicked around 400 pics upto now but no problem faced yet.  3. Blink detection are a great aspect and is far better than other cameras upto the price of 18k.  4. There's an anti-shake feature, which reduces the impact of shake of your hands, which again is a great use for general users.  5. Optical Zoom. Most of the camera exaggerate their specs saying this much and that much zoom, but mind you this camera really surpasses all in zoom criteria. 21x optical zoom is far far better than any camera out there plus an additional 4x digital zoom, but digital zoom is not much required. The only camera which surpasses its zoom is Nikon P5, but again that is priced at 20k.  6. Display. Another thing which surely will catch your eyes is its display. Its display is phenomenal and would surely make you fall in love with it.  7. HD recording. You would have never expected a 720p video recording for a 13k camera, but mate, here you have. Though, due to large file size, you arent going to use 720p always, but keeping the deadly weapon in your stock, isnt bad at all.  8. Size and shape. Now here there may be contradictions, but I am a lover with dslrs, and its shape surely resembles them. Plus, unlike the other Point and shoot camera, its easy to hold, gives a firm grip while capturing and hence is surely perfect for general users.  9. Its got a high ISO value, which means you can take quick pictures with a slight time lag, which in a matter of fact is a great aspect which most of the people often ignores and hence its a great catch here also.  Now some CONS:  1. First and most disappointing thing, which always irritates me while using this is its Manual Flash, yes. There's a button, which you have to click to raise the flash lite and after that only you can use the awesome flash. But doing this always becomes a pain.  2. Second, its lens cover. Again, unlike other cameras of its range, it has got a manual lens cover, means before snapping you have to remove the lens cover, take the photo and then again put the lens cover. So again its frustrating.  3. Its really heavy and since you cant keep it in your pocket, either you have to hang it in your neck or keep in hand, so for long use, its really not made for that.  Conclusion:  So we have seen its cos and pros. It has got tremendous pros which surely surpasses any camera near it. Its cos are because of its physical body and some manual work. But seeing all those plus factors in it, I think these useless cos can be easily neglected as there is no drawback in the system.  So on a whole, its a perfect camera for general users, advanced users, who want to customize all settings on their own can skip this and go for any high range camera. But this a superb camera seeing its performance and price and will surely shock you after its use.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Since we have planned an Europe tour so i was looking for a camera which is easy to handle and has high optical zoom with high picture quality and finally i purchased nikon coolpix L120. And as expected, it fulfilled all my expectations and we were amazed by the result. This camera has made our tour memorable by great results. The best camera in its range.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Only buy if u are looking for optical zoom, video and battery life....  There are many cams in this price range which provides better picture quality at higher iso's (the ones with CMOS sensors)  Dont be attracted by the 21x zoom....u will rarely use it..it's just for showoff....the picture quality detiorates when u use the max zoom as the aperture size decreases..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I bought this camera just few days back, and totally disappointed with the performance of this camera. I bought this camera after reading all the good reviews about this camera.  But this camera image quality is below par, All the pictures we have taken are below par (even my broken 8MP cannon camera outperforms this one)  I will recommend this camera to anyone besides I am wondering if reviews in Flipkart is rigged ? because anyone with atleast some sense of photography would not rate this above 2.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">This camera is a steel for its price.  Pros: Image Clarity. Super Zoom. Zoom button on the lens.  Cons: No Manual Mode ( I knew this before buying). No viewfinder ( Might be a little difficult for SLR Users). Modes are a bit confusing.  If you are looking for a Super Zoom , Super Clarity Point and shoot ( with Gr8 Value) camera look no further.  If you are looking for a Typical bridge may I suggest LUMIX DMC FZ100... Else if you wa</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">this camera is worth its price.. sexy look.... easy to use.... great performance.... excellent battery backup..... the most exciting feature its 21X ZOOOOOOOOOM.......its really awesome..........</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">4 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5-94.5mm / F3.1-5.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">21x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">431 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">109.9 (W) x 76.5 (H) x 78.4 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">640 x 480</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera, Camera Strap AN-CP22, LR6/L40 (AA-size) Alkaline Batteries, USB Cable UC-E6, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, Lens Cap LC-CP22, View NX 2 CD, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">Coolpix L120</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto Auto with red-eye reduction Flash Off Fill flash Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 0.7 fps up to 19 shots</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto (auto gain ISO 80-800) Sports continuous mode (ISO 400 to 3200) Manual selection: ISO 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200, 6400</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene modes Easy auto mode, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Sports continuous</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">HDMI Min Connector</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256 Segment Matrix Metering, Center Weighted Metering, Spot Metering</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4320 x 3240</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene modes Easy auto mode, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Sports continuous</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV Movie</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">4 AC Adaptor EH-67 (Optional)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">102 MB</specsKey>
