<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s4400-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdjbqr2j85bfjw?pid=CAMDJF5HBK7GACFS&otracker=from-search&srno=t_80&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0K6oC%2FG7GrXB8fn2fMrKivX%2BjoSS7piIf7SqU2aIR0MIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=2cfb7aa5-8298-4336-8579-fa81e4789b0e</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.2</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">52</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">17</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/c/f/s/nikon-coolpix-s4400-point-shoot-400x400-imadjf5rasnz9gte.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">7700</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S4400 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">nice one, simply superb,worth for the money delivery of the flipkart is really fast and appreciable compare to others</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I buyed this camrea on discouned price Rs.5500/- As the same is available in local market due to absolute of this model. afte a month battery goes faulty and service center refused to replace the battery as they specified batteries are not covered under warranty . Very bad service policy. Dont Buy Nikon Cameras buy Olympus , Canon Fujifil m etc</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">product is good but when we click pic it will get 4 to 5 second to take another pic . and it also touch screen so we will not much comfort with it . all over it average product</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Processing of this camera is obviously slow as it takes 5 to 8 seconds to get ready for another shot. Also it has another disadvantage that it can not shoots a video more than 8 minutes in a single shot. I mean long videos recording cannot supported by this camera. Apart from above picture quality is good.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Hey Don't buy this product. Its very slow. It will take too much time between two pictures. Even if you zoom in or zoom out once u can not immediately zoom in and zoom out. You have to wait for 5 to 8 secs.. Not Good Don't Buy this....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">i'm using this camera from 2 months good one at this range. nearly 300 snaps fon one battery liked this camera. touch is good but not best</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">nice camera in this budget. 20mp gives u clear picture go for ittttttttttttttttttttttttttt nice camera in this budget. 20mp gives u clear picture go for ittttttttttttttttttttttttttt</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">It have all features almost like costly cameras. I like its touchscreen feature, work fast and smoothly. Video recording is good than other same price range cameras.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">This is the best you can have at this price. All things work very fine but one small defect is there.. unable to take good pic when exposed to too much of light at night ..Rest all i simply love it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">The camera doesn't give clear photos but stil have some good modes like sunset and sunrise modes...I would suggest a 16 mp camera with a good lens for those who are looking for good photos. .. the camera is below average but I got it with a free good hand watch (UCB), a 4GB memory card and a camera case in very good price about RS 5500/- ... so over all I can rate it as average. .</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, Charging AC Adapter EH-70P, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL19 (with Battery Case), ViewNX 2 CD-ROM, Reference Manual (CD-ROM), Stylus TP-1, USB Cable UC-E6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S4400</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">20.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Image Size: 3648 x 2736 (10 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 5120 x 2880 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 27.6 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 156 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600, ISO 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">26 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">20.48 Total Megapixel, Motion Blur Reduction Detection (Still Pictures), Focus Range: 50 cm (W), Touch Focus and Touch Click, Special Effects like Selective Colors, Fish-eye, Special FX and Filter Effects, Smart Portrait System, Subject Tracking, Intuitive Control, Elegant to the Touch, Ensuring Exc...View More

20.48 Total Megapixel, Motion Blur Reduction Detection (Still Pictures), Focus Range: 50 cm (W), Touch Focus and Touch Click, Special Effects like Selective Colors, Fish-eye, Special FX and Filter Effects, Smart Portrait System, Subject Tracking, Intuitive Control, Elegant to the Touch, Ensuring Excellent Image Quality Every Time, Special Effects and Filter Effects, EXPEED C2 Image-processing Engine, Smart Portrait System, Scene Auto Selector, Subject Tracking, Eye-Fi Card Support, Fish-eye</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">6x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">5152 x 3864 (20 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">140 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">95.5 (W) x 58.9 (H) x 20.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
