<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s3600-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdu5x47gttzzzs?pid=CAMDU5X4VFYZHQFQ&otracker=from-search&srno=t_30&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0GB9Na%2BO5VcNK%2BFTryf2EyAnVB2pwJGc2SrYo7cfIcKIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=70bfa3c3-0ea3-487e-ab2e-3a6bc8e08d03</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">3.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">122</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">29</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/q/f/q/nikon-coolpix-s3600-point-shoot-400x400-imadu6udtprads85.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">5560</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S3600 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Hi, after using this product for 2 Months I am writing my views.  First of Pro's: 1. Excellent quality (most important) in this price but be careful adjust focus gently.   it is really very tricky to adjust otherwise you will never get a good quality photo. 2. Good Battery Backup.  3. Very small and light weight.  4. Ruff and Tuff  5. Optical Zoom work perfactly.  Cons..: 1. Not a good grip (many times slip down from hands even still work)  2. Very difficult to adjust focus other wise it will give worst quality.  3. Some times flash light does not work wait 1 sec then capture again.  4. after push capture button it took 1 sec to capture image (should be quick response )  5. Only for day uses , in night flash does not give quality after 2 meter.  But in last it is really very good product with good quality. you can capture what you can not see by your eyes using optical zoom..   go for it..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I bought this camera last month and then i came to know that this is a failure model .    - The main issue is " Battery Exhausted" once you get the message you can't switch your camera again.   - It take too much time between shorts.   " Don't buy any Nikon Cameras"</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">This camera has helped me to take a lot of pictures. I would recommend this item to whoever wants to buy a camera. It has 20.1 mega pixels and other nice features.   - Praveena HR , A happy buyer.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I orderd this camera befor two days and i got it yesterday (in 1 day). Thanks for Quick service from flipkart.  Photo Quality: The Nikon S3600 is good for outdoor daytime photography. 8x zoom gives u power to shoot object from long distance. But i m not getting exact result after zooming as it is displays on screen before capturing pic. Photo is blurry and back shaded when zoom in . I dnt know if any special setting is required for this or not. Photo quality is good on normal setting (without zoom). Video qulity is 'Fine' . Overall photo quality is 'Good'.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">This camera has good specs. ur budget is 6-8k than go for this product. good looks and design and available in range of colours zoom keys r at the shutter key that very much useful Pouch and 4gb card provided that saves some bugs images are sharp and good pixels videos is 720p which is good  cons. Screen resolution is good but viewing angles r not good buttons at screen sides are not good (menu and other buttons wobbles)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">I orderd this camera befor two days and i got it yesterday (in 1 day). Thanks for Quick service from flipkart.  Photo Quality: The Nikon S3600 is good for outdoor daytime photography. 8x zoom gives u power to shoot object from long distance. But i m not getting exact result after zooming as it is displays on screen before capturing pic. Photo is blurry and back shaded when zoom in . I dnt know if any special setting is required for this or not. Photo quality is good on normal setting (without zoom). Video qulity is 'Fine' . Overall photo quality is 'Good'.  Camera size:  The size of S3600 is very compact by which you can carry it inside pant pocket same as mobile. Easy to handle and operate.   I got Scandisk 4 GB memory card, battery , Charger with USB cable, Software CD, Carry case with this.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">nice product and nice delivery by ws retail..image and video quality is good..good camera from nikon..worth purchase..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I have purchased this camera 2 weeks back and using it since the date of purchase...Its not worth for the money and meets below expectations. Its taking too long to capture and processing the images. I would strongly recommend to DO NOT buy this camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">The camera is amazing, if you get a long time to capture the photo, then set the scene mode to auto mode and increase the ISO, Default is 100(i think so), jump to 200... or more to get a snappier pic, but beware! More ISO means MORE GRAIN, so don't go more than 400, i really love this cam, got advanced options (NTSC/PAL, and setting ISO to 3600 and more) which gives you more control as how you Pic finally looks!  Happy taking photos ;-)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Nice Camrea in a tight budget, very handy and looks cool. Performance wise no problem till date after usagae of 4 months</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Type">Mechanical, CCD Electronic Shutter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shutter Speed in other Modes">4 sec (when Scene Mode is Set to Fireworks Show)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Connectivity Features">Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, I/O Terminal: Audio / Video (A/V) Output, Digital I/O (USB)</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">NTSC, PAL</specsKey>
<specsKey="Tripod Socket">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S3600</specsKey>
<specsKey="Processor">Expeed C2 Image-processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">20.48</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">20.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Movie (720/30 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (720/25 fps: 1280 x 720 (16:9)), (480/30 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (480/25 fps: 640 x 480 (4:3)), (240/30 fps: 320 x 240 (4:3)), (240/25 fps: 320 x 240 (4:3))</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5 - 36.0 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 25 - 200 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Focus Features">Focus Area Selecton: Face Priority, Center, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF, Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 800 mm, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Pre-flashes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Construction">8 Elements in 7 Groups</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus Range">50 cm (1 ft, 8 inch) - Infinity (W), 1.5 m (5 ft) - Infinity (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.7 - F6.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Single (Default Setting), Continuous (the Frame Rate for Continuous Shooting is 1.1 fps and the Maximum Number of Continuous Shots is 6, BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600 (Auto), ISO 3200 (Manual)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Scene Auto Selector, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">ISO Sensitivity (Auto): 0.5 - 3.5 m (W), 1.5 - 2.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">2 cm (0.8 inch) - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Temperature">0° C - 40° C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Humidity">85%</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering Modes">Matrix, Center-weighted (Digital Zoom less than 2x), Spot (Digital Zoom 2x or more)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish...View More

Arabic, Bengali, Bulgarian, Simplified Chinese, Chinese (Traditional), Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Hindi, Hungarian, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Marathi, Norwegian, Persian, Polish, Portuguese (European and Brazilian), Romanian, Russian, Serbian, Spanish, Swedish, Tamil, Telugu, Thai, Turkish, Ukrainian, Vietnamese</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">One Touch HD 720p Movie Recording, Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift (Still Pictures), Lens Shift and Electronic VR (Movies), Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Charging Time: 2 hr 50 min (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-70P and when No Charge Remains), Still Pictu...View More

One Touch HD 720p Movie Recording, Vibration Reduction: Lens Shift (Still Pictures), Lens Shift and Electronic VR (Movies), Motion Blur Reduction (Still Picture), Tripod Socket: 1/4 (ISO 1222), Charging Time: 2 hr 50 min (when Using Charging AC Adapter EH-70P and when No Charge Remains), Still Pictures: 230 Shots when Using EN-EL19, Electronically Controlled ND Filter (-3 AV), Range: F3.7 - F10.5 Aperture 2 Steps, Movie Recording (Actual Battery Life for Recording): 45 min (720/30 fps) when Using EN-EL19, 50 min (720/25 fps) when Using EN-EL19, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 97% Horizontal and 97% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 99% Horizontal and 99% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">8x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Scene Auto Selector, Scene (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">3864 x 3864 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Megapixels">5152 x 3864 (20 M) (High), 5152 x 3864 (20 M) (Fine), 3648 x 2736 (10 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">File System: DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF Compliant</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Still Image Size 16:9">5120 x 2880 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">JPEG Sound Files (Voice Memo), AVI (Motion JPEG Compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Aspect Ratio">16:9, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-70P AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">125 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">97.1 (W) x 57.9 (H) x 19.9 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">25 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Modes">Programmed AE</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Exposure Compensation">1/3 EV Steps +/- 2.0 EV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brightness Adjustment">5 Levels Brightness Adjustment</specsKey>
