<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s2800-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdtjghjwe3fvnu?pid=CAMDTJGGRYMUQE34&otracker=from-search&srno=t_3&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2%2Byjx98l3D0WWw4dS%2BgqyKautnMhR9XJKF9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">3.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">127</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">28</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/e/3/4/nikon-coolpix-s2800-point-shoot-400x400-imaeyxfasngfteqh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">4580</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S2800 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">This is just awesome. Its very pretty to see. I love its looks. My wife is very happy after getting this camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">i think it's best compact camera with greatest features at this price by nikon . it's pic quality is suberb as it's mega pixels. the only thing lacks is speed . it takes around 5 sec to save photo and also digital zoom is not far good. battery life is good if used rightway i.e 1 day continous photo doesnt drain complete battery.  so at all if you more concentrate on pic quality not on speed processing it the best digital camera under Rs 8000 .</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">good camera for those who never done photography its 20.1 MP camera gives you good picture quality and its flash helps you to shoot pictures in dark but there is one problem its auto mode sometimes does not work properly when there is no need of flash it flashes up.I get it for Rs.4700.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Slimmest body of a digicam ever sen till now, pictures are crispiest and look much more vivid and sharper when seen in an LED, Battery life is also good, overall a worthy buy.......</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Camera is good.But when i connect to the computer running Windows 7,it asks to download software from nikon servers.What a shame?Nikon cant even provide driver software on its cd. My previous sony handy cam and sony camera came with complete installation cd and it was a breeze installing the applications.  Nikon should improve and more over flipkart could put effort to verify the products before they sell.  Regarding camera,this is my first day and satisfied with performance.Have to wait and see and will write the detailed review after 4 weeks of use.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">This is one bad model and worst compact camera I have ever used... So slow and bad imagining... Macro mode is good for nothing.. Really disappointing... Budget camera is one thing but this model is ridiculous</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">This camera is not useful even for small home purpose or personal use. Picture quality is very poor.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Its 2nd order on Flipkart & again they deliver fastly. Camera condition is excellent. tested good shots. 8gb sd card & pouch as mentioned in the offer. My firstever point & shoot camera In 4600 Rs. Thanks Flipkart After 1 week use i have to tell u that if u select highest pixel setting which is starred its result in only increase in size of your snaps select some lowest setting like unstarred 20 MP setting. it give u 5mb (approx) of snaps size. Overall experience with camera is good. Best in daylight condition. You do not expect much in this range of P&S camera. like it will rock in low light. Image is good in low light but u hav tobe prep 4 that. Thank you.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Pics quality is rally very good....a bit slow otherwise a very good buy at this price. hassle free just point & shoot....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">I have bought this camera to gift my friend on his Wedding. Flipkart delivery is 5 out of 5 again. But not very happy with Camera.  Camera is compact and easy to handle, but still looks stylish. Easy menu and you just need to point and shoot. Come with 8 GB memory card and camera pouch. so no need to purchase any thing extra.  But pictures are not so good as compare to other Nikon product. Images getting burl with very little motion/shake of your hand. Very hard to click clear piture as we are not profeshional photographer. You either need tripod and need to put on table for still and clear photos. In room lights image are not very clear.  Regards, Vikas Shrestha</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S2800</specsKey>
<specsKey="Processor">Expeed C2 Image-processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">EN-EL19 Rechargeable Li-ion Battery, USB Cable, Camera Strap, ViewNX 2 CD, EH-70P Charging AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600 (Auto), ISO 3200 (Manual)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">10 cm - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">One Touch HD 720p Movie Recording, Battery Life of Still Shooting: 250 Shots with EN-EL19 Battery, Electronic Vibration Reduction (Movies), Motion Blur Reduction: Motion Detection (Still Pictures), Advanced Glamour Retouch, Special Effects and Quick Effects, Easy-to-use Design, Scene Auto Selector, ...View More

One Touch HD 720p Movie Recording, Battery Life of Still Shooting: 250 Shots with EN-EL19 Battery, Electronic Vibration Reduction (Movies), Motion Blur Reduction: Motion Detection (Still Pictures), Advanced Glamour Retouch, Special Effects and Quick Effects, Easy-to-use Design, Scene Auto Selector, Target Finding Autofocus, Smart Portrait System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 23.0 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 26 - 130 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Focus Features">Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 520 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus Range">50 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">20.48</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">20.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">3864 x 3864 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Megapixels">5152 x 3864 (20 M (High)), 5152 x 3864 (20 M), 3648 x 2736 (10 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Still Image Size 16:9">5120 x 2880 (14 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">5x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-70P AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">120 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">93.8 (W) x 58.4 (H) x 19.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
