<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-1-j1-mirrorless-camera/p/itmdv58ergkctghz?pid=CAMD7BPYZCMGCUFN&otracker=from-search&srno=t_275&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2P42511dlrhX9orNyeewX%2F%2FlDOjrKbYsXnGkxu9FQsNIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=8531cd2f-10cf-4074-a34b-6793a7ed5459</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">12</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/u/f/n/nikon-1-j1-point-shoot-400x400-imad7bpbfftrec4r.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">23204</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon 1 J1 Mirrorless Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Mirrorless</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/16000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">1 J1</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL20, Battery Charger MH-27, USB Cable UC-E15, Body Cap BF-N1000, Strap AN-N1000, ViewNX 2/Short Movie Creator CD, User's Manual, Reference manual CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Fill Flash, Slow Sync, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain Sync, Rear Curtain with Slow Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F5.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Dust Shield Glass</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">2.7x Lens Focal Length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted 4.5 mm Circle in Center of Frame, Spot 2 mm Circle Centered on Selected Focus Area</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 5 frames per second 10, 30 or 60 fps using Electronic (Hi) shutter</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto ISO (ISO 100 - 3200, 100 - 800, 100 - 400)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Still image (3:2), Smart Photo Selector (3:2), Movie (HD 16:9, Slow Motion 8:3), Motion Snapshot (16:9)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual, All except Preset Manual with Fine Tuning</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C Mini-pin HDMI Connector</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Total Pixel: 12 megapixels, Playback Function, Focus Lock, Exposure Control, i-TTL Flash Control using Image Sensor, Remote Control, Motion Snapshot, Smart Photo Selector Mode, Slow Motion Movie 400 fps 640x240, 1200 fps 320x120, Dial Mode, Nikon 1 Mount, Picture Control System, Electronic Shutter, ...View More

Total Pixel: 12 megapixels, Playback Function, Focus Lock, Exposure Control, i-TTL Flash Control using Image Sensor, Remote Control, Motion Snapshot, Smart Photo Selector Mode, Slow Motion Movie 400 fps 640x240, 1200 fps 320x120, Dial Mode, Nikon 1 Mount, Picture Control System, Electronic Shutter, Shutter Release Mode, Exposure Lock, Exposure Compensation: 3EV in increments of 1/3 EV Steps, Active D-Lighting, Lens Servo, Face-priority AF, Flash Compensation: 3EV in increments of 1/3 EV Steps, Recording Time: 1080/60i (20 minutes), 1080/30p (20 minutes), 720/60p (29 minutes), Tripod Socket: 1/4 inch at ISO 1222, Operating Temperature: 0-40Deg C, Humidity Less than 85%, Battery Life (Shots per Charge): up to 230 Shots (CIPA) and 70 Mins of HD Footage at 1080/60i, CX Image Sensor Format, Still Images (Still Image and Smart Photo Selector Modes, Aspect Ratio 3:2) 3872 x 2592, 2896 x 1944, 1936 x 1296, Still Images (Movie Mode, Aspect Ratio 16:9) 3840 x 2160 (1080, 60i) 1920 x 1080 (1080, 30p), 1280 x 720 (720, 60p), Still Images (Motion Snapshot Mode, Aspect Ratio 16:9) 3840 x 2160, 1 SD Card Slot, Flash Sync Speed: Up to 1/60 sec, Frame Advance Rate, Scene Modes: Portrait, Landscape, Night Portrait, Close-up, Auto, Flash-ready Indicator, Movie Metering: TTL Exposure Metering using Main Image Sensor, Date, Time and Daylight Savings Time Settings</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">1 NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Hybrid Autofocus (Phase Detection / Contrast Detect AF)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">10 - 30 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 27 - 81 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">10.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">3872 x 2592 (3:2)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Still image (3:2), Smart Photo Selector (3:2), Movie (HD 16:9, Slow Motion 8:3), Motion Snapshot (16:9)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (RAW) 12-bit, Compressed JPEG: JPEG Baseline Compliant with Fine (1:4), Normal (1:8), Basic (1:16) Compression NEF (RAW) + JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">AAC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4, AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter, Requires EP-5C Power Connector (Sold Separately)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">EN-EL20 Li-ion Rechargeable Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">234 g (Camera Body Only), 277 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Body Cap)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">106 (W) x 61 (H) x 29.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Operating System">Windows XP SP3, Windows Vista SP2, Windows 7 SP1, Apple MAC OS X 10.5.8 - 10.6.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">LCD Monitor with Protection Glass and Wide Viewing Angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">3:2, 16:9</specsKey>
