<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d3100-with-af-s-18-55-mm-vr-kit-nikkor-50-f-1-8g-le-dslr-camera/p/itmdvqmykaguh932?pid=CAMDTAKFZRGSWXCM&otracker=from-search&srno=t_194&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0X5r%2FMkDXvKOnJYvdU5E9rV0LK2g97%2Fu4wwuee1eVqBYaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=5c320a3f-774a-47ac-acd4-f227d67597ff</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">425</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">97</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/x/c/m/nikon-d3100-with-af-s-18-55-mm-vr-kit-af-s-nikkor-50-mm-f-1-8g-400x400-imadte39ckngnhw6.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">34980</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D3100 (with AF-S 18 - 55 mm VR Kit + AF-S NIKKOR 50 mm F/1.8G Le DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Zooming? we are talking about a DSLR here, not a tiny sensor P&S camera. If you don't know what you are talking about, don't make such stupid, joke of the 21st century comments. DSLR doesn't deal in Number X zoom, it uses the term focal length to specify its reach, the 18-55mm lens that comes with a d3100 is a decent lens, if you need to take faraway stuff you have to buy a telephoto lens, ask any real photographer, photography is not about zooming, they zoom with their legs, many of them opt "primes" (un zoomable) for the superior quality of glass.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Lets begin! Nikon , one of the best camera makers -- we all know right. Again the company has done it with D3100. If you are a regular digital camera user and buying this as you first DSLR you will fall in love with it at first look (really). The basics; You can get the specs from any where you want so i am not wasting in writing it. Still, i will have a say about the image sensor size which is the heart of any camera and trust me this has a golden heart. If you wish to know the conversion of sensor size and 35mm comparison it is provided in the manual. Taking further the sensor is CMOS , a better variant than the D3000 which has a CCD sensor. Dont go in detail just know that CMOS is better in comparison. The build of the camera--9/10 Holding position -- very good . you feel confident when you hold it. Like it will nor slip out out. Dial and back panel buttons -- good position and quick access function. Lens - Fair enough for starters and VR -- AF does the job really well. Lack of zoom (if somebody want it).  Taking photos: As easy as a DSLR can get is the auto mode and guide mode. Although the guide mode a little boring but still good and must have for starters. Without much hassle you can get great photos. The manual mode is very expansive. you can make almost any change to the settings you want. Stick to the basics and go on step by step , like first setting the aperture only , and then exposure etc and you are in the way of being a pro soon. Now about the accessories:  Battery-- charges very fast and lasts long. Memory-- go for any size you like it depending on how much you shoot. Rest of the accessories are standard as the data cables, HDMi cables etc are sufficient. The ferrite cores provided are very useful put it on any data cable you are planning to use.  Okay guys i hope you will find it somewhat useful. If you want more please comment. Last verdict : Buy it if it fits your budget and wish to use a DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">I am impressed .This is my first DSLR and I am loving it. First thing I should tell here so many ppl has mentioned very constructive comments in the review. Before buying this DSLR I was pretty confused on which one to buy say in my list  Nikon D3100 Canon 1100D Canon 550D Nikon D5100  But I dont have lots of money per se. After doing so much research I opted for Nikon D3100 coz the gripping was so good in my hand than any others.  I have tried Canon 550D too ... it is a good camera to be very frank. But if u think carefully I would suggest to buy the Nikon D3100 body with a prime lense either 50mm 1.8G or 35 mm 1.8G , Nikkor offcourse.  I ma using this camera for more than 3 months, no problem found whatsover and I ma very satisfied.  But it might seem that the image is bit natural in ur DSLR, I have trick for u , if u check Canon 550D it will provide u much saturated color more vibrant than Nikon D3100. So make ur camera setting color as vivid and increase the saturation manually from the menu.  U wont regret this buy . Trust me.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Only Nikon AF-S lenses will auto focus on D3100. Nikon chose to not put a focusing motor in the D3000, D3100, D5000 and D5100 so you'd have to buy the more expensive AF-S lenses that have a focusing motor in the lens. The Nikon AF 50mm f1.8D is about $140.00 while the new Nikon AF-S 50mm f1.8G is about $220.00 - a nice extra $80.00 or thereabouts in profit for Nikon.  If you use the AF 50mm f1.8D on your D3100 you will have to manually focus the lens. It will not auto focus on your camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Purchased this about 3 weeks back, and am amazed at its performance: - My decision to buy Nikon D3100 v/s Canon 1100D was not bad. Though more expensive, the feel in hand, compactness, sensor size, HD movies capability, 3" dispalay, rubber grip tilted my decision towards Nikon. - excellent image quality & low noise at 14MP, even with flash. - Kit lens has its limitations, but ok for me to begin with experimenting. - I manual focusing for macro / close up shots much better than autofocus. - The HD video mode delivers excellent quality movies.  - The built in flash looks small, but has enough power to take good snaps at indoor functions. I recently took more than 150 photos at my niece's wedding, and the result was great. - I prefer to shoot in A (aperture priority) or Manual M mode. - I plan to buy a 50mm stand alone lens followed by 55 - 300 zoom. - In short, go for Nikon D3100!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Your Review was a good one, but have little inaccuracies, i too have been using this DSLR for 18 months with sb 400 flash and i bought it for 28500 then. The thing is that it can continuously auto focus while video recording and been one of the first entry level SLR to do so. The problem with video recording is that, it can only shoot 1080p at 24fps. While many other entry level SLR's can do it at 30 fps. The continuous auto focus can cause noise in the video which is a drawback.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Its been 8 months im using it n im totally happy with this camera. Has all the feature that you might expect from a camera. The 18-55mm lens which come with the camera is good for general purpose use but it wont be long before you start feeling its limited zooming ability. So, be ready to buy a zoom lens soon.  It has good battery backup, user friendly ,easy to operate. the most recommended product if you are thinking to move from your point n shoot to SLR..Its the best in its range..for sure!!  Last thing for general users (people who just want a good camera). I see SLRs these days in everybodies hand because it has gone cheap. You can afford it doesn't mean you should buy it. SLRs are those people want spend lot of time in photography. People who want good camera for their family trip should go for point n shoot. there are some really good PnP in the market, look for it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I've been researching on several entry level DSLR's (Canon 1100D, Sony SLT A35 to name a couple) since over a few months and finally narrowed on this marvel. Reasons to go for this and not the others are:  A: Slightly larger sensor size. B: More megapixels (I know it doesn't really matter but helps if you're to crop your shots). C: Higher ISO capabilities. D: Overall better value for buck.  Review: On first use it really does not feel like an entry level DSLR at all. As a matter of fact, Even when compared with higher end's like the D90, not a lot of difference can be observed (Tested with the same 50mm AF-S lens). If you are a beginner into professional photography, the Guide or Full auto mode can do wonders. However, the full potential of this beast can be felt under the Full manual mode. I've read several opinions on how this one cannot keep the shots distortion free on lower shutter speeds but, personally, I've tested it while in my car with considerable amount of vibration and with very low shutter speeds, and it was unbelievably stable and shots were great. I'm talking about using with the kit 18-55 lens here. It'd be way better with a prime or telephoto. Additionally, worrying about lack of juice is also a no no with this beast. With full charge, it lasted for more than a day with about 430 RAW / 500 JPEG shots.  Overall, its a beautiful piece of hardware to have for any photographer. Especially if you are a beginner, this would serve as the wand for a wizard !</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I have done lots of research, I am confused between D3200, D5100, canon 600D and sony a58, but all of them little expensive and I get this on Flipkart @21k. Its a too good a deal to miss and now I can spend my money to buy some lenses. If you are new to DSLR photography it will give you enough satisfaction.   Hats off to flipkart. mind blowing service. they deliver me within 2 days.  Downside of this camera is that it is launched in 2010 and also the screen's resolution is poor and it doesn't have built-in focus motor unlike Canon's so you have to buy the lenses that have focus motor built in and they cost you more.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Summary: Great starter to DSLR for beginners like me  Easy to learn photography with this camera Excellent performance for the price Will recommend a tripod (if you are very serious about photography/night shots)  I have been shooting using my point & shoot camera till date and wanted to upgrade to a better camera. At the same time I was intimidated by the myriad terms and features associated with a SLR. After due research, I had ordered this gem of a camera on Flipkart and got it delivered a month ago.   First mention is about how easy it is to use the camera and the additional flyer materials that came with the camera. The flyer contained easy set up guide to get you started with the camera without having to read the entire manual. On the camera as well you have guide mode which makes your life a breeze when it comes to taking photos. It has easy suggestions and 'how to' for th day to day usage scenarios and hence helps you to learn photography rather than use the auto mode.   Secondly the performance has been phenomenal and the battery life has been way better than what I had feared it will be. It also has sensors to detect light and it warns you if the subject is too dark or too bright prompting you to change exposure or shutter speed. If you are a person inclined to learn photography then you will use these hints and the light in the room to update your brain and learn yourself.  Only downside (which is actually not a downside for this price) is the performance under low light. You need to have incredibly steady hands or a tripod to take night portraits to avoid blurry images.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL14, Camera Body, AF-S 18-55mm VR Kit Lens, Body Cap BF-1B, User Manual, Rubber Eyecup DK-20, Quick Charger MH-24, Camera Strap AN-DC3, 2 Ferrite Core, USB cable, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, View NX 2 CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D3100 (with AF-S 18 - 55 mm VR Kit + AF-S NIKKOR 50 mm F/1.8G Le</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Red-Eye, Slow, Red-Eye Slow, Rear curtain</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">14.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">3456 x 2304, 2304 x 1536</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection by Nikon Multi-CAM 1000 autofocus module with AF-assist (range Approx. 0.5-3m), 11 focus point; Detection range: -1 to EV (ISO 100 at 20C/68F),</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">18 - 55 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">3D color matrix metering (type G and D lenses, color matrix metering II (other CPU lenses), Center-weighted (weight given to 8-mm circle in center of frame), Spot metering (meters 3.5-mm circle centered on selected focus point)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Continuous shooting mode: Approx. 3fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (12800 with boost)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white-balance with 420-pixel RGB sensor) Incandescent Fluorescent Direct sunlight Flash Cloudy Shade White balance preset</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">20</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Operating Temperature: 0Deg - 40Deg C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3072 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (12 bit compressed RAW) JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV movie (H.264/MPEG-4 compression format with monaural sound)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter (Available Separately; Requires Optional EP-5A Power Connector)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">455 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">124 (W) x 96 (H) x 74.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Eye-level penta-Dach mirror type; built-in diopter adjustment (-1.7 to .5m-1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Eye-level penta-Dach mirror type; built-in diopter adjustment (-1.7 to .5m-1)</specsKey>
