<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d300s-dslr-camera/p/itmczc2gq9ztyv3t?pid=CAMCVYDJSX8G78HZ&otracker=from-search&srno=t_186&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3VnYlBnf343Bb7Hpsxl0apwNwYjJG2AwQwwuee1eVqBYaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=5c320a3f-774a-47ac-acd4-f227d67597ff</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">11</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/8/h/z/nikon-d300s-slr-400x400-imacxmk97ghrp2pq.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">79004</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D300s DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/8000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 Sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Body, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL3e, Quick Charger MH-18a, USB Cable UC-E4, Video Cable EG-D2, Strap AN-DC4, LCD monitor cover BM-8, Body cap, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Rubber Eyecup DK-23, Software Suite CD-ROM, Power Cable, Accessory shoe cover BS-1</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D300s</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Front curtain, Rear curtain, Red-Eye, Slow, Red-Eye Slow</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">12.3 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">3216 x 2136, 2144 x 1424</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection, 51 focus points (15 cross-type sensors) by Nikon Multi-CAM 3500DX autofocus module; Detection -1 to EV (ISO 100 at 20C/68F)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">3D-Color Matrix Metering II (type G and D lenses); Color Matrix Metering II (other CPU lenses); Color Matrix Metering (non-CPU lenses if user provides lens data), Center-weighted: Weight of 75% given to 8 mm circle in center of frame; Diameter of circle can be changed to 6, 10, or 13 mm, or weightin...View More

3D-Color Matrix Metering II (type G and D lenses); Color Matrix Metering II (other CPU lenses); Color Matrix Metering (non-CPU lenses if user provides lens data), Center-weighted: Weight of 75% given to 8 mm circle in center of frame; Diameter of circle can be changed to 6, 10, or 13 mm, or weighting can be based on average of entire frame (fixed at 8 mm when non-CPU lens is used), Spot: Meters 3.0 mm circle (about 2% of frame) centered on selected focus point (on center focus area when non-CPU lens is used)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">1/200 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Continous low shooting mode: 1-7fps, Continous high shooting mode: 7fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">200 - 3200 in 1, 1/2 or 1/3 EV steps (100 - 6400 with boost)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white balance with 1,005-pixel RGB sensor); Incandescent, Fluorescent, Direct sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Choose Color temp., White balance preset</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">17</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4288 X 2848</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous shooting mode: approx. 3fps, Self-timer mode, Quiet Shutter Release</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (12 or 14-bit lossless compressed, compressed, or uncompressed RAW), TIFF (RGB), JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">AVI movie</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter (Optional)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">840 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">147 (W) x 114 (H) x 74 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">CompactFlash (CF) Card (Type I, compliant with UDMA); SD memory card (SDHC compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-2.0 to .0 m-)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-2.0 to .0 m-)</specsKey>
