<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-p520-advanced-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdhwhazazfhu6r?pid=CAMDHWH7CCFZHJTW&otracker=from-search&srno=t_397&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2Clb1TDts8y%2Fqzem932CeARwI9WfHKG1PSJKOpfHVjoIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=e824cc8c-17db-49de-ba96-24b339c84fe0</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">197</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">83</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/j/t/w/nikon-coolpix-p520-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadhwh7wkevwnqg.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">21500</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix P520 Advanced Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Advanced Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I bought this cam from flipkart for 17.4k.... .. The price has soared up since then,...So, I consider my deal as 100% value for money.   Pros: 1: 42x zoom. (There are zoom test videos in youtube... Check it out and you'll b surprised to see what this cam has in it) 2: HD video: Amazing quality for videos 3. Screen: The screen can be tilted to any angle you like... Very useful while taking ground level pics... 4: Sturdy built: The body looks n feels strong. It has a nice grip .  5: Decent pic quality: The max size f image is 8-9MB on 18MP FINE...The image data is quite small when compared to DSLR(15MB min). Noise level is moderate. Don't expect pic quality of DSLR though.  6. Battery : Lasts for about 300 shots.. It is better to carry a spare battery though. U just need to spend an extra 1000 for it. 7. Viewfinder: Very useful if u plan to take lots of pic in one go. Saves up lots of juice!!  8. Manual focusing : It is a delight to take pics on dis cam in manual mode. Please don't buy this cam if u plan to use auto mode... Its just a waste of money for auto mode. A 5000rs point and shoot cam cud easily do that for you.  9: GPS: Though I've not used this feature yet, it seems to be a pretty good addon for ur cam. Quite useful while exploring unknown places. GPS helps u to GEO TAG the pics. Dont think that i offers navigation n all... It just stores the position of the place where the pic was taken. If turned on, battery consumption would obviously increase. 10: Scene modes: Though I dont like auto mode, just for the sake of adding a good point about this cam, u can say that u have a wide range of scene modes to choose from on this cam. 11: CHEAP: Its not the best bridge cam in the market. But for 17.5k, this one is a steal-deal! For alternatives, u cud look at Sony hx300, canon sx50....but, u gotta pay 22k+ for sony and 26k+ for canon.. It is not worth the premium ! Image quality is almost the same... Sony and Canon has got faster zoom speeds and better autofocussing though...   Cons: 1. Autofocus: Manual focus is the best. But, for the ones who doesnt like all those stuff like fiddling with the controls, autofocus is the only way out. I felt that the delay to focus on to a subject is a little more when compared to other cams in the same class. If u are taking pics on manual mode, dont consider this as a reason for not buying this cam. Remember that if u want to take good pics, it must be you and not a software which controls the cam!! 2: Flash: Flash compensation feature is available. But, the performance f the flash is not upto the mark... But, it is still better that most other bridge cams available. Remember that u cant use this flash like the pros use it on their cams.. Bouncer cant be fixed. So, you'll probably get a high burst of light on the subj just like normal cams.   These are the only 2 probs I faced on this cam until now.. I've taken only abt 1000 pics using this cam..I am really happy with the nikon product...  So here is my final verdict: If u r a person looking for a camera for 20000 to 23000 range, Nikon P520 is ur best option. If u are a person who wants to buy a camera which has almost all the features of a DSLR but, dont want to or have enough money to spend exta cash on lens, Nikon P520 is a good option And If u r a beginner and wants to kickstart photography as a hobby, P520 is the one you shud go for!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">This is an excellent camera for the price (which I payed). Its features superior to almost all other point-and-shoots in its price range: Wi-fi capable (ability to connect to smart phones for viewing/sharing your photos and videos via the optional WU-1a adapter), built-in GPS, 18MP CMOS sensor, a zoom lens with incredible focal range (24mm-1,000mm), and 1080 HD video. For the price, that's a nice set-up, a camera with advanced features with an excellent ease-of-use, requiring little knowledge of photographic techniques. But yes, I wish the P520 had a few more pro-like features but this is an excellent - almost but not quite great - camera. However, if you're someone not interested in advanced photography and just want a very nice camera with higher-end consumer features, this is a 5-star camera.   One additional thing, I was able to get the same camera (plus usual stuff) for 10% less from another online store. I, being a long time flipkart customer, think it needs to up its game, especially regarding their product pricing.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">I got this one after a detailed survey of bridge cameras as well as simple long zoom point and shoot cameras from Nikon, Canon and Sony (I personally don't prefer other brands, even though they may be cheaper).  Luckily, the day I was about to order, Flipkart slashed the price to 19.5k for a narrow window of 3 hours or so :) Later, I used the extra 2000 for a 16 GB class 10 memory card, a Lens cleaner, and a tripod. I got the lens cleaner and the memory card delivered today - still waiting for the tripod.....  Coming to the camera, I feel it serves my purpose more than enough. It has all the things u need in a camera to grow as a photographer - auto>programmed>manual :)  If u want to buy an SLR, go for it. The price difference is not much. I certainly would have, but honestly, I do not rate myself high enough, as a photographer, to buy an SLR right now. I will surely buy one as and when I feel I am worthy enough to hold - not just for posing in a profile picture in some social networking site.....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I just brought this camera this diwali and I just love it. I have nikon D3100 with 18-55mm kit lens, 55-300mm telephoto zoom lens and a 50mm fixed focus lens. I am writing this review with reference to this camera. Starting with view finder, if you just ignore it, it just give a feel of DSLR. You cant off the LCD and use the view finder. If you use the camera without flipping out the LCD, every thing that is displayed in LCD will be displayed in the view finder. Its 42x zoom is equivalent to 28-1000 mm zoom lens which works great. Every one knows the cost of a 1000mm nikkor lens. You will love its HDR imaging( none in d3100), but you cant access the exposer settings for it. It's tilt screen(not avilable in d3100) is helpful in making videos from different angles, but all the photo you take seems granular. But it's ok as it is only LCD screen problem. It's command dial enable user to customize(can't do in d3100) his/ her shooting preference like a DSLR. It is packed with huge number of settings you can use. Battery is not sufficient after full charging to take more than 170-180 photos(D3100 takes 300 photos approx). Over all it is a value of money and worth buying.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">First of all, lets be honest, if you are someone who is into photography for a long time, you would definitely go for a DSLR! I'm a newbie, trying to develop my photography skills. My basic needs were to get good pictures in almost all conditions and occasions without having to splurge loads of money.So a 'Point and shoot' was more than sufficient.  Although the megapixel count is not essentially the deciding factor to obtain great pictures, the 18.1 megapixels on this one guarantee a great shot even at higher zooms. The controls are easy to understand and the camera is compact enough to capture your precious moments with ease! The rechargeable Li-ion battery ensures about 300-350 shots in single charge, so nothing to complain about the battery. Rest all features are similar to any standard camera.  It makes a smart decision to buy this camera if you are not willing to spend more for a DSLR. With a little research on the aperture and ISO settings, F-stop and exposure levels, you can take amazing pictures almost similar to a DSLR. I would recommend to use the Manual mode or Aperture priority mode to get the maximum outputs rather than relying on Auto modes. It is disheartening to see people buying expensive cameras loaded with features and using Auto mode only!   A really worth buying product! Got it for under 18k (inclusive of 2 yrs Nikon warranty, 4 GB memory card, Camera case, HDMI cable). Highly recommended for enthusiasts low on budget but eager to explore the joys of photography, rather than merely posing with a camera in their profile picture! :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Worth the money and buy. Colour is much better than the usual black ones. Point and shoot are better than other cans. 42 x zoom is the best thing</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Great camera only drawback is you need a tripod or extremely steady hands to get good shots after zooming beyond 30X</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I bought this camera in June last year. Since then I have been using it extensively. Here are a few few things I liked and didnÂ´t like about the camera.  Pros:  1. ZOOM. This is most probably the best feature available in this camera. The 42X lets you get really close to the subject. Yea it does have some little focus limitations but overall its really good. 2. Tilt-able display. You can click any angle using it. It even makes selfies so much fun(I usually use my tripod for that) 3. Zoom Speed: It lets you get really close really fast although in video mode its comparitively slow but thats for a good reason. 4. Manual Settings. Although it doesnÂ´t give you as many options as a pro DSLR but its as good as the entry level ones. Personally I chose it over them. Not because of my budget constraint but considering its qualities.  Some CONS: 1. Small Sensor: Daylight pics are quite good; even in full zoom mode but when it comes to shooting in dim light or flourescent bulb, itÂ´s a bit of a disappointment. 2. Unrealistic exposure in dim light. In dim light it automatically enhances the exposure and hence brightens the photo. It can really be a turn off some times. 3. Battery backup. Although under full battery it can last for a day of clicking but still it has a shortcoming there when compared to other bridge cameras. 4. Focus speed. It takes a bit time to focus automatically(In dim light mostly). In some situations that can be really annoying. 5. It takes a little time to get adjusted to clicking in dimly lit scenes but once you do, it can really make you get clicking on and on. 6. Poor image quality: Even though set on FINE and 18MP, it fails to give an extra crispy image, especially when cropped. Even a 2x crop can ruin the image quality.  Overall. Its a nice camera. For someone who is just learning to shoot with manual controls, it really is a good device. I mostly get time to shoot in the evening time so that is why i have so many problems with the low light sensitivity. If you are a day time photographer and want to capture natures beauty, it really stands up to that.   Advice: If you are starting with photography and want a beginners device, this is it. More options that an entry level DSLR (with a little compromise on image quality). Just the low light issue will bother you; rest it will amaze you every time.   Go clicking :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">very nice camera and worth for money. zoom and picture quality are very good. nicely packed and delivered on time.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Focusing is the biggest prob of this cam. Focusing doesn't comes accurately like L820 and sometime in long zoom it won't even focus. Power up also having some issue. I have to press the button 2 to 3 times sometime then it will start and processing is also slow. Another cron picture depth is not that much like L820 (clarity is more).</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">18.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Image Size: 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 4864 x 2736 (13 M), 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 1920 x 1080 (2 M), 3:2 Aspect Ratio: 4896 x 3264, 1:1 Aspect Ratio 3672 x 3672, Movie: 1080 / 30p, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 1080 / 25p, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9...View More

Image Size: 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 4864 x 2736 (13 M), 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 1920 x 1080 (2 M), 3:2 Aspect Ratio: 4896 x 3264, 1:1 Aspect Ratio 3672 x 3672, Movie: 1080 / 30p, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 1080 / 25p, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 25 fps, 1080 / 30p, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 1080 / 25p, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 25 fps, 1080 / 60i, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 60 fps, 1080 / 50i, 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 50 fps, 720 / 30p, 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 720 / 25p: 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 25 fps, iFrame 540 / 30p: 960 x 540 / 16:9 / 30 fps, iFrame 540 / 25p: 960 x 540 / 16:9 / 25 fps, 480 / 30p: 640 x 480 / 4:3 / 30 fps, 480 / 25p: 640 x 480 / 4:3 / 25 fps, HS 480 / 4x: 640 x 480 / 4:3, HS 720 / 2x: 1280 x 720 / 16:9, HS 1080 / 0.5x: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.3 - 180 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 24 - 1000 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">42x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">2x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">550 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">125.2 (W) x 84.1 (H) x 101.6 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3.2 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9, 1:1</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, Lens Cap LC-CP24 (with cord), Camera Strap, ViewNX 2 CD, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL5 (with terminal cover), USB Cable UC-E6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">P520</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 8.0 m (W), 1.5 - 4.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 7 Shots at 7 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 3200, ISO 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto 1, Auto 2, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Progr...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Program, Smart, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">32</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Motion Blur Reduction Motion Detection, EXPEED C2 Image-processing Engine, Coolpix Picture Control, Scene Auto Selector, Wireless Mobile Adapter Support, Wi-Fi Compatible, Auto HDR Mode, Easy Panorama 360° / 180°, 3D Shooting Mode, Customizable Function Button, Mode Dial, Subject Tracking AF...View More

Motion Blur Reduction Motion Detection, EXPEED C2 Image-processing Engine, Coolpix Picture Control, Scene Auto Selector, Wireless Mobile Adapter Support, Wi-Fi Compatible, Auto HDR Mode, Easy Panorama 360° / 180°, 3D Shooting Mode, Customizable Function Button, Mode Dial, Subject Tracking AF, 19 Optimized Scene Modes, Full HD 1080 / 60i (or 50i) Movie Recording, Back-illuminated 18 MP CMOS Sensor EXPEED C2 Processor to Deliver Clear Shots, Lens Construction: 14 Elements in 10 Groups (4 ED Lens Elements), Focus-area Selection: Face Priority, Auto (9-area Automatic Selection), Center (Wide, Normal), Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF, Electronic Viewfinder: 0.5 cm Equivalent LCD with Diopter Adjustment Function (-4 to m-1), Frame Coverage Shooting Mode: 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage Playback Mode: 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), 5-level Brightness Adjustment, Vari-angle TFT LCD, Exposure Control: Programmed Auto, Shutter Priority Auto, Aperture-priority Auto, Manual, Exposure Bracketing, Exposure Compensation: -2.0 EV - .0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Shutter Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, Electronically-controlled 6-blade Iris Diaphragm Aperture, Aperture Range: 10 Steps of 1/3 EV (W) Auto, Manual Mode, Flash Control: TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Flash Exposure Compensation: -2 EV - EV in increment of 1/3 EV, Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, HDMI Output: Auto, 480p, 720p, and 1080i, 1575.42 MHz GPS Receiver Frequency (C/A Code), Geodetic 84 System WGS, 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Temperature: 0 - 40° C, Humidity: 85%, Powerful Wide-angle to Super-telephoto Coverage</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4896 x 3672 (18 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Progr...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Landscape, Backlighting, Special Effects, User Settings, Program, Smart, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, MPO, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">15 MB</specsKey>
