<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s6300-point-shoot-camera/p/itmd7fnxpszjazmf?pid=CAMD72H4TAKYADS8&otracker=from-search&srno=t_130&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2gGYoL0OFtQ7S8MhhP06fr4qEpSf%2BhnA9hL%2FhzOtZpwoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=a1e1f8b5-49b6-415a-9ad8-14daf9f24495</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">128</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">39</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com//image/camera/d/s/8/nikon-s6300-400x400-imad73sqe3adz9sy.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">9254</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S6300 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Pink</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I bought this camera today, nd i must say i ws right to choose it over other sony nd canon powershot series priced just near 10k, it has all features which u want in a perfect camera for prsnl nd family use, pros:- 1.Full 1080p HD Video recording,  2.LCD with Anti-reflection Coating (no other cameras hv this in this price range excluding nikon cams.  3.BSI CMOS Image Sensor captures true vivid, clear nd rich color images, (best image sensor in this price category, none other camera have this sensor i guess)  4.10x Optical Zoom  5.Superb image quality in low light  6.Easy to use  7.Stereo Microphones record clear sound  8.HDMI Mini port  cons- 1.Low internal memory only 25mb (but no one depends on internal memory u'll b getting 4gb sdhc card inside the box)  2.2.7 inch lcd display, u cn get 3.0inch display in this price range bt its not a big deal,  camera is fully paisa wasool... dont think so much jst go 4 it,</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">:)Awesome pic quality @ nit thanx to BIS sensor. And pic stabilization is also very good overall performance is very good,  but :( have small battery does not last long, 4gb card is not sufficient for 16 mega pics as it is class four so data rate is also slow.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">best camera for those who want to take pictures in low light. overall best in its price range. i bought it with some doubt in mind but after getting this i am quite happy wid its performance and image quality</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I WILL FIRST LIKE TO THANKS FLIPKART people for there lightning fast delivery. I ordered it on 27NOV2012 in afternoon...and m amazed that the camera was in my hand on next day afternoon i.e. on 28NOV2012 afternoon.  GUYS BUY ONLY NIKON...IT GIVES VALUE FOR MONEY AND KEEP ITS PROMISE IN THE QUALITY............  now the question why to buy only this camera.....  GENERAL ADVANTAGES:-  1). Light weight 2). Small Size 3). looks cool in hands 4). portable  TECHNICAL ADVANTAGES  1). 10* ZOOM WITH "FULL" AUTO FOCUSING AND AUTO FOCUSING.   2). FULL HD RECORDING IN 1080p (HIGHEST RESOLUTION).  3). ADVANCE SENSOR FOR BETTER PHOTOGRAPHY.  4). BATTERY CAN BE CHARGE BY THE USB CABLE BY AC ADAPTER OR BY COMPUTER/LAPTOP.  5). PROBLEM FOR CHARGING IS SOLVED AS BATTERY GET CHARGE INSIDE THE CAMERA WITH SUPPLY LIKE MOBILES.  6). GIVES HIGHEST QUALITY OF PHOTOGRAPH IN FULL DARK WITHOUT NOISE.(BETTER ISO RATING)  7). ALL THE SCENE MODE IN THE CAMERA WORKS GOOD.  9). BEST CHARGING OPTION : BY COMPUTER/LAPTOP USING USB CABLE OR BY AC ADAPTER  10) 3D PHOTOGRAPHY  11). SUPPORT 4GB,8GB,16GB AND 64GB MEMORY CARD.  12). PANORAMA FEATURES.   13) BEST NIGHT PHOTOGRAPH, NEGLIGIBLE NOISE,  (IF U TAKE PHOTO IN DARK ROOM, STILL IT TAKE PHOTO IN SUCH A WAY THAT YOU ARE IN THE STUDIO WITH PROPER LIGHT)  14) POWERFUL FLASH  DISADVANTAGE;  1). ACCORDING TO ME I THINK THAT ITS LITTLE COSTLY BUT IF U WANT AWESOME PICTURE QUALITY THEN YOU MUST HAVE TO CHOOSE IT.  NOTE : FRIENDS I HAVE CHECKED NIKONS FOLLOWING CAMERA  1) NIKON L310 2) NIKON L810 3) NIKON L25 4) NIKON L26 5) NIKON S6400 6) NIKON S9100  BUT TRUST ME MY FRIENDS THESE CAMERA HAVE MANY PROBLEMS i.e. battery problem, size problem, price problem, less pixel, sm providing only 720p hd recording, and those who is giving 1080p is much costly.!!!!!  so guys i will say if u dnt have more money then go for NIKON COOLPIX L26 but if you have little more buDget ...go for NIKON COOLPIX S6300......................  NITHER SONY, CANNON, KODAK ,FUJIFLIM , OLYMPUS NOR ANY COMPANY CAN PROVIDE YOU SUCH DRASTIC EXPERIENCE IN THIS AMOUNT.   FOR CHOOSING THIS CAMERA I LITERARY TOOK 3 WHOLE NIGHT FOR SEARCHING FOR IT...ITS ONE TIME INVESTMENT FILL WITH HOPE........  NW U DECIDE WHAT U WANT.......!!!!!!!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">First of all i would like to thank FLIPKART(and the courier aswell) for this amazing product and delivering it at our doorstep within the stipulated time.[I received my product on 3rd day of placing my order(despite being a sunday). Well coming to the product, NIKON COOLPIX S6300,its a wonderful product within the price range 10k.It is very handy,comfortable,stylish,portable and very much suitable for personal use.I am a naive user,i dont know much technicalities about cam,but i find it extremely user friendly,easy to use and it stands upto my expections.This product(being 16mp) gives excellent pictures.When pictures shot with proper conditions, it gives HDR pics which really amazing and one would think those pics are taken from slr cameras.This camera has 19modes of shooting, you can explore it as and when u like.[those who want to experiment and do sum photography work].I find auto scene mode to be very useful as per my requirement.Only problm iz dat it has average battery lyf(when fully charged around 220 shot, as flash drains away its charge).It has a very good flash light quality which iz effective upto 5 mtrs raduis.It has 10x zoom(optical)n 4x (digital), which can zoom object at a distance of 15 feet conveniently.It gives a very good video hd quality. so, ultimatly this turns out to be a very good product as this many features.one more thing i want to say,before using this product (if possible) please read its manual if u want it to deliver its best,in my case it took me almost one day or 30 shots to set my hands on it(for proper timigs and best shots).Now i am enjoying and hav no regret for this product.  This is the best choice if you have budget under 10k,if not then i would recommend to go for nikon L310 or L810[if u r luking for dslr cameras which comes with hardly a difference of 2k(unless price matters to u)].</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">I imported it from USA. It cost me Rs.2000/- less ! Overall quality of the build is very nice. I am satisfied.  Pro's - 16mp 10X zoom HD video recording Powerful flash Decent battery  Con's- Low internal memory [only 25mb] avg display size of screen a bit over priced maybe..  overall 4/5 stars ! better to buy a sony cybershot cam in my opinion..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">First about Flipkart: Good: - Excellent delivery time. Just within two days. - HDMI cable is very useful. Bad: - 4GB card is no use for me; it's very old one. I bought new SanDisk Ultra Class 10 SDHC 16GB memory card for this. - e-Gift voucher takes 10 working days; absolutely ridiculous!  About Camera - Pros: 1. It's a very Lightweight and easy to carry. 2. Good picture quality. 3. Good flashlight. 4. HDMI port. 5. Full HD 1080p video recording - none of the other camera have 1080p at this price tag. 6. Capture speed is too good. 7. Easy to use camera.  Cons: 1. Average LCD screen. 2. Very poor LCD UI interface. Looks like 1980 MS-DOS program. 3. Lens shift vibration does not work at all. 4. It captures lens zooming sound also. 5. Full HD quality is average. I am not impressed at all. Was expecting far better quality. 6. Red eye reduction does not work everytime. 7. Build quility looks very average. 8. Some cases low light capture is not so good. 9. Low internal memory.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I have never had any other camera before this , so i don't know in-depth difference between various brand. But i liked the camera , the optical zoom and usability is good. The pic quality is also good.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">About Flipkart:- ================= *Delivery is Good. *Awesome Packaging. *Completely Assuring. *Awesome shipment tracking system.  About Camera:- ===============  Awesome Fabulous Mind-Blowing No Doubt (You may go for it without any hesitation) Better Than Sony DSC-W690; Samsung WB150F; Canon Powershot SX150  What you may not find in other cameras in the same range:- ----------------------------------------------------------  *Backside Illumination CMOS Sensor(Best for low light images) *Full HD Recording(1080p) *Eye-Fi Card Support(i.e. wifi support is there) *Stereo Microphone  Pros:- ------- *Including All Above *10x Optical Zoom *16 MP *Lithium Ion Battery with good battery backup(3.7 V; 1050mAh; 3.9Wh) *Way Too Small *Powerfull Flash(Effective upto 5m ) *Connectivity To Both HDTV and Regular TV *19 Shooting Modes *Focus Upto 12 faces(In Face Priority AF Mode) *Awesome Controls  Cons:- ------- *Average(or below) Panaroma Mode(180 and 360 degree) *Not Much Manual Control(Not Needed For Begginers) *Zoom In/Out sound of Lens may get recorded while recording(that's bearable) *10cm Macro Level(incomparison to others which may have 1cm or 5cm) *Camera get heat up after 10-25 min recording at Full HD level(Not a manufacturing defect;No need to worry as camera is smart enough to handle it by shutting itself off as soon as the tempreture reaches the threshold value)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">I bought this camera and got it delivered very soon by flipkart. I must say the camera is worth the price paying.  It's Zoom is really good. I took a pic at full zoom and was amazed with the quality of the pic so clear. And if you take a lot of pics in low light then this camera is a really for you. The images in low light are taken really well. Functions are very easy.   This is a starting series and should not be compared with DSLR's. If you are comparing the camera with the DSLR then you will definitely be disappointed. The image clarity is really good.  I got a 4 gb memory card with this camera which is ok, not so great since the speed of the camera is slow. If you find that the camera is working slow then you should replace the memory card with a higher class memory card. It is not a camera issue.  I liked one of the features in which you can select the colour and click image. Everything apart from that colour comes black and white. It's really cool.  I just missed the gift voucher from flipkart. If I would have placed the order 2 days later I would have got the voucher :( but its ok.  To summarize its worth paying the amount. AND do not compare with the DSLR's for image quality.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5 - 45.0 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 25 - 250 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">10x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">160 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">93.6 (W) x 57.7 (H) x 26.0 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, Reference Manual CD, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12 (with terminal cover), USB Cable UC-E6, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, Camera Strap, Charging AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S6300</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, On, Off, Red-eye, Slow-sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 5.6 m (W), 1.0 - 3.1 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">BSI CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.2 - F5.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">25 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6 fps (Continuous H), 1.9 fps up to 6 Images (Continuous L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto, 125, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (Auto gain from ISO 125 - 1600), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 125 - 400, 125 - 800)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, S...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Subject Tracking</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 10 cm (Wide-angle Position)</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">HDMI Mini Connector (Type C)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, S...View More

Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait, Subject Tracking</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264, MPEG-4, AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">25 MB</specsKey>
