<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-1-v1-mirrorless-camera/p/itmdv58fsmtmk3zn?pid=CAMDWJ6TZGQ73PKR&otracker=from-search&srno=t_414&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff1lGjaTx0KnbCTSL4W6iAH2yg8iswzhh0RTSZ%2BGEUlyJIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=8380be3e-0a03-45a1-bd25-80add7507bb8</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">5</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/p/k/r/nikon-1-v1-mirrorless-400x400-imadx8ya6b3ukcm8.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">21429</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon 1 V1 Mirrorless Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">White</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Mirrorless</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/16000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">1 V1</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Audio / Video Cable EG-CP14, USB Cable UC-E6, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL15, Battery Charger MH-25, Multi Accessory Port Cover BS-N1000, User's Manual, Body Cap BF-N1000, ViewNX 2/Short Movie Creator CD, Reference Manual CD, Strap AN-N1000</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Fill Flash, Slow Sync, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain Sync, Rear Curtain with Slow Sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F5.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Dust Shield Glass</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">2.7x Lens Focal Length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted 4.5 mm Circle in Center of Frame, Spot 2 mm Circle Centered on Selected Focus Area</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 5 fps, 10 fps, 30 fps, 60 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto ISO (ISO 100 - 3200, 100 - 800, 100 - 400)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Still Image (3:2), Smart Photo Selector (3:2), Movie (HD 16:9, Slow Motion 8:3), Motion Snapshot (16:9)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C Mini-pin HDMI Connector</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">25</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Still Image (Still Image and Smart Photo Selector modes, Aspect Ratio 3:2) 2896 x 1944, 1936 x 1296, Still Images (Movie Mode, Aspect Ratio 16:9) 3840 x 2160 (1080/60i), 1920 x 1080 (1080/30p), 1280 x 720 (720/60p), Still images (Motion Snapshot Mode, Aspect Ratio 16:9) 3840 x 2160, ISO Sensitivity:...View More

Still Image (Still Image and Smart Photo Selector modes, Aspect Ratio 3:2) 2896 x 1944, 1936 x 1296, Still Images (Movie Mode, Aspect Ratio 16:9) 3840 x 2160 (1080/60i), 1920 x 1080 (1080/30p), 1280 x 720 (720/60p), Still images (Motion Snapshot Mode, Aspect Ratio 16:9) 3840 x 2160, ISO Sensitivity: ISO 100 - 3200 in Steps of 1 EV, Can also be set to approx. 1 EV (ISO 6400 Equivalent) Above ISO 3200, Brightness Adjustment, Playback Function: Full Frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar) Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Slide Show, Histogram Display, Auto Image Rotation, Rating Option, 0.47 inch TFT LCD Viewfinder with Diopter Control and Brightness Adjustment, AF-assist Illuminator, Focus Modes: Single-point, Auto-area, Subject Tracking, Focus Lock, Exposure Control: Single Frame, Continuous, Electronic (Hi), Self-timer, Delayed Remote, Quick-response Remote, Interval Timer Shooting, Shutter: Single Frame, Continuous Mechanical, Electronic, Electronic (Hi) Self-timer, Delayed Remote, Quick-response Remote, Interval Timer Shooting, i-TTL Flash Control, Remote Control: Delayed Remote (2 sec), Quick-response Remote, GPS Unit GP-N100 (Optional Accessories), Nikon 1 Lens Mount, Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Selected Picture Control can be Modified, 100 % Horizontal and 100 % Vertical Frame Coverage, 17 mm Eye Point, -3- m-1 Diopter Adjustment, Eye Sensor, Compitabile Lens: 1 NIKKOR lenses for 1 Mount, Shutter Type: Electronically-controlled Vertical-travel Focal Plane Mechanical shutter, Electronic Shutter, Fastes Shutter Speed: Electronic Shutter - 1/16,000 sec in steps of 1/3EV, Mechanical Shutter - 1/4,000 sec in steps of 1/3EV, Slowest Shutter Speed: 30 sec in steps of 1/3EV with either Electronic or Mechanical Shutter, Flash Sync Speed: Electronic shutter - 1/60 sec, Mechanical Shutter - 1/250 Sec, Bulb Shutter Setting, TTL Exposure Metering, Exposure Mode: Programmed Auto with Flexible Program, Shutter Priority Auto, Aperture Priority Auto, Manual, Scene Auto Selector, Exposure Compensation: 3 EV in increments of 1/3EV, Exposure Lock, Active D-Lighting On and Off, Lens Servo: Auto Focus (AF), Single AF (AF-S), Continuous AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S/AF-C Selection (AF-A), Full-time AF (AF-F), Manual Focus (MF), Flash-ready Indicator, Multi Accessory Port, 1/4 inch (ISO 1222) Tripod Socket, Recording Time: 1080, 60i (20 minutes), 1080, 30p (20 minutes), 720, 60p (29 minutes), Accessory Shoe, Operating Temperature: 0Deg - 40Deg C, Humidity: 85 %</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">1 NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Hybrid Autofocus (Phase Detection / Contrast Detect AF)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">10 - 30 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 27 - 81 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">10.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">3872 x 2592 (3:2)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Still Image (3:2), Smart Photo Selector (3:2), Movie (HD 16:9, Slow Motion 8:3), Motion Snapshot (16:9)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (RAW), JPEG, NEF (RAW) JPEG, DCF, DPOF, EXIF 2.3</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">AAC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter, Requires EP-5B Power Connector (Sold Separately)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">294 g (Camera Body Only), 383 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Body Cap)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">113 (W) x 76 (H) x 43.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Operating System">Windows XP SP3, Windows Vista SP2, Windows 7 SP1, Apple MAC OS X 10.5.8 - 10.6.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">3:2, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Electronic Viewfinder</specsKey>
