<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-l830-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdtjgqy5fcuacw?pid=CAMDTJGZGHNQFAHE&otracker=from-search&srno=t_66&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3XHHh5Tw7JcFTW0hcRfoSmF97oVgHqwez7SqU2aIR0MIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=2cfb7aa5-8298-4336-8579-fa81e4789b0e</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.3</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">332</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">102</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/a/h/e/nikon-coolpix-l830-point-shoot-400x400-imadtkfzexzpyvxb.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">13900</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix L830 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Plum</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">First of all, I would like to thank the retailer, for the package, which was efficiently packed, and the speedy delivery, as against 22nd, it was delivered on 16th itself! Brand new item, which not even a scratch!  A word of advice to the vendor, please include the Bag & 4GB card that you are providing with in your item description! It was not mentioned in the description, and I found it out, when the package arrived, to my pleasant surprise. Other holler about it in their site!  Coming back to the camera, I found it pleasing to the eye, low start-up time, and a very loong lense..... Pros; 1. Outdoor shots are crisp & clear. 2. Good color rendition. 3. HDR works! 4. full HD video, and 60FPS & 120FPS too!  Cons; 1. at the tele end, AF doesn't work. So is when doing macro in low-light. 2. No manual control for Shutter speed & Aperture. 3. No VF 4. For HDR, Burst & Panorama, it is advised that you use a tripod.  Overall verdict;  A nice camera that gives VFM, only if you are into shooting Family pics, weddings and casual stuff... If you are serious about your PG-phy, go for something else;  As a person who once owned a true SLR (FILM), I found this camera lacks in many fronts; but a SLR is a SLR..... :) Happy shooting</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Bought this in flipkart more than a month. Product was delivered properly and Hats off to the communication from flipkart between order time and Delivery. Pls Keep it up. Though i found cheaper prices in ebay, the deal in flipkart was worth it. Got a Battery charger worth Rs 1900, 4 NiMH batteries and 4 NiMH original nikon rechargable batteries, pouch, HDMI cable. The product is worth the money. Great product from nikon. The best in Semi DSLR models. Compared this with other Nikon models and Sony, panasonic & Canon Models. Nikon wins hands down.  Pros : Excellent Camera quality. Long zoom quality is awesome. Simple features & easy to use.  Cons : They dont provide a soft cloth to clean the camera lens for minor dusts.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">I was surprised when open the box, every thing was fine except the SD card of 4GB instead of 8, that is unusual and not expected from FLIPKART</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I have used L810 camera which has almost same specification except zoom. If you want to use it for family then it is great gadget but for photography this is a big headache.  No Manual focus No control on shutter speed No aperture control  Very light weight which is bane for photography. Slight hand movement will give blur and shaked photograph. In one go you can take only 150-200 photographs, Believe me this number is very less once you go on clicking.  Too much noise at high ISO.  But personally this camera taught me all hook and crook of taking photographs when I had only click and zoom button under my finger.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">I god the product on 14th Apr, 2 days in advance to the date promised, and then finding the review of the same camera in the new products section in Times of India Paper on 15th was just too sweet for me that I did make a good choice. I am a casual photographer. This is going to put my skills to test and I am sure it is worth every rupee. Packing is really cool. Nikon's move to add the, SD card, Bag, charger, rechargeable batteries and the HDMI cable are the USPs for me. the additional 4 alkaline batteries are proof of Nikons forethought in allowing the users to test and use the camera while the rechargeable one gets their first charge. Camera is just too good. Since it is just few hours that I was able to check the functionality no serious comments, but first impression is it is a value for money product. Zoom-- as expected works well when held steady and the object in focus is not moving fast.  Movie recording is not upto the mark in low lights.  I am just trying to get used to set the camera to shoot moving objects as most of the times the images are really blurred. Serious comments in time tocome. Bye</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">First of all thanks for the timely delivery... it was delivered ahead of timing in neat packing..... The product is awesome....  On the negative side >> As per the post, there was 8GB SD card which was put as Free... But i found only 4GB card inside the product...was it a mix up in the description or was it wrongly placed.....  Would have given 5 stars if that was corrected.....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">After lot of research and comparison at various sites finally decided to go with the purchase of Nikon Coolpix L830 , it was really worth buying the product, the packet comes with 4 Fijutsu sample batteries, camera cover, cover strap, 4GB memory card, free 4 rechargeable batteries and its charger.  Had taken around 300 shots with alkaline batteries given free in the packet that means the machine uses less of battery...FIRST HAND LOOK of the camera is fabulous and its lens and zoom is really demonstrative and pic quality is excellent with full zoom. the tilt screen is something again an added feature of this machine..Technicalities cannot be demonstrated much as am not a professional photographer and usage is only at personal front.  Overall my experience with the camera is really satisfactory as the pic that I could capture of my small baby with her fast move is really great.   Only CONS that i could figure out is company is not providing the usage manual in details as I feel that the system is fully loaded but am unable to use the feature to the fullest.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">After a lot of research I went out to buy L820 but was for a sweet surprise to see L830. It's predecessor L820 was and still is a Nikkon 'SuperStar' Though with L830 the upgrades are not big but very very relevant.  Fancy title screen is soo relevant to the feature it targets-- 'Shooting-with-ease' whether it's a Child's smile or a heavy paparazzi crowd from a height. Just tilt the screen and you'll be smiling for the comfort you'll be getting with this feature.  With an extra zoom button on the left gives you that extra 'grippie' control over the zoom feature. And the one-touch video button is a treat to use for those 'not-to-miss' instant video moments.  It has been only 2 days since I brought this beauty from Nikkon but I'm already in love with it.  Oh yes, there is a minor 4x extra zoom upgrade w.r.t L820. It's now 34x. I was impressed (with open-mouthed) with its picture quality for a photo I clicked of a sign board 1Km away from my balcony.  Only minor flip-side was the flimsy battery slit-opener.I've a feeling that it won't last long but that's like a 0.0001% downside of a 'value-for-money-technological marvel' from Nikkon.  Normally you get a Free 4GB card+HDMI cable+ a pouch but that all depends upon company/retailer offer. Battery life is the same as L820 for which there are already hundreds of review comments.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I bought this camera last month and i found it so user friendly & in my budget. I liked the high optical zoom. The image quality is crystal clear. The best feature is that i can click pics with blurred background which i always have been fond of.  I recommend this camera for those who want to start photographing for the first time. This is the camera for you. I will give 5 out 5 to this camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">PROS:  EXCELLENT ZOOMING IMAGE VERY GOOD IMAGE QUALITY EXCELLENT CHARGE - U CAN TAKE MORE AND MORE PHOTOS LOOKS LIKE DAYLIGHT WHEN USING FLASH IN FULL DARK ROOM HD VIDEO RECORDING  CONS:  FOR VIDEO HD RECORDING ZOOMING LENS NOISE RECORDED IN THE VIDEO</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap, Lens Cap LC-CP28 (with cord), LR6/L40 (AA-size) alkaline batteries (x4), USB Cable UC-E16</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">L830</specsKey>
<specsKey="Processor">Expeed C2 Image-processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">BSI CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Total Pixel/Gross Pixel">16.79</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4 - 136 mm (35 mm (135) Equivalent 22.5 - 765 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Focus Features">Digital Zoom Magnification: 35 mm (135) Equivalent 3060 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus Range">50 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3 - F5.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600 (Auto), ISO 3200 (Manual)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">1 cm - Infinity</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Wide Viewing Angle, 5-axis Hybrid Vibration Reduction for Movie Recording, Smart Portrait System, Easy Auto Mode, Target Finding AF, Special Effects and Quick Effects, Tiltable VGA LCD Monitor (RGBW), 68x Dynamic Fine Zoom, Combination of Lens-shift and Electronic Vibration Reduction, Motion Blur Re...View More

Wide Viewing Angle, 5-axis Hybrid Vibration Reduction for Movie Recording, Smart Portrait System, Easy Auto Mode, Target Finding AF, Special Effects and Quick Effects, Tiltable VGA LCD Monitor (RGBW), 68x Dynamic Fine Zoom, Combination of Lens-shift and Electronic Vibration Reduction, Motion Blur Reduction: Motion Detection (Still Pictures), Battery Life of Still Shooting: 390 Shots with Alkaline, 1180 Shots with Lithium / 680 Shots with EN-MH2 Batteries</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">34x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focus">Auto</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Features">3456 x 3456 (1:1)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Size at Megapixels">4608 x 3456 (16 M (High)), 4608 x 3456 (16 M), 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Still Image Size 16:9">4608 x 2592</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">AA Alkaline Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">508 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">111 (W) x 75.8 (H) x 91.2 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
