<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d5200-dslr-camera/p/itmdxsprudh7bbr8?pid=CAMDF4FHEHKYNSHY&otracker=from-search&srno=t_7&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff1zbFIvV72nGEZ1nRm2CZ98dyzM1cqlIC6F9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">636</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">182</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/s/h/y/nikon-d5200-dslr-400x400-imaeyxfaq5qmz4tb.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">36500</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D5200 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I have purchased Nikon D5200 exactly a week back on this day from a local renowned dealer at a much lower price than quoted on Flipkart.  I was on the verge of buying a D5100 in October 2012 when I read about the impending launch of the D5200. So I waited patiently.  Does it mean D5100 is inferior - the answer is "NO" but just that it has a more experienced and better equipped elder brother who has joined the family.  Both the cameras have common strengths and weaknesses. To mention a few -  STRENGTHS - Low noise (grain) at high ISO's / good image quality and colour depth / flip out screens / focus continuously while recording movies / in-camera HDR (high dynamic range)  WEAKNESSES - No focus motor / slow max shutter speed (1/4000 of a second ) / no image stabilization / no panorama mode / slow continuous shooting ( 5fps on D5200 vs 4fps on D5100 )  DIFFERENCES - D5100 is a good 10k less than D5200 with the 18-55mm kit lens / longer battery life in D5100  So why should one buy a D5200???  1. Many more focus points - 39 vs 11 2. Much higher resolution - 24MP vs 16.1MP 3. More cross-type focus points - 9 vs 1 4. Shoots faster - 5fps vs 4fps 5. In-built audio - Stereo vs Mono  D5100 was launched in April 2011   I have not had a proper opportunity to put my camera through the grid but the few shots taken are simply amazing. I will probably write another review later.  I am a complete amateur so far as photography goes but learning everyday.  Hope the above helps...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">This is an amazing camera with great features and functions, yet another milestone by Nikon after the very successful and famous Young brother D5100! Buy it!! you'll never ask for more!! it completes almost all the needs to a beginner Photographer and young Enthusiasts! Only thing that makes it step down is absence of an Autofocus motor! But if you are a new and picking this one as your first DSLR?? Trust me you wont even feel the difference! And Touchscreen would have been a great feature, as its competitor Canon Model already has one! but an articulated screen always helps and makes creativity go at another level!! :)   And Flipkart?? You guys are doing an amazing job!! I seriously dont shop anymore, I JUST FLIPKART it! :D</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">If u wanna know the actual meaning of the word 'AWESOME"... go for it.  As soon as it arrived to me, without reading the manual I took it into my hand and let me say it is so easy to use that even a layman can operate it. (Yeh kuch jyada ho gaya) It has tons of various functions,,,,,,,  Competitors of This camera are -  1.>Nikon d5100 ,,, But d5200 is better 2.>Nikon d5300,,, d5300 is better than d5200 3.>Nikon d3200,, d5200 is way better 4.>Nikon d3300,, almost same....  PLEASE BEFORE BUYING ANY CAMERA (DSLR or Only DIGITAL) LOG ON TO snapsort.com,,,,  and know which camera is better and in what aspects ....( all techinal details are give in this website) and please do compare ......</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I have not purchased this camera from FK though I wanted to write how good it is.   D5200 is a major upgrade from previous model D5100. After waiting for 2 months I finally purchased and I felt that it was worth waiting for it.. Ergonomics wise I feel very good in my hands.  They have upgraded to 9 cross type auto focus points compared to 1 in previous one. Video quality has been improved and in manual mode one can control ISO and shutter speed with ease.  New feature of using it with WR-R10 will be a plus point to those who want wireless.  Megapixel has been upgraded from 16mp to 24mp though I am not a pixel peeper..  In nut and shell I can say that it has stolen most of the qualities of D7000 that includes 39 autofocus. Ofcource at this price no company would give you a metal body with prosumer grade dslr qualities .   One good thing is that it has a fantastic metering and has no over exposure and back focus problem like D7000. Nikon has worked nicely on it. So that is why I would recommend this product to you....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">I really like the fact that someone already pointed out that go for d5100 and save 10000 bucks, because its better use of money.If you really want something good go for d7000 which is an awesome camera and nails everything (d7000 is not for starters though ,people will feedle with the manual settings and post crap that it has exposure problems and stuff) learn to understand every camera that u use.Now D5200 why should some one buy it, it is a good camera and offers a lot for its price if u are a casual photographer - people get over 24 megapixel hype it does not make great cameras - if you ask me i would say d90 is a better still camera which is 12 megapixel...then what to look for when u buy a camera ...first things first - 1> how it feels in your hand 2>how quickly does it focus.. does it have autofocus motor built in?)(d5200 lacks this) (this means that u can go for nikon d lenses which is cheaper than g lenses) 3> whats the low light capability like (the iso mark - what imgaes look like iso 800 - iso 2000) - cameras do offer much higher isos but trust me u don't want to breach iso 2000 on crop sensor bodies. 4>the shutter speed and battery life .What most people forget to do when buying a slr ... make sure to have a kit lens if u are tight on budget (18-55 /18-105) but make sure u buy a prime 50 mm 1.8 cheapest/50mm 1.4 or 35 mm 1.8 which i could suggest for good potraits .Make sure u get a tripod and a remote...i am sorry if anyone is offended but i spoke from what i felt after using d3100/d3200/d5200/d90/d7000/d7100/d300s...Always remember every nikon that i mentioned here are great cameras provided u know how to use it and put goo d lens .....if money made good photos then the richest photographers would have the best ones isn'nt it .....be smart use your money wisely</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Before i share my views on the camera, let me acknowledge the incredibly swift delivery of the product. In a day's time, if you can believe. Marvelous job FlipKart.   I have a passion for photography. Having said that, I am no expert on DSLR's. To satiate my passion, I first bought myself Cannon EOS 1000D and used it extensively for shooting portraits, wildlife, nature, buildings etcetra over a 3 year period. I was impressed with the pictures until i came across a friend who showed the images he had shot using Nikon D5100. Despite lacking in professional knowledge on photography, i could easily see the difference in sharpness and quality of images. Nikon was definitely in a different league.   I decided to progress to the next level and buy a Nikon. Before purchase, i did my research by comparing Nikon with Cannon. I was glad that Nikon camera's scored higher on various parameters when compared with a relative product manufactured by Cannon.    I brought down my search to two products of Nikon, D90 and D5200. I spent sometime studying both. And finally decided to go in for D5200 buoyed by the various modes of photography offered on this camera. Despite my research i was tentative since i was not paying peanuts for this camera. When i finally got the camera, I started exploring it.   I was fascinated with the choice of modes, the menu options, the image quality, size, flash effect to mention a few. The camera also enables you to shoot using various effects instead of editing using applications.  The camera came with an 18-55 mm VR kit lens. I have shot portraits, buildings and nature using this product. And boy have i been impressed with the images.   My journey with this fascinating product has just begun. So far so good!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I would not go for D5200 unless I want those features for 10k extra. Stick with D5100, it is the best in its category and will give you amazing shots. Use extra 10K to get a good lens. This does not mean that D5200 is bad. It is very good, but my vote goes to D5100.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">My first DSLR. I cannot rate the camera as such, but I trust the umpteen reviews across the various websites and believe this is a good camera. I'm still trying to come up with good pictures with it though :)  Apart from that, I'd like to point out: 1. The DSLR bag that came is functional, but looks awful. 2. The box had a sticker that claimed a 2-year warranty. But the warranty card inside indicated a 1-year warranty. I'm confused about this here.  Some things that you must plan to buy along with the camera: 1. A screen guard for the LCD 2. A lens cleaner. 3. Filters (at the minimum, a UV filter to protect the lens) (I bought Hoya's 3 filter kit)  And some time later, you'd want: 1. A fast Class 10 SDHC card with higher capacity that the 4GB provided. 2. A prime lens (35mm or 50mm f1.8) and/or a zoom lens.  This is one white elephant :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I will be buying this camera very soon and have been reading a lot about Nikon cameras. The Nikon D5100 was a very good camera till now, but it has been replaced by D5200. This camera brings features of high end Nikon cameras in this price range and will make for an ultimate all in one camera for atleast 4 years from now. Good investment !</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">I needed the Camera to be delivered super fast as I was leaving outstation and requested Flipkart for a early delivery. Amazing service and responsiveness from flipkart, they were very helpful, responded back and delivered much before their promised SLA. 5/5 for their customer service.   As far as the product is concerned, came in Factory Sealed Pack, no damage, all freebies as promised and no worries. Came with the latest VR2 lens and an excellent Memory card. The bag was a bit so so - effective but not really impressive.  Chose 5200 after evaluating Nikon 5300 (more cost and not much more for the extra buck), Nikon 3200 (5200 has a better dynamic range, better picture quality and better ISO for around 10% more cost) and way way better than the Canon 600D. Liked the picture quality better image then the Sony A58 (again A58 was at a higher cost)  So chose the 5200 based on image quality and value for money.   Took 500 snaps in 4 days with the Nikon. 5200 has an amazing picture quality, excellent low light sensitivity and the best part is that it was able to capture the vivid colors of the Ajanta Frescos in low light without flash - which were not at all visible to the naked eye! Even with the stock lens was able to get a few snaps with amazing depth of field. Bright sunshine photos were never over exposed and the low light photos were way better than my expectation. Was surprised to be able to capture a shot of the moon at 3 pm blazing sunshine.   Only thing I was not impressed was the 5200's HDR. Without HDR itself the camera was capturing vivid images, did not see much change with the HDR ON - possibly my learning curve.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D5200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Warranty Card), Digital Camera D5200 with Lens AF-S DX VR 18 55 mm/ f/3.5 f/5.6 G II 1 Set (Including: Strap, AV Cable, Software, Manual and Guide Book, USB Cacble, Eyepiece Cap, Rechargable Battery, Battery Charger</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Image Sensor Cleaning</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix Metering: 3D Color Matrix Metering II (Type G and D Lenses), Color Matrix Metering II (Other CPU Lenses), Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 4 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100 - 6400</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent (7 Types), Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Portrait, Child, Close Up, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Pet Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">24.71 Million Total Pixels, Single-lens Reflex Digital Camera, Effective Angle of View (Nikon DX Format, Focal Length Equivalent to 1.5x, Picture Control System (Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Selected Picture Control, Custom Picture Controls), Frame Coverage (95% Horizon...View More

24.71 Million Total Pixels, Single-lens Reflex Digital Camera, Effective Angle of View (Nikon DX Format, Focal Length Equivalent to 1.5x, Picture Control System (Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Selected Picture Control, Custom Picture Controls), Frame Coverage (95% Horizontal and 95% Vertical), Magnification (0.78x, -1.0 - m-1), 17.9 mm Eyepoint, Diopter Adjustment (-1.7 - .7, m-1), Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark 7 Screen Focusing Screen, Reflex Mirror Quick Return, Lens Aperture (Instant Return, Electronically Controlled), Compatible Lenses (Autofocus is Available with AF-S and AF-I Lenses, Autofocus is Not Available with Other Type G and D Lenses, AF Lenses (IX NIKKOR and Lenses for the F3AF are Not Supported), and AI-P Lenses, Non-CPU Lenses, Electronic Rangefinder Lenses that have a Maximum Aperture of f/5.6), Shutter Type: Electronically-controlled Vertical-travel Focal-plane Shutter, Flash Sync Speed: X=1/200 sec, Sync with Shutter at 1/200 sec, Release Mode (Single Frame, Continuous L, Continuous H, Self-timer, Delayed Remote ML-L3, Quick-response Remote ML-L3, Quiet Shutter Release, Photography Supported), Frame Advance Rate: Upto 3 fps (L), 5 fps (H), Range (ISO 100, f/1.4 Lens, 20° C, 68° F), Matrix or Center-weighted Metering: 0 - 20 EV, Spot Metering: 2 - 20 EV, Exposure Compensation (5 EV in increments of 1/3 or 1/2 EV, P, S, A, and M Modes), Exposure Bracketing: 3 Shots in Steps of 1/3 or 1/2 EV, White Balance Bracketing: 3 Shots in Steps of 1, Active D-Lighting Bracketing: 2 Shots, Exposure Lock, Active D-Lighting (Auto, Extra High, High, Normal, Low, Off), Detection Range: -1 - EV (ISO 100, 20° C, 68° F), Lens Servo (Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S / AF-C Selection (AF-A), Manual Focus (MF), Electronic Rangefinder), 11 Focus Point, AF-area Mode (Single-point AF, 9-, 21-, or 39- Point Dynamic-area AF, 3D-tracking, Auto-area AF, Focus lock, Color Sketch: Auto Flash with Auto Pop-up (P, S, A, M), Food: Manual Pop-up with Button Release, i-TTL Flash Control Using 2016-pixel RGB Sensor, Flash Compensation (-3 - EV in increments of 1/3 or 1/2 EV), Flash-ready Indicator, Accessory Shoe, Nikon Creative Lighting System (CLS), Advanced Wireless Lighting Supported, AS-15 Sync Terminal Adapter, Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Full-time-servo AF (AF-F), Manual Focus (MF), AF-area Mode: Face-priority AF, Wide-area AF, Normal-area AF, Subject-tracking AF, Automatic Scene Selection, Frame Size (pixels) and Frame Rate: 1920 x 1080 (60i / 50i), 1920 x 1080, (30 p / 50 p / 60 p), 640 x 424, (30 p / 25 p), Playback Full-frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar), Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo Movie Slide Shows, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, Image Comment (upto 36 Characters), Audio Input Stereo Mini-pin Jack (3.5 mm Diameter), Operating Temperature: 0° - 40° C, Operating Humidity: 85%</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F Mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Color Filter">Primary (RGB) Color Filter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.1 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">4496 x 3000 (M), 2992 x 2000 (S)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">6016 x 4000 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Portrait, Child, Close Up, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Pet Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, NEF (RAW), NEF (RAW) JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF 2.0, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, MPEG-4 / H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">555 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Cap), 505 g (with Camera Body Only)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">129 (W) x 98 (H) x 78 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC / Compatible with UHS-I</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor with 170° Viewing Angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30p</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
