<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s6150-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdfm5qrsa3zhpp?pid=CAMDFQZYC9TADRQM&otracker=from-search&srno=t_247&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0LzplkiYS9EU%2BDN8Jmsa5rbIPkrMjYuGHQSxUX9kMohYaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=77476514-6655-436f-9c8a-f4423dfc7d42</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.3</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">48</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">12</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/r/q/m/nikon-s6150-point-shoot-400x400-imadftxyz5vyvdep.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">8324</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S6150 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Red</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">This is an amazing piece from Nikon. Nikon is the leader in the field of camera and this is simply amazing. The battery backup is excellent, with 7x zoom its really amazing. You get a touch screen with this phone which is simply amazing at this price. Nikon has got rid of all the useless buttons that other cameras have and have integrated everything into the touch screen. The stylus pen is amazing and gives an expensive feeling. The photo quality is crisp and the flash is bright. It has several photos modes which is amazing and the video quality is better than many camcorders. The styling of camera is also good and it looks really good in hand. The black colour looks the best.   Overall so much features at this price is amazing. Moreover flipcart service and delivery is unmatched. So go for it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Camera is darn good. 1. Touch screen. 2. Li-Battery 3. Nikon Itself- Name matters. 4. Picture clarity. 5. Battery performance.  Nikon just need improvement on the control of flash light.  Anyways, i am completely happy with this choice of mine.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">PICTURE VERY CLEAR...BUT IM NOT HAPPY WITH THE ZOOM DETAILS ..ANYWAY A GOOD CAM FOR PREFECT SHOTS..IM HAPPY WITH MY CAM AND GIFTED TO MY GIRL FRIEND ...NICE TOUCH SCREEN BUT WORKS WELL WITH THAT SITCK ...SO USE THE STICK FOR PERFECT TOUCH</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">This camera comes with 16MP & 7x Optical Wide Zoom which is quite nice for beginners. Picture quality is too good & really cool and video also. There are more than 16 individual scene modes. Close up & Landscape modes are really nice. If you compare the price of it with such Samsung, Kodak, Olympus etc. products with same features, you will find that this camera is quite costly than other. But Nikon s6150 is much better with its great performance from others.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">I really like the video quality, which is excellent.... rest of the other features like touch screen, modes are all good.... I got the product in just two days... Flipkart is changing the way the buyers buys the goods....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">This is my first Digi cam and I had to do a lot of research before buying this camera. No other brand offered 16 MP with 7X zoom, so went ahead and bought it.  The initial experience was slow image processing and was first dissapointed.  Did a lot of research in the net and understood that the SD card has to be equally good enough to withstand the camara speed so upgraded it with a sandisk 16GB SDHC Class 10 card card the fastest image processor card available with 30MB/S and the camara is now truly awsome.   Just keep the 4GB SDHC Class 4 card that comes with the camera aside and upgrade to class 10 SD cards with some extra bucks and u have yourself a good and fast camera.  As always flipkart rocks.......</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I got this product last week till my exp abt dis camera is gud, very user friendly interface,easy to operate and quick respond from touch screen.In deem environment picture image is so clear its mind blowing,and 720p HD quality video is Gr8. Overall till now my exp abt this camera is very nice.Thanks nikon.  Also abt the flipkart service, i got my product within 3 day. Service from flipkart is awesome.Thanks flipkart.:-)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Hi all,  After doing a great research for a cam ranging around 6-8k about a week, I finally choose this product. And satisfied to the core with this cam. It has all cool features that you expect.  Pros: 1. 3" Touch screen. 2. Can be chargeable directly without removing battery! (like mobiles) 3. 20 scene modes including panomara 4. You will get an AV cable with this cam, by using it u can directly connect it to TV 5. Face detection, Smile Detection, Blink detection, Skin softening Subject tracking, Micro mode, Vibration reduction and many more  Cons: 1. Little slow processing. May be due to memory stick. better go for 10C card. You will get 4C 4GB card along with camera.  About Flipkart: Flipkart is offering this product at lowest price compared to few other sites and stores i've checked.  But this time I was disappointed with the delivery, coz, all my earlier items I received in 2-3 days. But I waited for about 1 week for this product. Be aware of it. ;) Anyway Thanks to Flipkart! :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">HI i'm using this camera for last 2 months macro mode: I have bought this camera for its macro mode which can focus an object 3 cm distance from lens. Yes the lens system has the capability but most of the times the software is not intelligent enough to recognise the desired object in the frame though it is the range of 3 cm. So that was disappointing to me. flash: flash range is very small only 2 metres i mean if an object more than that the quality is not good. so in the low light its not good to use zoom Zoom: In good lighting conditions the photo quality is very good even at 7x optical zoom and the digital zoom even at maximum level is excellent user interface: when switches on within 3 seconds it is ready to take photos. and focusing time is also low which is a good thing. But some features are slow. deleting a image is a pain for that i need to press the screen 4 times. and reviewing the last image is not possible (may be a software bug).  touch screen: smooth & very sensitive and responsive but i suggest u to use screen guard.  over all it is a good camera in its price range  and of course the flipkart service is awesome</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Macro mode is a bit dissapointing else the camera is great can surely go for it.Picture quality is awesome and the touchscreen is fast and responsive.The camera is very user friendly and good for beginners.ISO adjustment is great.overall a descent product in a good budget.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Glass lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">5.0 - 35.0 mm (35 mm format equivalent to 28 - 196 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">7x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">175 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">97.9 (W) x 58.0 (H) x 26.6 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD Touch Screen Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Strap AN-CP19, Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, Audio Video Cable EG-CP16, View NX 2 CD, USB Cable UC-E6, Stylus, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL12</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">Coolpix S6150</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with red-eye reduction, Off, Fill flash, Slow sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.7 - F5.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.2 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto (auto gain ISO 80-1600), Fixed range auto (ISO 80 to 400, 80-800), Manual selection: ISO 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Preset manual, Daylight, Incandescent, Fluorescent, Cloudy, Flash</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene modes, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Scene Auto Selector</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 3 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">HDMI mini connector</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256-Segment matrix metering, Center-weighted metering, Spot metering</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4680 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto mode, Scene modes, Smart portrait mode, Movie mode, Scene Auto Selector</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, EXIF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-62F</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">20 MB</specsKey>
