<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s9400-advanced-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdhwha22fsbttz?pid=CAMDGX5HEQRZ5PEC&otracker=from-search&srno=t_380&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2QITWctPn%2Bm4OQKVI5C5tsgieKtgUQvS9j2K0puhcoV4aLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=77f98400-2c7e-45da-bbcb-662d414e0ac6</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">19</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">11</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/p/e/c/nikon-coolpix-s9400-advance-point-and-shoot-400x400-imadgx8trfbbs2h2.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">14000</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S9400 Advanced Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">White</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Advanced Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Flipkart did good job in delivering the product on time. The product is perfect, except the addon free bees they promised to send. One of them was Camera Pouch. This Pouch was smaller than the camera - so the pouch was not meant for the camera I purchased - How strange!! I called Flipkart customer care, but they told that this free bee was added from the manufacturer's side, so I better call Nikon customer care. I did the same, while they told it's Flipkart's responsibility to deliver right product, they can't take care of this issue. They also added that Flipkart is not their authorized dealer. So, it has ended up into a blame game.   I expect perfection in product delivery from Flipkart. This was not expected. Hope Flipkart team can do something in this case and going forward to take care of such issues.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Hi got this one just before 2 days ...picture quality is very good with and without zoom ... works well in low light condition ...flash is required only in very low light ..... back light option is one of the high light ..with 18MP and 18x , this is one of the better option compared to other models within the range ..go for it ...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">i bought this camera yesterday, awesome picture quality, far better than other point n shoot cameras, good in low light, CMOS sensor is superb, 18X zoom clearity is also very clear, but stability of any object only works when flash is on, if flash is not on then motion picture will blur ......</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Small and easy to use  RATINGS (OUT OF 5) Design 4 Features 3.5 Ease-of-use 4.5 Image quality 4 Value for money 4.5  The Nikon Coolpix S9400 is a slim and stylish digital compact camera.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">easy to handle..nice picture quality..nice video quality..only problem is flash which comes out while clicking a photo and battery life is also short......................................................................</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">i bought the camera three days before...it was just awesome...very good picture quality....red eye detection....smart portrait...high zoom.....video recording with pause options are some of the vivid advantages....but there are still more options to be viewed...after having this with u....u will imagine yourself as a professional photographer....just go for it without having any doubt.....and for me the pouch fits well as i bought it in Nikon showroom....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">This is the best camera at this price. And to my surprise its features and performance it is better than any other camera in sub 20K bracket. I compared it with Sony, Panasonic, Cannon and Olympus before finalizing this one. The 18.x zoom is awesome and has literally no lag. Also the picture quality is superb and the colors are vivid and lively and image is very crisp and sharp and in some cases better when compared with my friends cheap SLR camera. Captures extremely nice images in low light conditions. It also has multiple shooting and editing modes. The best feature of this camera is it is charged directly like mobile and does not require a separate charger for battery. If you are looking to buy a camera, go for it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">This Camera was gift to my sister. it looks pretty good. many options to make clear picture. I love it..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">good quality of pictures good quality of video  but little heavy  Flash panel come out during flash is nice feature of this cool pix</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Excellent for those who do not know much about photography but still want amazing pictures. Good night mode too..</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/1500 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S9400</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 6.0 m (W), 1.5 - 3.5 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.4 - F6.3 (W)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 5 Shots at 7.5 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600, ISO 3200 (Auto Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene Auto Selector, Scene</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">25 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 1 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type D, Micro HDMI Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">32</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">18.91 Total Megapixels, 12 Elements in 10 Groups (1 ED Lens Element), Digital Zoom Magnification (1800 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Motion Blur Reduction (Motion Detection (Still Pictures)), Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Center, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Target Finding ...View More

18.91 Total Megapixels, 12 Elements in 10 Groups (1 ED Lens Element), Digital Zoom Magnification (1800 mm Lens in 35 mm (135) Format), Motion Blur Reduction (Motion Detection (Still Pictures)), Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Center, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF), Min Focus Range: 50 cm (W) - 1.5 m (T), 5 Level Brightness Adjustment, Focus Lock, Shooting Mode Monitor Frame Coverage (98% Horizontal, 98% Vertical), Playback Mode Monitor Frame Coverage (100% Horizontal, 100% Vertical), Recording Reslution (HD: 1280 x 720p at 30 fps, HS: 1920 x 1080 at 15 fps, 1280 x 720 at 60 fps, 640 x 480 at 120 fps, 320 x 240 at 24 fps, iFrame: 960 x 540 at 30 fps), Voice Memo Function, Exposure Control (Programmed Auto Exposure, Exposure Compensation), Exposure Modes (Programmed Auto), Scene Modes (Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Night Landscape, Night Portrait, Backlighting, Special Effects, Smart Portrait), In-camera Image Editing (Crop, Data Imprint, D-lighting, Glamour Retouch, Quick Effects, Quick Retouch, Small Picture), Exposure Compensation: 2 EV in incremetns of 1/3 EV, Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, Shutter: 1/4000 - 1/120 sec (Continuous H: 120 fps) 1/4000 - 1/60 sec (Continuous H: 60 fps) 4 sec (Fireworks Show Scene Mode), Aperture (Electronically Controlled ND Filter (-2.0 AV)), TTL Auto Flash with Monitor Preflashes, Interface Data Transfer Protocol (MTP, PTP), HDMI Output (Auto, 480p, 720p, 1080i), Charging Time (3 hrs 50 mins When Using EH-70P Battery Charger), 230 Shots Battery Life, Tripod Socket (1/4, ISO 1222)), Operating Temperature: 0 - 40° C, Operating Humidity: 85%, Continuous Shooting (Single (Default Setting), Continuous L (31 Images at 1.9 fps), Pre-shooting Cache (12 fps / 25 Frames), Continuous H: 120 fps (50 Frames at the Speed of 1/120 sec or Faster), Continuous H: 60 fps (25 Frames at the Speed of 1/60 sec or Faster), Best Shot Selector, Multi-shot 16)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.5 - 81 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 25 - 450 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">18 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), 640 x 480 (VGA), 4864 x 2736 (16:9,13 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4896 x 3672 (18 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene Auto Selector, Scene</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, MPO, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">18x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">200 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">110.1 (W) x 60.3 (H) x 30.7 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">65 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Wide Viewing Angle OLED Monitor with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">614,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
