<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d3300-dslr-camera/p/itmdsqgbwfpw8kqx?pid=CAMDSQGBWFPW8KQX&otracker=from-search&srno=t_8&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff3sb1wMB9n%2BE4jamoT7XcN81YfMg2Q3ql%2BF9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">274</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">80</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/k/q/x/nikon-d3300-dslr-400x400-imaeyxfakakguuzz.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">33900</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D3300 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Very Good Camera in its range. Absence of Low Pass Optical Filter indeed makes a difference in photos. I have N3200 and now I own N3300 too. N3300 is Just awesome.  Price Quoted in Flipkart by other Sellers (Not WSRetail) seems to be more than local market. Nikon in fact provides u with a DSLR Bag and 4GB Memory Card along with these camera for Much Cheaper price almost 3k less than current price in Flipkart !!! I also have heard that if purchase made in online, Nikon fails to provide warranty. Pl go through Nikon site for warranty. Its better to buy from authorized nikon outlets than from online so that our penny spent seems to have some safety in respect to after sales and service. Currently nikkon provides some offer for new purchase of camera go through nikon site.  I recommend this product to others. My Suggestion wait till WSRetail makes this product available or buy in you local authorized shop.  Happy Nikkoooorrrrring !</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I bought this camera on April 4th 2014.   â¢ I recommend the Nikon D3300 to everyone who asks what camera to buy for great photos of family, friends, sports, concerts, theater and action.  â¢ Got kids and want great action, low-light and long-distance photos? The D3300 is the camera to get. Paying more won't get you much more other than a lot more weight to have to carry around.  â¢ The built-in flash is excellent. You probably don't need a separate flash unless you're trying to shoot action or kids which demand a fast recycle time.  â¢ The included 18-55mm VR II is probably all you need for everything. If you're new to photography, the strongest advice I can give you from 45 years of experience is that it's far more important to learn how to use what you've got, instead of confusing the issue by buying more lenses, as you're starting out.  â¢ Personally, I usually use the 35mm f/1.8 DX for everything and leave the 18-55mm VR at home.  â¢ The D3300's LCD is big, bright, sharp and color-accurate. You couldn't really put a bigger or better screen on a camera this small.  â¢ Like most DSLRs, the battery lasts forever. The biggest worry you should have is being lulled into forgetting to bring your charger on a long trip.  â¢ New in the D3300, a swept panorama mode lets us hand-hold and swipe the D3300 in any of four directions to make a 180Âº panorama.  â¢ Color rendition is superb; the D3300 uses all the same picture controls, with matching results, to all the other current Nikon cameras.  PROS: Small for a DSLR; Retracting lens makes camera compact; Sharp, clear images with accurate color; Video has smooth movement; Great price  CONS: No tilting LCD screen; Limited shooting controls.  VERDICT : The Nikon D3300 is an excellent entry-level camera for aspiring photographers, delivering a good feature set and high-quality images.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Canons have good color reproduction and the photos look really good on the camera screen but when zoomed they are not as sharp as Nikons and Canons produce more noise compared to Nikon especially when comparing 3300 and 600d in the Low light. Canon is more famous because of it is easy to use as well as good marketing programs such as Loyalty Programs which makes you buy Canon again and suggest your friends to buy canon, more like Network Marketing but Nikons are more sharp especially when cropped at 100% Nikon are more sharp and have Less noise. Other reason why Canon is more famous because the people who buy a DSLR Camera are 80% enthusiasts and 20% or less professionals. A non proffestional want an easy to use Camera while Proffessionals are more concerned about picture quality. These 80% can become proffessional at some point they may choose their previous brand . so there are more Canons than Nikon. Comparing D3300 and 600d , D3300 is a new camera, Faster autofocus with Expeed 4, more megapixels 24MPX vs 18MPX , 5fps vs 3.7fps , good performance in low light- Low noise at 1385 ISO vs 793 ISO and 60fps vs 30fps D3300 is a clear winner.  If you still have doubts, goto Dxomark.com and get the scientific test results and  Search in google that "Nikon d3300 flickr" goto group pool open the images at 6000x4000 resolution and compare them with 600d by doing the same.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">I've purchased D3300 @ Nikon authorized dealer in Pune, 2 months before and price was just 2000 extra to compared with flipkart. some people are very eager to write here, and they say this camera is for beginner.......beginner?? ....oh come on......this is very high quality product for professional purpose also. this camera comes with 18-55 Nikon VR2 lense which is extremely stable.  But there is huge deference in VR1 and VR2 lenses of Nikon. so please don't purchase 55-200mm VR1......it is very low quality lense. and it is very uncomfortable & risky to swipe lense again & again while on tour. Please note VR2 telephoto lenses are very costly. so try 18-200mm tamron which is not that good but can be used in all condition zoom while traveling and you can avoid any damage to camera body.  About D3300?? This is really awesome camera, I took some extraordinary photos with this...... it took time to learn after reading some books and training......but now no word to explain. I took some moon photos with 55-200mm lense, which need a steady tripod, perfect settings and i can see moon craters clearly but in 100% crop.  One more thing.....dont use low quality cheap filters on lenses.....you'll loose photo qualty. try to get filters from Hoya made.  Enjoy the photography....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">I've got D3300 at the most competitive price (Rs.27461) from WS retail. Also able to register the camera and kit lens with Nikon India site. Delivery was very quick.  Overall satisfied with the purchase on flipkart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">The Camera is good and I am satisfied with the delivery timelines as well, haven't read thru the whole booklet but will surely read it. It's a great product to buy. Buy only from WS Retail as Nikon verifies it as a true seller and honours the warranty...not sure about other sellers</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Initially i was bit confused between D5300 & D3300 but after doing some intensive research i decided to buy D3300.  The product got delivered within 24 Hrs. Thanks to Flipkart...!!!  This camera shoots very high quality stills & records 60 fps 1080p videos.  With the price difference of 15k between D5300 and D3300, i would suggest people to go for D3300 and add some beautiful lens to your kit eg: A must have 35mm Nikkor Lens 55 -200mm VR Nikkor Lens).  Will share more in detail after few weeks of usage.  For now i am very satisfied with the product & the service provided by the Flipkart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">best among the price range, provides all necessary specs for doing good photography for beginners. smaller than most other dslr cameras, light and very convenient to carry around. picture quality is great. can't expect anything more under this price range</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Just bought few days back so sharing early experience IQ is fantastic  Easy handling Quick focus ( a problem in most of the entry level DSLR) New processor by Nikon seems real fast Retractable lens is quite good Very handy guide mode for beginners  I have not used any other one so cant actually say about the IQ of others. I feel articulated LCD would have been quite a good introduction in this model Other wise loving the came :)  Buying experience was quite frustrating . most likely i am not gonna buy an expensive item from Flipkart.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Hi Guys,   I have recently brought Nikon D3300 and its a perfect entry level DSLR.  If you want to buy with 100% confidence please buy from WS- Retailer as they are " The Best " reseller here.   I registered my product on Nikon website without any problem.  I also got my self registered in Nikon school.  Camera works absolutely fine !!!  Camera Build Quality is great !!!  Not getting much into Tech spec as all of you are aware of the same.  Over all, its the best deal out there For Nikon D3300, Buy peacefully and Click Happily !!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Built-in Monaural</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D3300</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">DK-25 Rubber Eyecup, BF-1B Body Cap, AN-DC3 Strap, EN-EL14a Rechargeable Li-ion Battery (with terminal cover), ViewNX 2 CD-ROM(DVD Tutorial), MH-24 Battery Charger, EG-CP14 Audio/video Cable, UC-E17 USB Cable</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 (W) - F6.5 (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Image Sensor Cleaning</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix Metering: 3D Color Matrix Metering II (Type G, E and D Lenses), Color Matrix Metering II (Other CPU Lenses), Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO in Steps of 1 EV (200 - 6400), 1 EV above ISO (12800 Equivalent)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Manual, Portrait, Landscape, Child, Sports, Close-up, Night Portrait, Night Vision, Super Vivid, Pop, Photo Illustration, Color Sketch, Toy Camera Effect, Miniature Effect, Panorama</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent (7 Types), Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini-pin HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">34</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">1.5x Lens Focal Length, 24.78 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Frame Coverage: 95% Horizontal and 95% Vertical, 18 mm Eyepoint (-1.0 m-1...View More

1.5x Lens Focal Length, 24.78 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Frame Coverage: 95% Horizontal and 95% Vertical, 18 mm Eyepoint (-1.0 m-1), -1.7 - +0.5 m-1 Diopter Adjustment, Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark VII Focusing Screen, Quick Return Reflex Mirror, Lens Aperture: Instant Return, Electronically Controlled, Compatible Lenses: Autofocus is Available with AF-S and AF-I Lenses, Autofocus is not Available with Other Type G and D Lenses, AF Lenses (IX NIKKOR and Lenses for the F3AF are not Supported), and AI-P Lenses, Non-CPU Lenses can be Used in Mode M, but the Camera Exposure Meter will not Function. The Electronic Rangefinder can be Used with Lenses that have a Maximum Aperture of f/5.6 or Faster, X=1/200 sec Flash Sync Speed, Release Mode: Single Frame, Continuous, Self-timer, Delayed Remote, Quick-response Remote, Quiet Shutter Release, Metering: TTL Exposure Metering using 420-pixel RGB Sensor, Range (ISO 100, f/1.4 Lens, 20° C): Matrix or Center-weighted Metering: 0 - 20 EV Spot Metering: 2 - 20 EV, CPU Exposure Meter Coupling, Exposure Mode: Auto Modes (Auto, Auto (Flash Off), Scene Modes (Portrait, Landscape, Child, Sports, Close-up, Night Portrait), Programmed Auto with Flexible Program (P), Shutter-priority Auto (S), Aperture-priority Auto (A), Manual (M), Exposure Compensation: 5 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Exposure Lock: Luminosity Locked at Detected Value with AE-L/AF-L Button, On and Off Active D-Lighting, Focus Detection Range: -1 - +19 EV (ISO 100, 20° C), Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S/AF-C Selection (AF-A); Predictive Focus Tracking Activated Automatically According to Subject Status, Manual Focus (MF): Electronic Rangefinder, 11 Focus Point, AF-area Mode: Single-point AF, Dynamic-area AF, Auto-area AF, 3D-tracking (11 Points), Focus Lock, Built-in Flash: Auto, Portrait, Child, Close-up, Night Portrait, Super Vivid, Pop, Photo Illustration, Color Sketch, Toy Camera Effect: Auto Flash with Auto Pop-up P, S, A, M: Manual Pop-up with Button Release, Guide Number: 12/39, 13/43 with Manual Flash (m/ft, ISO 100, 20° C), Flash Compensation: -3 - +1 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Flash-ready Indicator, Accessory Shoe: ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync and Data Contacts and Safety Lock, Nikon Creative Lighting System (CLS), AS-15 Sync Terminal Adapter (Sold Separately), Playback: Full-frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar) Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo and/or Movie Slide Shows, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, and Image Comment (upto 36 Characters), Temperature: 0° C - 40° C, Humidity: 85% (No Condensation), Frame Size (Pixels) and Frame Rate: 1920 x 1080, 60p (Progressive) / 50p / 30p / 25p / 24p, High / Normal 1280 x 720, 60p / 50p, High / Normal 640 X 424, 30p / 25p, High / Normal Frame Rates of 30p (Actual Frame Rate 29.97 fps) and 60p (Actual Frame Rate 59.94 fps) are Available when NTSC is Selected for Video Mode. 25p and 50p are Available when PAL is Selected for Video Mode, Actual Frame Rate when 24p is Selected is 23.976 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F Mount (with AF Contacts)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">18 - 55 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">4496 x 3000 (M), 2992 x 2000 (S), 1920 x 1080, 1280 x 720, 640 x 424</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">6000 x 4000 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Manual, Portrait, Landscape, Child, Sports, Close-up, Night Portrait, Night Vision, Super Vivid, Pop, Photo Illustration, Color Sketch, Toy Camera Effect, Miniature Effect, Panorama</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, NEF (RAW), NEF (RAW) + JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF 2.0, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, MPEG-4 / H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-5b</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">460 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Cap), 410 g (Body Only)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">124 (W) x 98 (H) x 75.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / UHS-I Compliant SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror Single-lens Reflex Viewfinder</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror Single-lens Reflex Viewfinder</specsKey>
