<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d7000-dslr-camera/p/itmduzhneu5h4paq?pid=CAMCVYDJHSCVDVK8&otracker=from-search&srno=t_35&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2fVsPmjROlWcAyIjTa5BD4o4jRmRlFgSuSrYo7cfIcKIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=70bfa3c3-0ea3-487e-ab2e-3a6bc8e08d03</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">31</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews"></specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/v/k/8/nikon-d7000-slr-400x400-imacymdm8udmrkfd.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">47960</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D7000 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">USB 2.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/8000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D7000</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Camera Body, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL15, Quick Charger MH-25, Rubber Eyecup DK-21, Camera Strap AN-DC1, Body Cap BF-1B, Eyepiece Cap DK-5, Accessory Shoe Cover BS-1, USB Cable UC-E4, Video Cable EG-D2, View NX 2 CD, User Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Front-curtain sync, Red-eye reduction, Slow sync with red-eye reduction, Slow sync, rear-curtain sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Format">23.6 x 15.6 mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">1/250 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Continuous low shooting mode: 1-5 , Continuous high shooting mode: 6 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 100 to 6400 in steps of 1/3, 1/2, or 1 EV, plus HI-0.3, HI-0.5, HI-0.7, HI-1, HI-2 (ISO 25600)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous low shooting mode: 1-5 fps, Continuous high shooting mode: 6 fps, Quiet shutter-release, Self-timer mode, Remote Control, Mirror-up mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">Approx. 1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto (TTL white-balance with main image sensor and 2016-pixel RGB sensor,Incandescent Fluorescent Direct Sunlight Flash Cloudy Shade preset manual choose color temperature</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">3D color matrix metering II (type G and D lenses), color matrix metering II (other CPU lenses), Center-weighted (weight of 75% given to 8-mm circle in center of frame), Spot metering (meters 3.5-mm circle centered on selected focus point)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">22</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">Nikon F mount</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL phase detection,39 focus points (9 cross-sensors) by Nikon Multi-CAM 4800DX autofocus module,Detection range: -1 to EV (ISO 100 at 20C/68F)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">1.5x lens focal length</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4928 X 3264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Single frame shooting mode, Continuous low shooting mode: 1-5 fps, Continuous high shooting mode: 6 fps, Quiet shutter-release, Self-timer mode, Remote Control, Mirror-up mode</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">NEF (12 or 14-bit lossless compressed or compressed RAW) JPEG (Baseline-compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV movie (H.264/MPEG-4 AVC compression format with Linear PCM sound,Stero sound with eXternal microphone)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5a AC Adapter (Available Separately; Requires Optional EP-5A Power Connector )</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">690 g</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">132 (W) x 105 (H) x 77 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">Low-temperature Polysilicon TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-3 to .0 m-)</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Fixed eye-level pentaprism; built-in diopter adjustment (-3 to .0 m-)</specsKey>
