<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-d3200-dslr-camera/p/itmdyz8hpwfdydv2?pid=CAMDA6RJERF8HS4G&otracker=from-search&srno=t_6&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff165lMXPquKRdWIlwJFHn4N%2F%2B%2BMo8yRP3SF9BAHhjh2NoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=1bb5a6a8-9bee-4991-92c5-e579f444ed92</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">754</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">165</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/s/4/g/nikon-d3200-dslr-400x400-imaeyxfa7sybqxrr.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">29050</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon D3200 DSLR Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Black</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">DSLR</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Last week I bought Nikon D3200. It was like my dream fullfilled. After searching and reviewing tons of sites, I ended my search on D3200 as Camera and Flipkart as Seller.  First of all I would tell you the future buyers or who have been using other cameras (in this category) that D3200 is much better camera than previous models like D3100 or D5100 or in Canon 550D. People who compare this with 550D or D3100/D5100 don't know that D3200 is the second best camera in sensor performance after Nikon 800. And its hardware features is being compared to Nikon Flagship Camera D800. Let me tell you why this camera is better than others.  - Sensor of D3200 is second best sensor amongst all hi-end  cameras. - Processor of D3200 is same as Nikon Flagship Camera D4 (Reader can find it on Nikon site)  People (all of us) who claim that image quality and ISO sensitivity of D5100 is better than D3200 because they are just reading testing lab result, otherwise normal or expert user can't tell the distinguish be it D3100 / D3200 or 550D/600D.   I just started using this camera and have posted some pix on my facebook and flickr and I got really really good response.  And above all, I would like to thanks "Flipkart Team" who helped me get my dream fulfilled. I got my camera before the committed time i.e. in less than 24 hr of my purchase order. (except Sunday).  I am giving this Camera 4 out 5 star because my hands are bigger and size of this camera is bit small for me. :)  PS : This is unbiased feedback. I am praising D3200 not for that because I have bought it. I just wanted to buy latest launched camera. D3200 was launched in April 2012. Rest are almost 2 years old cameras. But still I love D3100 / D5100 / 550D / 660D, because all are same.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Here are a few reasons to go for the D5100 over the D3200, for those who are undecided and just can't make up their minds:  (1) Better low-light performance - with 16.2MPixels, the noise at high-ISO settings is better than the D3200 (which provides 24MPixels on a marginally smaller sensor). The 24MPixels gives the D3200 a resolution of ~129 line-pairs/mm, while the 16.2 MPixels gives the D5100 a resolution of ~104 lp/mm. Even a high-end exotic lens will provide a maximum optical resolution of ~50 lp/mm, which means that the 104 lp/mm sensor of the D5100 already outresolves the lens. So go for the lower noise, better low light performing D5100.  (2) Auto exposure and white balance bracketing: Believe it or not, the D3200 does not have an AE/WB bracketing option! The D5100 on the other hand allows auto-bracketing in 1/3 or 1/2 stop increments, and in addition, provides an in-camera HDR option (which I rarely use, but there it is).  (3) Active D-Lighting: More options in the D5100 (Auto, High+, High, Normal, Low), i.e. more control for improving dynamic range, vs. ADL on/off in the D3200.  (4) Less expensive: Save your money on the body and use it on the lenses - go for the 70-300mm/55-300mm zoom, or the 50mm/1.8G prime lens to complement the 18-55mm kit lens.  (5) And of course, there's the flip-out screen in the D5100.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Nikon D3200 is pretty nice camera with lots of features, great image quality, lower noise levels even in high iso settings.. Two main rivals of the camera in this price range is Canon 600D & Nikon D5100...I am going to discuss them comparatively.....  1.Megapixels..(megapixels helps you to get high resolution, so that you can crop your primary image and you will still get high quality images)---- 600D- 18MP D5100- 16MP D3200- 24.1MP (so D3200 gives you high quality images, and gets about 30% more detail in images)  2. Autofocus Motor..(body AF motor lets you to auto focus with more lenses)--- 600D- Body AF motor D5100- Lens Af motor D3200- Lens Af motor  3. HDR mode.. (it lets you get high image dynamic range even in backlight situations)--- D5100 has HDR mode, which is nice, but you can also do that with D3200 or 600D, later in any editing software..  4. AF points..(helps to focus perfectly)--- 600D- 9 AF points. D5100- 11 AF points. D3200- 11 AF points.  5. Night shooting-- D3200 is simply better than others in this case, it has very low noise levels even in higher iso settings, trust me, this is amazing.  6. Colour depth and Image quality-- D3200 has much better colour depth, higher image quality, wide dynamic range than others in this case.  7. Sensor size-- D3200 and D5100 both have about 10% larger sensor than 600D  8. Battery life-- D5100-- 660 shots D3200-- 540 shots 600D-- 440 shots  9. Flip out screen..(good for video shooting)-- D5100--Yes 600D-- Yes D3200--No  10. Video quality-- all the cameras have Full HD 1080p video shooting mode, but D3200 has continous autofocus system in video mode, it is a very nice feature...on the other hand 600D has much more manual control on video shooting..  Finally I can recommend you to buy D3200 if you are really interested in still photography and also videography. I am sure this product will satisfy all your needs, but if you want much more control on video shooting you may consider buying 600D. (but keep it on mind that D3200 is much better in image quality, color depth, night photography, dynamic range, image resolution than 600D). I am currently using Nikon D3200, and trust me, you won't regret this buy....  Another thing is that if you are ready to pay about 10k more then you may buy Nikon D5200, which is a really beautiful camera. D5200 has all the good features of these 3 cameras..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Its a great camera..and this entire thing about entry level and professional is a gimmick by the companies to sell their so called higher end models..unless you make a living by taking pictures, it makes no sense to spend lakhs on a camera..if you have to spend money, spend it on a good lens, cos that will give you the best result, and if you have a great lens, you don't need anything more than a D3200..here's why..it is extremely handy..good high ISO performance..good video features..what else do you need ?? People also get confused regarding the brand..the immediate competition is the canon 600d..well, one thing that i must say is that canon does better video..just a little better..a difference not huge enough to matter..if you are looking at still and video combined, nikon does much better..canon gives you glossy pictures, while nikon gives you a more film like result, that actually looks better..and you can always gloss it up on photoshop..If you have a good eye, and know the basics of photography, you can do wonders with the D3200..Its a camera that you can use for ages..and ya, get it from a local camera shop, they sell it at a cheaper rate compared to flipkart, and u'll also get better freebies.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">This was the first DSLR I ever bought. Few pointers:  Pros: - Easy to operate: Even if you are not sure of the aperture and shutter settings you can use the guide to take some really nice pics - Low noise at high ISO..But a tripod as usual is always useful - Great quality of images - Good battery life & lighter - Less start up time  Cons: There are a lot of cons which obviously will be there when you compare with a higher priced camera, but for the price, its definitely worth it.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Buy this camera only if are upgrading from a point and shoot one,or if you own a DSLR which is older than the Nikon D3000 (and other Canon equivalents).  Buying your first camera? Make it this one. :)  And Flipkart,kindly add some freebies to it,like a Tripod...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">The Nikon D3200 is a great intermediate level dslr shooter's companion, it has a 24MP Sensor, but most photographers know that the megapixels don't matter much, its the sensor that does, the Nikon D3100 on the other hand is a camera aimed towards beginners looking to get into DSLR photography, in my opinion it is a better buy, and for 4-5000 rupees more, all your really getting is (in terms of specifications) a bump in megapixels and a microphone input port, in conclusion, I can still recommend the Nikon D3200, but really to a specific crowd rather than the slighter larger majority which would be better off with the D3100. :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I tried my hands on D3200 for a couple of days. I actually borrowed it from my friend for test images. It is definately a leap foeard from Nikon's entry level D3000, D3100 in many ways. Most amateurs think that more Mega Pixel makes better picture. WRONG! It all depends on sensor size and image proessing hardware of the camera. When there are too many pixels get packed onto a same size sensor, light sensitivity of each pixel reduces marginally which tends to nullify quality gain. Additionally, image processing engine also play a critical role in reproducing colours, cancelling noise, maintaining highlights, etc. I often when people say that Nikon D3200 uses the same processor of D4. If that was true the camera would have produced same quality photo as D4. It will never! Camera companied try to woo the entry level customers by such eye-wash. My Nikon D200, a pro level camera uses a 10.2 MP sensor. This same size sensor is also found in D3000 which is a entry level camera. BUt Nikon D3000's crappy image can not be compared with D200's professional quiality imaging. I would any time go for lesser pixel in a camera (if the sensor size is same) assuming that the pixels will be less densed which makes each pixel more sensitive to light.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Flipkart delivered this Camera within 2 days with good packing. Thanks for such fastest delivery. Price also very reasonable. I am very Happy to buy this camera on Flipkart.  Nikon D3200 DSLR Camera is a Great Camera. I used this product from last 2 weeks. Pros: 1. Very easy to use because of Guide mode and Auto mode 2. Best Quality of Photo with 24 Megapixels 3. Fast performance with Expeed 3 image processor  4. Nice HD video recording 5. Great photos in low light with Flash 6. 11 focus points helps to achieve sharply focused images 7. 3 inch LCD screen useful for the videos recording 8. Software is user friendly, easy to access and make changes in setting 9. 18-55 mm Lens provides great picture quality. 10. Dust reduction, image sensor cleaning function is too good. 11. Light weight and Nice Design which provides comfortable while using it 12. DSLR Tutorial DVD is very helpful before using the DSLR Camera  Cons: 1. Full charged battery clicked only 150 photos with LCD display. It may increase while using only viewfinder 2. No other cons found.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">Bought this camera just the next day of its launch in India, and Nikon delivered what I expected for. Its a good choice if you're new to photography and I love it... Pros: * Awesome photo quality even in low lights (night lights, or inside home) * 24MP helps when you want to crop an image * Auto focusing is ok and good image stabilization with its default kit lens (18-55, VR-2 lens) * Good battery backup  Cons: * No flipping screen  Additional accessories you might need: * UV filter. Its just to protect your lens. Most of the shops will give it for free (else might cost you 100). * A tripod. If you want to be a photographer (or look like a photographer), its a necessary one. Even this you might get it for free. * External flash (optional). The default flash is fair enough. If you're expecting good lighting effect for your indoor effect, you might need one. I bought "Nikon Speedlight SB-400" and its worth. But again, its an optional one.  I bought it in G.K Vale for ~37K (tripod, uv filter, 4GB memory card, bag, lens cleaning set and 100 free photographs in g.k vale) It was not available in flipkart that time but now it has with better price.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/4000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">30 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Monaural</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="PictBridge">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">EN-EL14 Rechargeable Li-ion Battery (with terminal cover), MH-24 Battery Charger, AN-DC3 Strap, EG-CP14 Audio/Video Cable, UC-E17 USB Cable, DK-5 Eyepiece Cap, BS-1 Accessory Shoe Cover, DK-20 Rubber Eyecup, BF-1B Body Cap, ViewNX 2 CD-ROM, Reference CD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">D3200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off</specsKey>
<specsKey="External Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">APS-C</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">24.2 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">4512 x 3000 (M), 3008 x 2000 (S), 1920 x 1080, 1280 x 720, 640 x 424</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Phase Detection</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">18 - 55 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 27 - 82.5 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F5.6</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dust Reduction">Image Sensor Cleaning</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix Metering: 3D Color Matrix Metering II (Type G and D Lenses), Color Matrix Metering II (Other CPU Lenses), Center-weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sync Terminal">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 4 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO in steps of 1 EV (100 - 6400), 1 EV above ISO (12800 Equivalent)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Incandescent, Fluorescent (7 Types), Direct Sunlight, Flash, Cloudy, Shade, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2, 5, 10 and 20 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type C, Mini HDMI</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">26</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">Nikon F Lens Mount (with AF Contact), 1.5x Lens Focal Length (35 mm Format Equivalent, Nikon DX Format), 24.7 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Land...View More

Nikon F Lens Mount (with AF Contact), 1.5x Lens Focal Length (35 mm Format Equivalent, Nikon DX Format), 24.7 Total Megapixels, Dust Reduction System: Image Dust Off Reference Data (Optional Capture NX 2 Software Required), Picture Control System: Standard, Neutral, Vivid, Monochrome, Portrait, Landscape, Viewfinder Frame Cavarage: 95% Horizontal and 95% Vertical, Viewfinder Magnification: 0.8 x (50 mm f/1.4 Lens at infinity, -1.0 m-1), 18 mm Eyepoint, -1.7 - 0.5 m-1 Diopter Adjustment, Type B BriteView Clear Matte Mark VII Focusing Screen, Quick Return Reflex Mirror, Lens Aperture: Instant Return, Electronically Controlled, Compatible Lenses: Autofocus is Available with AF-S and AF-I Lenses, Autofocus is not Available with Other Type G and D Lenses, AF Lenses (IX NIKKOR and Lenses for the F3AF are not Supported), and AI-P Lenses, Non-CPU Lenses can be Used in Mode M, but the Camera Exposure Meter will not Function. The Electronic Rangefinder can be Wsed with Lenses that have a Maximum Aperture of f/5.6 or Faster, X=1/200 sec Flash Sync Speed, Release Mode: Single Frame, Continuous, Self-timer, Delayed Remote, Quick-response Remote, Quiet Shutter Release, Metering: TTL Exposure Metering using 420-pixel RGB Sensor, Range (ISO 100, f/1.4 Lens, 20C/68F): Matrix or Center-weighted Metering: 0 - 20 EV Spot Metering: 2 - 20 EV, CPU Exposure Meter Coupling, Exposure Mode: Auto Modes (Auto, Auto (Flash Off), Scene Modes (Portrait, Landscape, Child, Sports, Close Up, Night Portrait), Programmed Auto with Flexible Program (P), Shutter-priority Auto (S), Aperture-priority Auto (A), Manual (M), Exposure Compensation: 5 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Exposure Lock: Luminosity Locked at Detected Value with AE-L/AF-L Button, On and Off Active D-Lighting, Focus Detection Range: -1 - EV (ISO 100, 20C/68F), Lens Servo: Autofocus (AF), Single-servo AF (AF-S), Continuous-servo AF (AF-C), Auto AF-S/AF-C Selection (AF-A); Predictive Focus Tracking Activated Automatically According to Subject Status, Anual Focus (MF): Electronic Rangefinder, 11 Focus Point, AF-area Mode: Single-point AF, Dynamic-area AF, Auto-area AF, 3D-tracking (11 Points), Focus Lock, Built-in Flash: Auto, portrait, child, close up, night portrait: Auto Flash with Auto Pop-up, Program, Shutter-priority, Aperture-priority, Manual, Manual Pop-up with Button Release, Guide Number: 12/39, 13/43 with manual flash (m/ft, ISO 100, 20C/68F), Flash Compensation: -3 - EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Flash-ready Indicator, Accessory Shoe: ISO 518 Hot-shoe with Sync and Data Contacts and Safety Lock, Nikon Creative Lighting System (CLS), AS-15 Sync Terminal Adapter (Sold Separately), Playback: Full-frame and Thumbnail (4, 9, or 72 Images or Calendar) Playback with Playback Zoom, Movie Playback, Photo and/or Movie Slide Shows, Histogram Display, Highlights, Auto Image Rotation, and Image Comment (up to 36 Characters)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">6016 x 4000 (L)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, NEF (RAW), NEF (RAW) JPEG, EXIF 2.3, DCF 2.0, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">Linear PCM</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, MPEG-4 / H.264</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">EH-5b AC Adapter</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">505 g (with Battery and Memory Card but without Cap), 455 g (with Camera Body Only)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">125 (W) x 96 (H) x 76.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body & lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Carry in</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC / Compatible with UHS-I</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30p</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">921,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Viewfinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
<specsKey="ViewFinder">Yes, Eye-level Pentamirror</specsKey>
