<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s2700-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdgw7vg6jpzszb?pid=CAMDGWCPXJJXYHHX&otracker=from-search&srno=t_120&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2HHC0RGA01tEUY1R8LEo8Kh5YrsjTRIbWTklp%2FkHDNW4aLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=8bbd11b5-1f29-4feb-ac51-5887ad0263da</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">3.7</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">51</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">29</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img5a.flixcart.com/image/camera/h/h/x/nikon-coolpix-s2700-point-shoot-400x400-imadgwec6anwn3hh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">5580</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S2700 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Pink</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I bought this camera 5 days ago from Great Eastern Trading Co, Kolkata. I am here  to help you customers who are thinking to buy this product or can't decide. About Nikon S2700:--  Pros :- 1. Good 16.1mp CCD image sensor, produces great quality image & accurate colours  in bright light. Being a very cheap & entry level CCD, low light picture is not superb  but it's decent. 2. Loss-less optical zoom, excellent image even in 6x zoom. Digital zoom is good  also(4x). 3. HD video can be recorded when zoomed. 4. Very handy, slim, light weight & beautiful design. 5. USB charging when connected to a computer or AC adapter (multi USB). 6. It got everything it should have at this price.  Cons :- 1. Battery is small & not very powerful. It's 220 shots or 25 mins HD video can be  taken/recorded when fully charged. 2. Its image stabilization feature has some problem so sometimes (not always)  produces less sharp images (when viewed in full resolution) even in steady shot  mode. But it is decent and manageable.  Others :- 1. Its built quality is good enough but not upto the mark. 2. Has no pause option during video recording. It's actually not a disadvantage because none of the cameras in this price range has this feature. They all produce  video clips only. 3. 2years warranty.  Inside the box :- Camera, battery, 4 GB SDHC memory card, USB cable, AC adapter (AC-UB 10C), power cord, AV cable, wrist strap, user manual, warranty card.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">good product in this price range,but the watch which is free is not upto the expectation.service of flipkart is excellent ,</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">I bought it looking at the brand and cost. Assumed it would click decent pictures. But for my dismay the picture quality isn't that great. My samsung mobile takes a better picture. Lot of disturbances in the photos. could find the disturbances when i did 20% zoom in. Bought this April 2013 and now the camera is gone for a lost. There seems to be a big problem.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">i got this camera from flipkart with very fast delivery service, with nice packing and with UCB watch, 4 GB memory card camera pouch and strap, this is an small wonder with lots of functions, battery back-up is very good you can take 200 shots with a single charge lot of picture modes are there. but there are one problem with this product it is little bit slow when we taking continuous shots it take little time to records first image and then take another image. you can go for it if you have tight budget</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">It is a very good product from Nikon. I am always looks for performance of any electronic good. This camera is an excellent one. Very compatible in size and nice 6x optical zoom. It is worth for normal home usage and shooting very special moments in your life.   Also very good packaged delivery from Flipkart within delivery time. Thanks to Flipkart and Nikon..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Nikon's new S2700 is a good product. Though there are no new features that make it stand out, but if you are looking for a digi cam for under INR 6K. This is wat u should buy....  Pros: Picture quality is very gud....  16 Mega is good for screen viewing.   Cons: I found one drawback - its slow at the time of deleting pictures.....</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I was looking for some basic camera for my parents, easy to handle, nice picture quality. This one really satisfied me.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">I have bought this product 2 months ago, its a overall good product at this price but my suggestion would be invest some more and go for type CMOS.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Good Camera. Slick. Works well. Price Acceptable. Innovative design. Good for starters.  $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">I bought this camera recently, and have been using Sony's Digital Cameras until now. There is a distinct difference between Sony and Nikon products. It starts from everything like picture quality, battery back up, processing time for consecutive pics etc. Unlike Sony cams Nikon does not offer you any verity of shooting mode, I would stronly suggest NOT to go for this camera, instead buy a SONY</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Image Size: 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA 640 x 480, 16:9 Aspect Ratio 4608 x 2592, Movie: VGA: 640 x 480, 30 fps, QVGA: 320 x 240, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Auto Focus</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 27.6 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 156 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">6x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">125 g (with Battery and SD Meomry Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">94.8 (W) x 57.8 (H) x 20.8 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">1 year Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD Monitor</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1280 x 720, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">16:09</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Charging AC Adapter EH-70P, USB Cable UC-E6, ViewNX 2 CD, Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL19 (with battery case), Reference Manual CD, Camera Strap</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S2700</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 4.0 m (W), 0.5 m - 2.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 6 Images at 1.3 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 80 - 1600, ISO 3200 (Auto Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">26 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256 Segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">16.44 Megapixel Total Pixels, Construction: 5 Elements in 5 Groups, Blur Reduction Motion Detection (Still Pictures), Contrast-detect AF, Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Auto (9 Area Automatic Selection), Center, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, 5 Level Brightness Adjustment, Frame...View More

16.44 Megapixel Total Pixels, Construction: 5 Elements in 5 Groups, Blur Reduction Motion Detection (Still Pictures), Contrast-detect AF, Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Auto (9 Area Automatic Selection), Center, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Subject Tracking, 5 Level Brightness Adjustment, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 98% Horizontal and 98% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 100% Horizontal and 100% Vertical (Compared to Actual Image), Continuous Shooting: Single (Default Setting), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16, Exposure Compensation: -2.0 - .0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Shutter: Mechanical and Charge-coupled Electronic Shutter, Aperture: Electronically-controlled ND Filter (-3.3 AV) Selection, 2 Steps Range (f/3.5 and f/11.5 (W)), Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, Charging Time: 2 hrs 30 min, 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Operating Temperature: 0° C - 40° C, Humidity: 85%, Versatile Image Expressions and Editing Features, Scene Auto Selector Simply Activates the Optimal Mode, EXPEED C2 Image-processing Engine, Smart Portrait System, Subject Tracking, Eye-Fi Card Support</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">AVI (Motion JPEG Compliant)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">42 MB</specsKey>
