<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s5200-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdgw8ybwneg8fb?pid=CAMDGW88WFBVU7BT&otracker=from-search&srno=t_161&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff1aC2F9gXDkqm0TT3MlHGseY%2FGfwy8Hdd%2FbAfZ%2FmKkJvoaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=a1b53757-b30a-4964-8785-1ac6f15c41cf</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.1</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">37</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">18</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/7/b/t/nikon-coolpix-s5200-point-shoot-400x400-imadgwchgmydctea.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">7160</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S5200 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.9</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Blue</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">Great delivery by Flipkart within 24 hours of ordering. But one minor issue - instead of Micro HDMI Cable, the box has Mini HDMI Cable. Called up the customer service and now am expecting a callback in 24-48 hours from Flipkart.  Camera has been awesome looks and quality wise. Charged for 2 hours and took few snaps. Good number of accessories cables have been provided.  This is my third camera in the last 10 years and am just amazed at how feature rich these models are these days.  Recommend this, not for the Wi-Fi feature, but for the CMOS sensor + Full HD video recording.  UPDATE on HDMI Cable Issue: Flipkart & WS Retail representatives called me up and finally Micro HDMI cable has been dispatched today. Great customer service by Flipkart & WS Retail. I would definitely love to buy more products from Flipkart & WS Retail in future.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">Bought with the expectation of a good product & cheap price but made a mistake.  I received a faulty product & had to go through servicing it with Nikon. The service was pretty pathetic as well & took a long time. But the product works OK now, I would recommended a different brand</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Nikon Coolpix S5200 Verdict The headline feature on the S5200 is its built-in Wi-Fi, You can also use your mobile device for remote shooting. camera can edit pictures, the camera is a fairly standard digital compact, with a 16 megapixel sensor and 5x optical zoom. Its image quality is OK.  Nikon Coolpix S5200 Pros Built-in Wi-Fi Records at up to 10 fps Easy Panorama 360Â°/180Â° Available in a range of colours  Nikon Coolpix S5200 Cons Short battery life No optical image stabilisation Images are noisy from ISO 800 upwards</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">the brand "Nikon" only makes cameras and that's why you can trust it anywhere anytime. I have purchased this product from a reputed electronics shop from my locality and i am very satisfied. As I'm not a photographer, i did not want a DSLR. I went for a point&shoot and got the best product.. the only con of this camera is it's battery backup is not so good but ok.  Overall I will recommend this product to every beginners ... for everyday use its very nice and classy.. I love my Nikon..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">I am not happy with this camera. I m still in search whether flipkart provided faulty piece or Nikon.I m using with proper care still I had problem of lens error twice in 6 months which costed Rs 4500.worst experience.NEVER BUY....PLEASE</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">camera is good what i liked about is video recording awesome recording with stero sound direct attachment with my tv through the hdmi cable which i got from the seller itself . we can also pause and resume the video while recording .</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">Good value for money.. High quality pics and some impressive filters.. Happy with the product overall..</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Good Camera worth money... I also own a Nikon DSLR which I like a lot with very good pictures taken..  Just wanted to buy a sleek cam for which I again opted Nikon.. compares with other brands also, S5200 was something more convincing...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">superb, handy lightweight & very good features in Nikon Coolpix S5200 Point & Shoot camera & hats off to flipkart for flipkart for timely delivery</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">it is very useful and clear its having a 3*3 lens it is very light and very good for daily use. it is not so clear at maximum zoom and at dark</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Stereo</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S5200</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, Auto with Red-eye Reduction, Auto Slow Sync, Auto Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Fill-flash, Red-eye Reduction, Slow Sync, Slow Sync with Red-eye Reduction, Rear-curtain with Slow Sync, Rear-curtain Sync, Off: Auto FP High-Speed Sync Supported</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 4.0 m (W), 1.0 m - 2.0 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CMOS</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Other Resolution">Image Size: 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA (640 x 480), 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 4608 x 2592, Movie: 1080 / 30p (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 1080 / 30p: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 720 / 30p: 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, iFrame 540 / 30p: 960 x 540 / 16:9 /...View More

Image Size: 3264 x 2448 (8 M), 2272 x 1704 (4 M), 1600 x 1200 (2 M), VGA (640 x 480), 16:9 Aspect Ratio: 4608 x 2592, Movie: 1080 / 30p (Default Setting): 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 1080 / 30p: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 720 / 30p: 1280 x 720 / 16:9 / 30 fps, iFrame 540 / 30p: 960 x 540 / 16:9 / 30 fps, 480 / 30p: 640 x 480 / 4:3 / 30 fps, HS 480 / 4x: 640 x 480 / 4:3, HS 720 / 2x: 1280 x 720 / 16:9, HS 1080 / 0.5x: 1920 x 1080 / 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">TTL Auto Focus</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 27.6 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 156 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot</specsKey>
<specsKey="Delete Function">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 10 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">ISO 125 - 1600, ISO 3200 (Auto Mode)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Cloudy, Daylight, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Preset Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="HDMI">Type D, Micro HDMI Output</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">31</specsKey>
<specsKey="Additional Features">16.79 Million Totalpixels, Built-in Wi-Fi, Construction: 5 Elements in 5 Groups, Motion Blur Reduction Detection (Still Pictures), Autofocus (AF): Contrast-detect AF, Focus Range: 50 cm (W) - 1 m (T), Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Center, Subject Tracking, Target F...View More

16.79 Million Totalpixels, Built-in Wi-Fi, Construction: 5 Elements in 5 Groups, Motion Blur Reduction Detection (Still Pictures), Autofocus (AF): Contrast-detect AF, Focus Range: 50 cm (W) - 1 m (T), Focus-area Selection (Face Priority, Manual with 99 Focus Areas, Center, Subject Tracking, Target Finding AF), 5-level Brightness Adjustment, Frame Coverage (Shooting Mode): 99% Horizontal and 99% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Frame Coverage (Playback Mode): 99% Horizontal and 99% Vertical (Compared to Actual Picture), Continuous Shooting (Single (Default Setting), Continuous H (Images are Captured Continuously at Rate of About 10 fps), Continuous L (upto 6 Images are Captured Continuously at Rate of upto About 2 fps), Pre-shooting Cache (Frame Rate: upto 18 fps / Number of Frames: upto 5 Frames), Continuous H:120 fps (50 Frames are Captured at Speed of About 1/125 sec or Faster), Continuous H:60 fps (25 Frames are Captured at Speed of About 1/60 sec or Faster), BSS (Best Shot Selector), Multi-shot 16), Exposure Compensation: -2.0 - .0 EV in increments of 1/3 EV, Shutter: Mechanical and CMOS Electronic Shutter, Aperture: Electronically-controlled ND Filter (-3.3 AV) Selection, 2 Steps Range (f/3.5 and f/11.5 (W)), Data Transfer Protocol: MTP, PTP, HDMI Output: Can be Selected from Auto, 480p, 720p, and 1080i, 3 hrs Charging Time, 1/4 inch Tripod Socket, Operating Temperature: 0° C - 40&deg C, Humidity: 85%, Wi-Fi (Wireless LAN): Standards IEEE 802.11 b/g/n (Standard Wireless LAN Protocol), High-quality Images and Movies Directly to Smart Device, Back-illuminated 16-MP CMOS Sensor, Smart Portrait System, High-speed Continuous Shooting, 19 Scene Modes, Subject Tracking AF, Retouch Menu, EXPEED C2 Image Processing System</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">6x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456 (16 M)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party / Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk / Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Easy Panorama, Pet Portrait, 3D Photography), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, MPO, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF, MPF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV, AAC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">MOV, H.264 / MPEG-4 AVC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">146 g (with Battery and SD Meomry Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">97.7 (W) x 58.4 (H) x 21.3 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Operating System">Windows XP, Windows Vista, Windows 7, Windows 8, Mac OS X10.6, 10.7, 10.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">25 MB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Wi-Fi">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Display Resolution">1920 x 1080, 30 fps</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">460,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
