<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s2500/p/itmdv58gtpfa58jw?pid=CAMCW26FTWHG9HXZ&otracker=from-search&srno=t_267&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff0yHMPZ%2FuY0OdYHIRK9%2Bm9ebQDUl1rBvAnnGkxu9FQsNIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=8531cd2f-10cf-4074-a34b-6793a7ed5459</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">41</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">12</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/h/x/z/nikon-s2500-point-shoot-400x400-imacxhq5bhjefgyh.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">5534</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S2500</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Silver</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">i have purchased from flipkart and it is very cool camera if anybody wants to purchase a camera in range of 6000 so Nikon Coolpix S2500 is a very good option for you   The Nikon Coolpix S2500 is a 12 megapixel compact digital camera. This Coolpix camera uses Nikon's EXPEED C2 Image Processing Engine and has a 1/2.3-inch CCD sensor. The S2500 has a 20 mm slim body, which makes it easier to carry around.  Body This Coolpix camera weighs 117 g (with battery and memory card) and has dimension of 93.1 x 57.1 x 20.0 mm. The 2.7-inch TFT LCD monitor in this Nikon camera has resolution of 230,000 dot pixels. The S2500 comes with an internal memory of 16 MB and additional external memory can be added using SD, SDHC, or SDXC memory card. The camera kit comes with rechargeable Li-ion battery EN-EL19, which can take up to 220 shots per charge.  Performance The Nikon Coolpix S2500 uses the 4x zoom NIKKOR lens with focal length of 4.9 - 19.6 mm. The camera can zoom digitally and optically up to 4x. The Auto Focus of the camera has a range of 50 cm in Normal mode and 8 cm in Macro mode. The Auto ISO sensitivity of the S2500 ranges from ISO 80 - 1600 and Manual ISO ranges from ISO 80 - 3200. This Coolpix camera has Aperture range of f/3.2-5.9.  Features and Connectivity The Coolpix S2500 has Electronic VR and BSS (Best Shot Selector) image stabilization feature. The camera supports various scene modes such as Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night portrait, Party/indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk/dawn, Night landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting and Panorama assist.  The Self timer function can be set at 2 or 10 sec duration. The camera can also shoot in Continuous mode at 0.9 fps for up to 3 shots. The Nikon Coolpix S2500 can shoot video in VGA (640 x 480) resolution and supports mono/wav file, AVI movie formats. The images are saved in Compressed JPEG - EXIF format. The S2500 compact digital camera supports Hi-speed USB.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">First i thought of buying sony cybershot, but i don't know what had happened to me, i changed my mind and bought this one. Then i felt very guilty for not buying sony. But then i realized when i saw the pictures that I've taken with Nikon in my laptop. It was amazing! The clarity is superb! Even i compared these pictures with the pictures that I've taken from sony, definitely Nikon scores over sony! Coming to features, It got 4x optical zoom where your picture clarity will not be affected and 4x digital zoom where your picture clarity will slightly less. It got auto focus, manual focus and many scene selections. It also includes smile detector. The only thing it lacking is HD video recording and panorama, but you can create panorama by panorama maker software given with the camera. so if you want to buy a camera around 6000 rupees, just GO FOR IT!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">I purchased Nikon Coolpix S2500 from Flipkart.com the service of flipkart seems good but I am not at all happy with its Battery. The battery got spoiled with in a month which is against a goodwill of Nikon.  I will rather suggest to not go with Nikon......</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">the nikon s2500 is a good camera, gives good pics in both night and daylight pictures .i had bought the silver one from a retailer   the other night. I felt that i might have lacked in some features if compared to a higher price camera eg: sony , canon . in this level of price this the best camera which i felt . if u need a camera for trips , excursions go for it .</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">Bought this digicam with my 1st scholarship, 2years ago. Everything is fine, only the night time photographs are little poor in quality as compared to canon. Daylight photos are as superb as heaven, you cannot complaint abt it ever.  But guys NEVER go for a digital camera if you are not a professional photographer. Dont waste your money for fun. Why I am saying this??   These companies give product at cheap price, but the accessories, battery and service are costly as HELL. Battery (Nikon EN-EL19 Rechargeable Li-ion Battery) price for this cam is Rs 8214. ABOUT DOUBLE THE PRICE OF CAMERA !!!! http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-en-el19-rechargeable-li-ion-battery/p/itmdy5hqtn2ypgpf?pid=ACCDY5HZNNWCHUW8&  And forget about service after warrenty period. It is so costly that you will prefer not to repair it. Thats why my brothers I said "Dont buy digicams if you are not an professional"  Even if you buy the camera, dont leave the battery in the camera even for a day. The current leaches out continuously and battery will be dead in few months. It can even damage your camera's motherboard. I am suferring from both of these issues, so its my duty to aware you of their dirty business strategy.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">I bought my S2500 from a shopping mall in New Delhi towards the end of Dec 2011. I thought I will write about my experiences with this camera   For initial few months, results were amazing. I tried all the picture modes (except the panorama) in almost all weather conditions and was delighted by picture quality. It is an easy to use system and connects well with your computer. And when you get all of this for 5772, it sure is a bargain.  However, after continuous usage (i.e. after 6 months) I discovered that:  1. Buttons started malfunction (e.g. Flash toggle button offers menu for trashing the pic) 2. Images started turning ‘shaky’ (funnily enough, I thought it is a problem with stability of my hands. However, later, a friend who is using Nikon Coolpix L810 confirmed that even he is facing similar problems) 3. Battery backup is noticeably lower than comparable peers from other OEMs.  I went to Nikon Service centres (Noida pickup centre & Karol Bagh) and they were not able to fix it to my satisfaction (that is altogether a different story though and I will not write about it here).   Please excuse if I sounded too naïve, this was my first review :-)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">I have been using this camera for last 2 years...its a nice, basic point and shoot with easy shooting modes...it is very lightweight and sleek...video quality of this camera is poor so Nikon L26 would be a better option with same price and added feature of 720p video recording...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Hi, This is awesome camera in the budget range. Anyone can click with this camera & no need to have great knowledge to operate digital camera. In one line" Bas Camera Lao Photographer Ban Jao". Great Video recording with HD movie button. Separate recording button & separate button to click the photos. The only problem is with the recording:-No pause button to hold the recording when you want to stay for a while. Remaining are the very good.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">I did a lot of homework before zeroing in on this model for its Value For Money. The offer of a watch and the purse was not available in the retail stores but was available on Flipkart. Apart from this advantage, I could play around with the billing cycle of Credit card payment as well as the EMI.  For simple point and shoot, this could be the most recommended. Night time photos still aren't as good as the high end model, but for a person who bought the last digicam ten years ago, this has been a revelation. The battery backup is amazing. At 5MP (which is 2.5 times better than a mere 2 MP resolution generally required for a good photo print), in a 4GB memory card, it saves some 2500 snaps.  As usual, the Flipkart service and delivery has been fantastic. Strongly recommended for the price band.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">If you are looking for a decent digital camera with basic features and you have fixed less than 6 K as the budget than this is one of the best choices you could get.  Its very light weight, 12 mp gives good details for your shots, clarity is good in both indoor and outdoor shots.Video is not very great but watchable.  Plese make sure you set the ISO setting to 200 or preferably even below that (this model provides option to change ISO manually) as at ISOs > 200, the picture gets grains.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">Coolpix S2500</specsKey>
