<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-freebie-timex-watch-point-shoot-camera/p/itmdpejmqagjq3j2?pid=CAMDPEJHTSHHCSSF&otracker=from-search&srno=t_396&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2iloZAEKklnlcqow7uRw6jZpkpm6IgHYLSJKOpfHVjoIaLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=e824cc8c-17db-49de-ba96-24b339c84fe0</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">124</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">11</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com/image/camera/s/s/f/nikon-freebie-timex-watch-for-nikon-point-shoot-400x400-imadqzfz8r3wrhwm.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">349</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Freebie (Timex Watch) for Nikon Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">1.0</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">I got it free with Nikon camera..excellent watch!!! Look very dashing and amazing...I love this watch very much...... Worth buying!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I found this watch so nice... got free with Nikon!!!!!!!!!!!! Awesome gift pack for my Friend...!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Great watch and really great to have got it free with the nikon camera. the build quality is great and the packaging is awesome.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">Excellent in one word..... in this price..... i get this in Free with nikon 20.1 MP camera from flipkart :) thankyou flipkart......... awesome packing & delivery :)</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">found ok, one thing is that it give one addition benefit of the timex watch watch was much better for elder ones .</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">Freebies can be that good and useful? Thanks Nikkon.  I got it with Nikkon D5100 in Nov 13. Using the watch daily. Still as good as new.No complain!! Didnt éxpect this performance from a freebie. I got the cam from local retailer and the watch as well.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">best camera and watch as well just loved it and its damn awsum watch very cute.... ppl just keep looking at my watch its so much awsum and with a great deal its nice</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">Very good gadget and cost wise also is not expensive. Always ready for shoot in daily use. Nikon company should provide standard rechargeable battery with the gadget then use becomes more useful.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">NOT WOKING WELL. I can reset the time every day. some time 2 or 3 times a day. i can advise Don't purchse</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">I am buy Nikon Freebie (Timex Watch) for Nikon Point & Shoot Camera. this is good looking product for me . I buy this product again and again.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">Freebie (Timex Watch) for Nikon</specsKey>
