<specsKey="link">http://www.flipkart.com/nikon-coolpix-s3300-point-shoot-camera/p/itmd7fnxjfjhzxvk?pid=CAMD72H4S2K8QHGU&otracker=from-search&srno=t_321&query=nikon&al=WoEJrNIH%2Ff2SjdHyD6YhnG5ow24b68Xti3Vk3f11efczMHyzyctwh4aLq2lx4bRfFLwHQxVDMNU%3D&ref=77a115fb-88a1-4e50-bcef-820488540c3b</specsKey>
<specsKey="avg_rating">4.3</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_ratings">103</specsKey>
<specsKey="number_of_reviews">28</specsKey>
<specsKey="img_url">http://img6a.flixcart.com//image/camera/h/g/u/nikon-s3300-400x400-imad73sqauutgw6g.jpeg</specsKey>
<specsKey="price">6255</specsKey>
<specsKey="title">Nikon Coolpix S3300 Point & Shoot Camera</specsKey>
<specsKey="sentiment_score">0.8</specsKey>
<specsKey="color">Pink</specsKey>
<specsKey="type">Point & Shoot</specsKey>
<specsKey="review1">First things first, I placed the order for this camera through flipkart on Tue 10:55 PM and they delivered it by Thu afternoon. Their packing and delivery system is just awesome. Keep it up.  Review about the camera, I did 1 week of research to narrow down to this camera. In a word, its just awesome. There were couple of review comments that said it takes longer time (6-8 seconds) for the camera to store the image and get ready for the next shoot. This is not true, it is less than 3 seconds. I did test this on various shooting modes (only photo not the video)  Ease of use: My earlier camera was a Canon Powershot, I have been using that for almost 6 years now, at first with Nikon S3300 I fumbled a bit but within no time I got the hang of it.  Quality of Images: Simply superb.  Battery Charging: You don't have to actually remove the battery from the camera to charge it, this in my opinion is a really cool feature.  Interface: I'm used to Canon's mechanical interface, it is taking some time for me to adjust on this.  Software's accompanying the Camera: I'm an Ubuntu fan, so View NX2 is of no use to me. That being said, Shotwell, a photography managing tool from Ubuntu is all you need. However, I suspect that the post processing for panoramic view will not be possible using shotwell.   My Verdict: Total value for money with no compromise. I would highly recommend this product for people who are transitioning from a beginner to practitioner in photography.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review2">I bought this camera some time back after going through many reviews and ground work and all.But i have to say my work was not good because after all that i ended up with this piece of junk.It lures you in with its attractive colors and other feature sets and all.but it fails to perform as it is expected to perform.The camera worked well for the first two weeks but then after that it started to crate problems.its responsiveness towards low light settings was pathetic.Also the time for the shutter to close after pressing the shutter release button also was slow. Overall the camera is very slow now and its image processing powers have reduced very much.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review3">Great cam as compare to Canon PowerShot A 3300 IS Point & Shoot , its has 6x optical zoom , very slim and handy. the image quality is too good with 16 megapixel . and the most beautiful feature of it is its style , Canon PowerShot A 3300 can't beat this in look. the image clearity is too good , the worst part is its speed it takes some time to click another pic , but overall its a good product. the best part of this cam is its macro mode , i clicked a lot of insects , flowers etc pics with a very good quality.  for a novice user it may not be a good cam , but for a avg and expert its great.  in this range this is the best cam i found.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review4">its absolutely worst service i have ever seen buy it and keep shuttling to service station i was not even able to use it for the pourpose of my brothers marrige its still with service people since i bought the instrument and service people are not all good and competetive</specsKey>
<specsKey="review5">I just got my hand on Nikon Coolpix S3300 Point & Shoot. First of all Flipkart is unbelievable. I ordered yesterday only. Now about the product. I was confused about buying Nikon nikon coolpix l26 & s3300. Ultimately I ordered this one because i saw some reviews of the both and the pic quality of s3300 (obviously it is costlier) seems to be better. The camera is small and very portable , easily fits in your palm. Because of Lithium Ion battery it works faster. Its one of the reason I choose S3300 over L26 which uses AA battery. The display screen is just ok. But the digital zoom (zooming a photo) works little slow. I took some indoor pictures with flash. Pictures quality is pretty good and not blurred. Outdoor pictures obviously will be far better. Only thing I did not like is the recording. You don't have a pause option. And recording is only for 8 minutes. I don't know may be it can be changed from settings. But for 6000 bucks its really a good buy.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review6">I have brought this camera some 6 months ago. The quality of picture is good and the look is very attractive. On the whole, the camera is good at this price, but I would also like to mention that the processing of this camera is very slow. It take 8-10 seconds time to click next picture. Nikon should work on this.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review7">This piece of product is not up to the mark. Any mobile camera would be much better than this. I am not able to shoot a single snap without shake and noise in a naturally well lit area in my house. Some snaps went absolutely black. No clue what is wrong with this camera.  The body material is slippery to handle, you should have the string attached to your wrist not to have this fall down.  I have turned off the digital zoon - not even worth mentioning this function.  There is significant lag between once you press button and the shutter. Also, significant time taken to save the picture before it gets ready for next one.  Seriously, if I had experienced this camera before I wouldn't have ended up buying this for sure.  Thumps up for FlipKart, delivery excellence continues...</specsKey>
<specsKey="review8">good item i have used this camera and according to my experience t is best product of cameras.and i it's providing best quality pivture and webcom.</specsKey>
<specsKey="review9">Pros: - Battery - Outdoor pics  Cons - No image stabilization - auto focus slips when indoor shots are taken producing blurred images  Advice : Check out Canons</specsKey>
<specsKey="review10">it is a nice camera ... but the negative points are  1. it looks bigger on the site but is actually little smaller than expectations. 2. Its picture quality is not better than any 8MP camera  3. Its cover is such that if you dont care the camera can fall out if  you don t see. however the batter is impressive . the site should have informed that it has a pouch and the 4GB memory free with it.  rest all is as expected nothing to boast of</specsKey>
<specsKey="Maximum Shutter Speed">1/2000 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Minimum Shutter Speed">1 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Sensor Resolution (in MegaPixel)">16 Megapixels</specsKey>
<specsKey="Lens Type">NIKKOR Lens</specsKey>
<specsKey="Auto Focus">Contrast Detect AF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Focal Length">4.6 - 27.6 mm (35 mm Equivalent to 26 - 156 mm)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Manual Focus">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Optical Zoom">6x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Digital Zoom">4x</specsKey>
<specsKey="Weight">128 g (with Battery and SD Memory Card)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Dimensions">94.8 (W) x 57.8 (H) x 19.5 (D) mm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Covered in Warranty">Warranty of the product is limited to only manufacturing defect on camera body.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Summary">2 years Nikon India Warranty and Free Transit Insurance.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Warranty Service Type">Customer needs to carry the product to the nearby Authorized Service Center to get the product repaired or inspected.</specsKey>
<specsKey="Not Covered in Warranty">Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused ...View More

Nikon Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Defects or malfunctions caused by damage resulting from improper care, misuse or abuse of this product or operation of this product contrary to the instructions contained in the owner's manual. Damage or defect caused by accident, sand, water or battery leakage. Damage caused during transportation or mail. Damaged caused by any modifications or servicing performed by person(s) other than NIKON AUTHORISED SERVICE FACILITY. Accessories including batteries, charger, AC adaptor and other consumables. Any electronic data loss due to malfunctioning or repair of this product. Any consequential or incidental damages resulting from any breach of warranty, express or implied, applicable to this product. Nikon India New Extended Service Warranty (Local Warranty) does not apply to any of the followings:- Accessories like batteries, charger, USB cable, AV cable, Adapters, strap, etc. are not covered under warranty. Damage caused due to accident, sand, water, dust, fungus, battery leakage, etc are not covered under warranty. Warranty on free gifts is as per the terms of their respective manufactures, and this warranty does not extend to such gifts. Warranty does not cover the replacement of Product. Warranty does not cover any special, consequential or incidental damages arising in way due to malfunction of the Product such as loss of photography, loss of data, use, profits, or costs and expenses, etc. less</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Display">TFT LCD with Anti-reflection Coating</specsKey>
<specsKey="LCD Screen Size">2.7 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Display Resolution">230,000 dots</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Aspect Ratio">4:3, 16:9</specsKey>
<specsKey="Microphone">Mono</specsKey>
<specsKey="USB Cable">Hi-speed USB</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Video Interface">Audio / Video Output (NTSC, PAL)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sales Package">Rechargeable Li-ion Battery EN-EL19 (with battery case), Charging AC Adapter EH-69P, Audio Video Cable EG-CP14, ViewNX 2 Installer CD, USB Cable UC-E6, Reference Manual CD, Camera Strap</specsKey>
<specsKey="Brand">Nikon</specsKey>
<specsKey="Series">Coolpix</specsKey>
<specsKey="Model ID">S3300</specsKey>
<specsKey="Built in Flash">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Modes">Auto, On, Off, Red-eye, Slow-sync</specsKey>
<specsKey="Flash Range">0.5 - 4.5 m (W), 0.5 - 2.4 m (T)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Size">1/2.3 inch</specsKey>
<specsKey="Sensor Type">CCD</specsKey>
<specsKey="Aperture Range">F3.5 - F6.5</specsKey>
<specsKey="Red Eye Reduction">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Continuous Shots">Yes, 1.3 fps up to 6 Shots</specsKey>
<specsKey="ISO Rating">Auto ISO 80, 100, 200, 400, 800, 1600, 3200 (Auto Gain ISO 80 to 1600), Fixed Range Auto (ISO 80 to 400, 80 to 800)</specsKey>
<specsKey="White Balancing">Auto, Daylight, Cloudy, Flash, Fluorescent, Incandescent, Manual</specsKey>
<specsKey="Picture Angle">26 mm Wide-angle</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Macro Mode">Yes, 5 cm</specsKey>
<specsKey="Self Timer">Yes, 2 and 10 sec</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Supported Languages">27</specsKey>
<specsKey="Metering">256-segment Matrix, Center Weighted, Spot, Multi, Spot AF Area</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Sizing">4608 x 3456</specsKey>
<specsKey="Shooting Modes">Auto, Scene (Scene Auto Selector, Portrait, Landscape, Sports, Night Portrait, Party, Indoor, Beach, Snow, Sunset, Dusk, Dawn, Night Landscape, Close-up, Food, Museum, Fireworks Show, Black and White Copy, Backlighting, Panorama Assist, Pet Portrait), Special Effects, Smart Portrait</specsKey>
<specsKey="Image Format">JPEG, DCF, EXIF 2.3, DPOF</specsKey>
<specsKey="Audio Formats">WAV</specsKey>
<specsKey="Face Detection">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Video Format">AVI (Motion-JPEG)</specsKey>
<specsKey="Power Supply">AC Adapter EH-69P</specsKey>
<specsKey="Battery Type">Lithium Battery</specsKey>
<specsKey="Memory Card Type">SD / SDHC / SDXC</specsKey>
<specsKey="Upgradeable Memory">Yes</specsKey>
<specsKey="Inbuilt Memory">42 MB</specsKey>
